<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Typer</string>
    <string name="input">input</string>
    <string name="wpm"> wpm</string>
<!--    Texts scraped from typerracer.com using the python script.-->
    <string-array name="texts">
        <item>Sticks and stones will break your bones. They seldom let you snooze. Spooky, scary skeletons will wake you with a boo!</item>
        <item>But first, A toast, to Emily. Always the bridesmaid, never the bride! Tell me my dear, can a heart still break once it\'s stopped beating\?</item>
        <item>Say it once, say it twice, take a chance and roll the dice. Ride with the moon in the dead of night.</item>
        <item>Now I have a story that I\'d like to tell about this guy, you all know him, he had me scared as hell! He comes to me at night after I crawl into bed. He\'s burnt up like a weenie and his name is Fred!</item>
        <item>Very superstitious, writing\'s on the wall. Very superstitious, ladders about to fall, thirteen month old baby. Broke the looking glass seven years of bad luck. The good things in your past.</item>
        <item>Back home, everyone is scientist. Even my plumber wins Nobel Prize. Your country does not make enough scientist. Always needs more. You should be a scientist, Victor.</item>
        <item>Walls have ears, doors have eyes, trees have voices, beasts tell lies. Beware the rain, beware the snow. Beware the man you think you know.</item>
        <item>I\'ve seen enough horror movies to know that a weirdo wearing a mask is never friendly.</item>
        <item>On Halloween night, the Great Pumpkin rises from his pumpkin patch and flies through the air with his bag of toys to all the children.</item>
        <item>We\'re sorry skeletons, you\'re so misunderstood. You only want to socialize, but I don\'t think we should cause spooky, scary skeletons shout startling, shrilly screams. They\'ll sneak from their sarcophagus and just won\'t leave you be.</item>
        <item>Out from his coffin, Drac\'s voice did ring. Seems he was troubled by just one thing. He opened the lid and shook his fist and said whatever happened to my Transylvania Twist\?</item>
        <item>I begin tucking him into bed and he tells me, \"Daddy check for monsters under my bed.\" I look underneath for his amusement and see him, another him, under the bed, staring back at me quivering and whispering, \"Daddy there\'s somebody on my bed.\"</item>
        <item>Scooby Dooby Doo, where are you\? We got some work to do now. Scooby Dooby Doo, where are you\? We need some help from you now.</item>
        <item>Ladies and gentlemen. I think the confusion here is that you are all very ignorant. Is that right word, ignorant\? I mean stupid, primitive, unenlightened. You do not understand science, so you are afraid of it. Like a dog is afraid of thunder or balloons. To you, science is magic and witchcraft because you have such small minds. I cannot make your heads bigger, but your children\'s heads, I can take them and crack them open. This is what I try to do, to get at their brains!</item>
        <item>Why am I a sucker for all your lies\? Strung out like laundry on every line. Why do I come back to you like I don\'t mind if you ruin up my life\?</item>
        <item>From my laboratory in the castle east to the master bedroom where the vampires feast. The ghouls all came from their humble abodes to get a jolt from my electrodes.</item>
        <item>Dear Great Pumpkin, I am looking forward to your arrival on Halloween night. I hope you will bring me lots of presents.</item>
        <item>All you have to do is walk up to a house, ring the doorbell, and say tricks or treats.</item>
        <item>I was doing my experiment, my project, and the first time it worked great, but the next time it didn\'t. I mean, it sort of worked, but then it didn\'t and I don\'t know why.</item>
        <item>Science is not good or bad Victor, but it can be used both ways. That is why you must always be careful.</item>
        <item>With this hand I will lift your sorrows. Your cup will never be empty, for I will be your wine. With this candle, I will light your way into darkness. With this ring, I ask you to be mine.</item>
        <item>I was a bride. My dreams were taken from me. But now - now I\'ve stolen them from someone else. I love you, Victor, but you are not mine.</item>
        <item>You don\'t believe the story of the Great Pumpkin\? I thought little girls always believed everything that was told to them. I thought little girls were innocent and trusting.</item>
        <item>I am the one hiding under your bed. Teeth ground sharp and eyes glowing red. I am the one hiding under your stairs. Fingers like snakes and spiders in my hair!</item>
        <item>Halloween is not only about putting on a costume, but it\'s about finding the imagination and costume within ourselves.</item>
        <item>I\'m wondering why do all the monsters come out at night\? Why do we sleep where we want to hide\? Why do I run back to you like I don\'t mind if you ruin up my life\?</item>
        <item>They\'re creepy and they\'re kooky. Mysterious and spooky. They\'re all together ooky. The Addams family! Their house is a museum. When people come to see \'em. They really are a screaming. The Addams family!</item>
        <item>Therefore, it stands to reason, does it not, sisters dear\? That we must find the book, brew the potion and suck the lives out of the children of Salem before sunrise. Otherwise, it\'s curtains. We evaporate! We cease to exist! Dost thou comprehend\?</item>
        <item>I sense there\'s something in the wind. That feels like tragedy\'s at hand and though I\'d like to stand by him. Can\'t shake this feeling that I have. The worst is just around the bend and does he notice my feelings for him and will he see how much he means to me. I think it\'s not to be.</item>
        <item>If I touch a burning candle, I can feel no pain. In the ice or in the sun, it\'s all the same. Yet, I feel my heart is aching. Though it doesn\'t beat, it\'s breaking. And the pain here that I feel, try and tell me it\'s not real. I know that I am dead, yet it seems that I still have some tears to shed.</item>
        <item>Spooky, scary skeletons send shivers down your spine. Shrieking skulls will shock your soul, seal your doom tonight. Spooky, scary skeletons speak with such a screech. You\'ll shake and shudder in surprise when you hear these zombies shriek.</item>
        <item>She had a horror of rooms. She was tired you can\'t hide beat. When I looked in her eyes they were blue but nobody home. She could\'ve been a killer if she didn\'t walk the way she do, and she do. She opened strange doors that we\'d never close again.</item>
        <item>One, two, Freddy\'s coming for you. Three, four, better lock your door. Five, six, grab your crucifix. Seven, eight, gonna stay up late. Nine, ten, never sleep again.</item>
        <item>Friends say I\'m stupid and I\'m out of my mind. But without you, boy, I\'d be bored all the time. No, I don\'t really care for the same conversation. Got everything I need and I\'d rather be chasing. Chasing love, with a monster.</item>
        <item>I was working in the lab, late one night. When my eyes beheld an eerie sight. For my monster from his slab, began to rise and suddenly to my surprise. He did the mash! He did the monster mash! The monster mash! It was a graveyard smash. He did the mash! He did the monster mash!</item>
        <item>Oh, he\'ll buy me a thorn before he\'ll buy me a rose. Be covered in dirt before I\'m covered in gold. He\'s trying it on, yeah, he\'s ticking me off. Say what you want but I won\'t ever be told. Cause I\'m in love with a monster.</item>
        <item>\"It\'s safe to come out now sweetie,\" dad said reassuringly. His blue eyes shining at me through the gap in the bedroom door. He\'s been saying that for hours, but it doesn\'t change the fact that my dad\'s eyes are green.</item>
        <item>Each year, the Great Pumpkin rises out of the pumpkin patch that he thinks is the most sincere. He\'s gotta pick this one. He\'s got to. I don\'t see how a pumpkin patch can be more sincere than this one. You can look around and there\'s not a sign of hypocrisy. Nothing but sincerity as far as the eye can see.</item>
        <item>You know, I think this Christmas thing is not as tricky as it seems! But why should they have all the fun\? It should belong to anyone! Not anyone, in fact, but me! Why, I could make a Christmas tree! And there\'s not a reason I can find, I couldn\'t have a Christmas time! I bet I could improve it, too! And that\'s exactly what I\'ll do!</item>
        <item>He wears the same hat and sweater every single day and even if it\'s hot outside he wears it anyway! He\'s gone when I\'m awake but he shows up when I\'m asleep. I can\'t believe that there\'s a nightmare, on my street!</item>
        <item>This is Halloween, this is Halloween. Pumpkins scream in the dead of night. This is Halloween, everybody make a scene. Trick or treat \'til the neighbors gonna die of fright. It\'s our town, everybody scream in this town of Halloween.</item>
        <item>Hear ye, hear ye! Victor Van Dort seen last night on the bridge in the arms of a mystery woman! The dark-haired temptress and master Van Dort slipped away into the night! And now the weather: scattered showers...</item>
        <item>I got a monster in my closet. Someone\'s underneath my bed. The wind\'s knocking at my window. I\'d kill it but it\'s already dead. At first I was scared when I looked at his eyes but now that I know him I\'m not that surprised. I\'m just waiting on the sun to rise. Oh how I wish that old sun would rise.</item>
        <item>When the Jews return to Zion, and a comet rips the sky, and the Holy Roman Empire rises. Then you and I must die. From the eternal sea he rises, creating armies on either shore. Turning man against his brother \'til man exists no more.</item>
        <item>She began to wail jealousies scream. Waiting at the light know what I mean. Scary monsters, super creeps. Keep me running, running scared.</item>
        <item>Try and hear me then I\'m done cause I might just say this once. Seen this played out in my dream. It doesn\'t matter. Time for giving up the ghost. It\'s you I hate the most and there is no guarantee. It doesn\'t matter.</item>
        <item>Cause the world might do me in. It\'s all right cause I\'m with friends cause I\'m giving up again. It doesn\'t matter and I\'m feeling like a ghost and it\'s what I hate the most cause I\'m giving up again and this time. I might just disappear!</item>
        <item>I used to wonder why he looked familiar. Then, I realized it was a mirror. Oh, and now it is plain to see. The whole time the monster was me. Oh, there\'s a monster in my closet. Someone\'s underneath my bed. The wind\'s knocking at my window. I\'d kill it but it\'s already dead. The living dead.</item>
        <item>So, tell me pretty lies, look me in my face. Tell me that you love me, even if it\'s fake. You can lead me on and leave these questions in my sheets. I\'m under it, I made my bed and I\'m still wondering.</item>
        <item>And there shall be signs in the sun, and in the moon, and in the stars; and upon the earth distress of nations, with perplexity; the sea and the waves roaring; Men\'s hearts failing them for fear, and for looking toward those things which are coming on the earth: for the powers of heaven shall be shaken.</item>
        <item>You know we got a mystery to solve. So, Scooby Doo, be ready for your act. Don\'t hold back and Scooby Doo, if you come through. You\'re gonna have yourself a Scooby Snack. That\'s a fact!</item>
        <item>Then this ebony bird beguiling my sad fancy into smiling, by the grave and stern decorum of the countenance it wore, \'Though thy crest be shorn and shaven, thou,\' I said, \'art sure no craven, ghastly grim and ancient raven wandering from the Nightly shore - tell me what thy lordly name is on the Night\'s Plutonian shore!\' Quoth the Raven, \'Nevermore.\'</item>
        <item>Tis the night - the night of the graves delight and the warlocks are at their play; Ye think that without the wild winds shout, but no, it is they - it is they.</item>
        <item>Don\'t it make you sad to know that life is more than who you are\?</item>
        <item>I\'ve seen it all. I\'ve seen the dark, I\'ve seen the brightness in one little spark. I\'ve seen what I choose and I\'ve seen what I need and that is enough. To want more would be greed.</item>
        <item>I know that I need to close the door and accept that my love wasn\'t appreciated. Not because it was wrong, but because I gave it to someone who couldn\'t understand it.</item>
        <item>I never know if I can handle anything. That\'s what makes my life so exciting.</item>
        <item>No matter how deep the night, it always turns to day eventually.</item>
        <item>You were red and you liked me \'cause I was blue. But you touched me and suddenly I was a lilac sky. And you decided purple just wasn\'t for you.</item>
        <item>Every new medium transforms the nature of human thought. In the long run, history is the story of information becoming aware of itself.</item>
        <item>And all you touch and all you see is all your life will ever be.</item>
        <item>I remember what it was like to love you because I still do.</item>
        <item>My good man, did you simply get carried away with your dramatic gesture or are you pointing the weapon at me with lethal intention\?</item>
        <item>The loneliest people are the kindest. The saddest people smile the brightest. The most damaged people are the wisest. All because they don\'t wish to see anyone else suffer the way they did.</item>
        <item>Would you risk your life, now that you\'ve drawn your pistol are you willing to use it\? I\'m saying that guns aren\'t for threats, they\'re for actions.</item>
        <item>Even though my life hasn\'t been all that great, I figure that if I live long enough, something good might happen.</item>
        <item>If you are observing someone you naturally dislike, or who reminds you of someone unpleasant in your past, you will tend to see almost any cue as unfriendly or hostile. You will do the opposite for people you like. In these exercises you must strive to subtract your personal preferences and prejudices about people.</item>
        <item>I don\'t want to live without your love, I don\'t want to face the night alone. I could never make it through my life, if I had to make it on my own. I don\'t want to love nobody else, I don\'t want to find somebody new, I don\'t want to live without your love, I just want to live my life with you.</item>
        <item>I used to want to save the world. To end the war and bring peace to mankind. But then I glimpsed the darkness that lives within their light and learned that inside every one of them, there will always be both. A choice each must make for themselves. Something no hero will ever defeat. And now I know, that only love can truly save the world. So I stay, I fight, and I give, for the world I know can be. This is my mission now. Forever.</item>
        <item>Bother me, tell me awful things. You know I love it when you move that on me, love it when you do that on me.</item>
        <item>Speak the speech, I pray you, as I pronounced it to you, trippingly on the tongue: but if you mouth it, as many of your players do, I had as lief the town-crier spoke my lines. Nor do not saw the air too much with your hand, thus, but use all gently; for in the very torrent, tempest, and, as I may say, the whirlwind of passion, you must acquire and beget a temperance that may give it smoothness.</item>
        <item>A person is smart. People are dumb, panicky, dangerous animals and you know it. Fifteen hundred years ago everybody knew the Earth was the center of the universe. Five hundred years ago, everybody knew the Earth was flat, and fifteen minutes ago, you knew that humans were alone on this planet. Imagine what you\'ll know tomorrow.</item>
        <item>The wretchedness of slavery, and the blessedness of freedom, were perpetually before me. It was life and death with me. But I remained firm, and, according to my resolution, on the third day of September, 1838, I left my chains, and succeeded in reaching New York without the slightest interruption of any kind.</item>
        <item>If we assume the existence of an omniscient and omnipotent being, one that knows and can do absolutely everything, then to my own very limited self, it would seem that existence for it would be unbearable. Nothing to wonder about\? Nothing to ponder over\? Nothing to discover\? Eternity in such a heaven would surely be indistinguishable from hell.</item>
        <item>Sometimes there are no words, no clever quotes to neatly sum up what\'s happened that day. Sometimes you do everything right, everything exactly right, and still you feel like you failed. Did it need to end that way\? Could something have been done to prevent the tragedy in the first place\?</item>
        <item>My name is Gideon, and I\'m about to die. I was born on a world long since destroyed. Some say I played a hand in its destruction. Less charitable voices say I was the sole cause of its demise. I cared little at the time, as I was blinded by my own self-righteous fury. But then a reckoning came upon me. I found others who could travel between worlds, and whose beliefs conflicted with my own. I was humbled by their power and tempered by their convictions. I resolved to learn from my opponents. I would do better, be better, and fight the very kind of tyrant I had become. For years I had stood alone; in countless battles, I won every time, until now. I\'ve given my all and it wasn\'t enough. But I have a plan. I\'ve done the one thing my opponent could never do. I\'ve made allies out of enemies.</item>
        <item>Words are flowing out like endless rain into a paper cup. They slither while they pass, they slip away across the universe. Pools of sorrow, waves of joy are drifting through my open mind, possessing and caressing me.</item>
        <item>You know, sometimes we\'re not prepared for adversity. When it happens sometimes, we\'re caught short. We don\'t know exactly how to handle it when it comes up. Sometimes, we don\'t know just what to do when adversity takes over. And I have advice for all of us, I got it from my pianist Joe Zawinul who wrote this tune. And it sounds like what you\'re supposed to say when you have that kind of problem. It\'s called mercy, mercy, mercy.</item>
        <item>Here, one of everything! No cheese, no crust, no pickles to the left, four squirts of ketchup, wheat buns, non-dairy lettuce, and farm-raised tomatoes carnival style! And if there is anything else I can do, please hesitate to ask!</item>
        <item>Well Homer, maybe you can take some consolation in the fact that something you created is making so many people happy. Oh, look at me I\'m making people happy! I\'m the magical man, from happy land! In a gumdrop house on lollipop lane! Oh, by the way I was being sarcastic. Well, duh!</item>
        <item>A crystalline solid has long-range order. In other words, its atoms or molecules lie in an orderly arrangement that is repeated over long distances. When the crystal melts, that long-range order is lost. In the liquid, the kinetic energy of the molecules can partly overcome the intermolecular forces, and so the molecules are able to move past one another.</item>
        <item>Just as you can never guarantee that the person you like will like you back, you can never guarantee that the person you hate will hate you. Nor is it always possible that they\'ll let you hate them. We aren\'t characters in a manga... there\'s no human who is all bad. There is no human who is all evil. No one has the same personality when viewed from all angles, and no one has the same personality at all times.</item>
        <item>No man has the right to be an amateur in the matter of physical training. It is a shame for a man to grow old without seeing the beauty and strength of which his body is capable.</item>
        <item>And with her he had found the light. He had discovered the scents and aromas of a spring that was eternally one day away. He had laughed, really laughed, and known with her it would at last be all right. So he had poured all of himself into her, giving her everything; all his hopes, his secret thoughts, his tender dreams; and she had taken them, taken him, all of him, and he had known for the first time what it was to have a place to live, to have a home in someone\'s heart. It was all the silly and gentle things he laughed at in other people, but for him it was breathing deeply of wonder.</item>
        <item>In a hole in the ground, there lived a hobbit. Not a nasty, dirty, wet hole, filled with the ends of worms and an oozy smell, nor yet a dry, bare, sandy hole with nothing in it to sit down on or to eat: it was a hobbit-hole, and that means comfort.</item>
        <item>Over shadowy spires and gleaming towers lay the ghostly darkness and silence that runs before dawn. Into a dim alley, one of a veritable labyrinth of mysterious winding ways, four masked figures came hurriedly from a door which a dusky hand furtively opened. They spoke not but went swiftly into the gloom, cloaks wrapped closely about them; as silently as the ghosts of murdered men they disappeared in the darkness. Behind them a sardonic countenance was framed in the partly opened door; a pair of evil eyes glittered malevolently in the gloom.</item>
        <item>Have you ever heard of the Hedgehog\'s Dilemma\? Hedgehogs have a hard time sharing warmth with other hedgehogs. The closer they get, the more they hurt each other with their quills. People are also like that. I think some part of Shinji is afraid to take that risk because he\'s afraid of being hurt.</item>
        <item>As far as I can tell there are only three kinds of lies: the kind you don\'t want to get caught telling, the kind you don\'t care if you get caught telling, and the kind you can\'t get caught telling.</item>
        <item>Both the stack and the heap are parts of memory that are available to your code to use at runtime, but they are structured in different ways. The stack stores values in the order it gets them and removes the values in the opposite order. This is referred to as last in, first out. Think of a stack of plates: when you add more plates, you put them on top of the pile, and when you need a plate, you take one off the top. Adding or removing plates from the middle or bottom wouldn\'t work as well! Adding data is called pushing onto the stack, and removing data is called popping off the stack.</item>
        <item>I stretched out on the sofa and closed my eyes for a long time, thinking of nothing. It was not hard for me to think of nothing, the way I felt at the moment. In order not to think of any one thing, all I had to do was think of many things, a little at a time: just think about something for a moment and fling it into space.</item>
        <item>What\'s the difference between a king and his horse\? And I\'m not talking about obvious stuff like one\'s an animal and one\'s a person or one has two legs and one has four. Form, ability, and power: that\'s what\'s puzzling. If their form, ability, and power are exactly the same why is it that one becomes the king and leads them into battle, while the other becomes the horse and carries the king\? So what\'s the characteristic that distinguishes these two beings\? There\'s only one answer. Instinct!</item>
        <item>In Evanston, Illinois, in 1875, a law was passed forbidding the sale of ice-cream sodas on Sunday. To get around the law, on Sundays enterprising soda jerks began serving ice cream with syrup but no soda water. The concoction became popular, and on weekdays customers began asking for \"Sundays.\" City officials objected to naming the dish after the Sabbath, so the spelling was changed - and it has been \"sundae\" ever since.</item>
        <item>Closure comes from knowing ourselves, knowing our worth, and finally realizing what we deserve. It\'s seeing the other person for who they really are, not who we\'ve made them to be in our head. I don\'t think he really knows why he acts the way he does. I don\'t think he truly knows himself. If anything, your closure right now is knowing how confused he is. You want a man, not a little boy.</item>
        <item>What is right\? What is wrong\? In this mixed up world, deciding what is right and wrong is not easy. You can\'t just go by somebody else\'s rules. If you let yourself be controlled like that, you\'ll just become a puppet that can\'t make decisions on its own. You have to live by your rules.</item>
        <item>Like roses, we\'re only here for a moment. Ashes to ashes, mountains will always need to be climbed. But we only go one foot at a time. Our voices, trying to be more than just noises. Echo to echo, nobody gets to leave here alive. Don\'t just survive, don\'t just survive.</item>
        <item>The spiritual world and the physical world are constantly intermingling; the spiritual plane is not a vague intangibility but is real and natural, a vast zone of refined substance, of activity and progress, and life there is a continuation of life in the physical world.</item>
        <item>It is believed that shortly after the Big Bang the early universe was composed primarily of hydrogen and helium, with no heavy elements. Today, Earth and its inhabitants contain an abundance of heavier metals. The study of stellar nucleosynthesis strongly suggests these heavier nuclei were generated in the interiors of stars. It can be said that we are all \"star dust,\" the product of heavy element generation within previous generations of stars.</item>
        <item>Crazy how I love the same block that tried to break me. Pray that I ain\'t in my own hood when they take me. This all we know, a life of peace what we can\'t see. I\'m from where we\'re unheard and we can\'t speak. We go to school, they try to tell us what we can\'t be.</item>
        <item>For this reason, it is to be expected that one or more nation-states will undertake covert action to subvert the appeal of transience. Travel could be effectively discouraged by biological warfare, such as the outbreak of a deadly epidemic. This could not only discourage the desire to travel, it could also give jurisdictions throughout the globe an excuse to seal their borders and limit immigration.</item>
        <item>I don\'t want to play in your yard. I don\'t like you anymore. You\'ll be sorry when you see me sliding down your cellar door. You can\'t holler down our rain barrel. You can\'t climb our apple tree. I don\'t want to play in your yard if you can\'t be good to me.</item>
        <item>All seeds contain the tree they will become. In that seed is the limit of its growth. No amount of water or nurture or love can grow a tree taller than the seed has allowed. If it is pushed to grow taller or wider than that, then it will die slowly. It will die of itself. Most things in the universe fade this way. If a tree is to survive then it must make itself content with its height and hide. It must hide its pride and limit its curiosity, lest it birth the end of everything.</item>
        <item>Close friends and relatives, while not meaning to do so, often handicap one through \"opinions\" and sometimes through ridicule, which is meant to be humorous. Thousands of men and women carry inferiority complexes with them all through life, because some well-meaning, but ignorant person destroyed their confidence through \"opinions\" or ridicule.</item>
        <item>We love what we love. Reason does not enter into it. In many ways, unwise love is the truest love. Anyone can love a thing \"because.\" That\'s as easy as putting a penny in your pocket. But to love something \"despite,\" to know the flaws and love them too - that is rare and pure and perfect.</item>
        <item>Sometimes things happen to you that may seem horrible, painful, and unfair at first, but upon reflection you find that without overcoming those obstacles you never would have realized your potential, strength, willpower, or heart.</item>
        <item>It\'s not her shape, her face, or her hair that makes her beautiful. Neither is it the smoothness of her skin, the boldness when she stands or the perseverance in her heart. But the condition of her heart, the gratitude she lives by and her love for God.</item>
        <item>Aggressive behavior in domestic dogs is an issue that has long needed to come out of the closet. There is an incredible stigma attached to dogs that bite, as though they have character flaws and are qualitatively different from dogs who have never bitten. They are not. There are not two kinds of dogs: nice dogs who would never bite and less nice dogs who do. Biting is natural normal dog behavior. This is why it is so prevalent.</item>
        <item>Are you afraid of other people\? I know that by keeping others at a distance you avoid a betrayal of your trust, but you must endure the loneliness. Man can never completely erase this sadness, because all men are fundamentally alone. Pain is something man must carry in his heart, and since the heart feels pain so easily, some believe that life is pain.</item>
        <item>Vlad was right. There are no choices. Nothing but a straight line. The illusion comes afterwards, when you ask, \"Why me\?\" and, \"What if\?\" When you look back, see the branches, like a pruned bonsai tree, or a forked lightning. If you had done something differently, it wouldn\'t be you, it would be someone else looking back, asking a different set of questions.</item>
        <item>When atomic fire consumed the earth, those who survived did so in great, underground vaults. When they opened, their inhabitants set out across ruins of the old world to build new societies, establish new villages, forming tribes. As decades passed, what had been the American Southwest united beneath the flag of the New California Republic, dedicated to old world values of democracy and the rule of law.</item>
        <item>We the people of the United States, in order to form a more perfect union, establish justice, insure domestic tranquility, provide for the common defense, promote the general welfare, and secure the blessings of liberty to ourselves and our posterity, do ordain and establish this Constitution for the United States of America.</item>
        <item>Every portrait that is painted with feeling is a portrait of the artist, not of the sitter. The sitter is merely the accident, the occasion. It is not he who is revealed by the painter; it is rather the painter who, on the coloured canvas, reveals himself.</item>
        <item>Maybe there isn\'t such a thing as fate. Maybe it\'s just the opportunities we\'re given, and what we do with them. I\'m beginning to think that maybe great, epic romances don\'t just happen. We have to make them ourselves.</item>
        <item>Big bolts of lightning hanging low over the coast, everyone\'s convinced it\'s a government drone or alien spaceship. Either way, we\'re not alone. I\'ll find a new place to be from. A haunted house with a picket fence to float around and ghost my friends. No, I\'m not afraid to disappear. The billboard said the end is near. I turned around, there was nothing there. Yeah, I guess the end is here.</item>
        <item>The term hypersensitivity is used to denote inflammation that occurs in response to normally harmless material. For example, animals normally do not react to antigens injected intradermally. If, however, a hypersensitive animal is given an intradermal injection of allergy, it will provoke inflammation.</item>
        <item>If it\'s possible for us to present them with the correct answers, we should do that. But that\'s not always something we can do. Instead, the best we can do is make sure that they don\'t stop thinking and they don\'t stop searching for the ways and things that are best for them.</item>
        <item>I don\'t like the terms good person or bad person because it\'s impossible to be entirely good to everyone, or entirely bad to everyone. To some, you are a good person, while to others you are a bad person.</item>
        <item>I imagine death so much it feels more like a memory. Is this where it gets me, on my feet, several feet ahead of me\? I see it coming, do I run or fire my gun or let it be\? There is no beat, no melody. Burr, my first friend, my enemy. Maybe the last face I ever see. If I throw away my shot, is this how you\'ll remember me\?</item>
        <item>The list of people I will miss, if the dead can miss anyone, is so short I shouldn\'t even call it a list: there\'s Dad, for doing his best; my best friend, Lidia, not only for not ignoring me in the hallways, but for actually sitting down across from me in lunch, partnering with me in earth science, and talking to me about how she wants to become an environmentalist who will save the world and I can repay her by living in it. And that\'s it.</item>
        <item>The truth is, war never changes. It\'s exactly the same, no matter which era it happens upon. In the age of discovery, humanity sailed to oceans unknown, their hearts hungry for adventure. But soon, those hearts were filled with a desire to conquer the seas. Unfortunately, a new enemy appeared, one that hailed from another world.</item>
        <item>Faces slide by in glowing shadows. Like snowbound ghosts that go up and down in epileptic shivers and negative radioactive slivers, in a landscape of endless dull glitter and a taste in my mouth so sweet, yet so bitter. And we exhaust ourselves trying to get there.</item>
        <item>The blade of suspicion is keener than that of hate, for it slays friends as readily as foes. It sunders kin and rends apart those who in sane course of action would be allies as easily as those whom nature itself decrees as deadly foes. So savage a weapon it is that they who master it need fear none, save of course for themselves.</item>
        <item>Hate and love are two sides of the same coin. It\'s like a finely-tailored suit with a food sturdy stitching. In other words, the deeper the hatred, the deeper the love grows.</item>
        <item>I don\'t know which option you should choose. I could never advise you on that... No matter what kind of wisdom dictates the option you pick, no one will be able to tell if it\'s right or wrong until you arrive to some sort of outcome from your choice.</item>
        <item>Sergei the Significant and four of his five teammates were lined up at the center of the ring, doing a spot of preshow posturing to the capacity crowd. Each dwarf was less than three feet tall and wore a tight-fitting crimson leotard with a lightning-flash logo.</item>
        <item>I feel the sun on my face. I see trees all around me, the scent of wildflowers on a breeze. It\'s so beautiful. In this moment, I\'m not stranded in space. It\'s been ninety-seven years since a nuclear apocalypse killed everyone on Earth, leaving the planet simmering in radiation. Fortunately, there were survivors. Twelve nations had operational space stations at the time of the bombs. There is now only the Ark, one station forged from the many.</item>
        <item>Life is nothing how he expected it would be when he was young and living under the delusion that things could be controlled. Nothing can be controlled. Only endured.</item>
        <item>In Vinheim, I was an assassin. A sorcerer only in name, a killer for hire. What a fool I was, thinking one day I would learn real sorceries. When I became Undead, I was exiled from the school. But here I am, now, exploring the depths of sorcery. All thanks to you, I might add.</item>
        <item>No, I don\'t wanna spend any money, you guys. Let\'s just do something fun that\'s free. Stan, don\'t you know the first law of physics\? Anything that is fun costs at least 8 dollars.</item>
        <item>Sometimes people have to do things that just seem right. That seem right in their hearts, I mean. And if they do those things and then end up not feeling right, full of questions and sort of like they got indigestion, only inside their heads instead of in their guts, they think they made a mistake.</item>
        <item>This had nothing to do with you lacking in spirit or your feelings not being strong enough. Your body and your spirit aren\'t two separate things. A strong body will nurture a strong spirit. This isn\'t about overcoming your limits, it\'s about raising them.</item>
        <item>The universe is big, it\'s vast and complicated, and ridiculous. And sometimes, very rarely, impossible things just happen and we call them miracles. And that\'s the theory. Nine hundred years, never seen one yet, but this would do me.</item>
        <item>It\'s like I\'m reading a book, and it\'s a book I deeply love, but I\'m reading it slowly now so the words are really far apart and the spaces between the words are almost infinite. I can still feel you and the words of our story, but it\'s in this endless space between the words that I\'m finding myself now. It\'s a place that\'s not of the physical world - it\'s where everything else is that I didn\'t even know existed. I love you so much, but this is where I am now. This is who I am now.</item>
        <item>Long ago, the world was nothing more than an endless sea cloaked in a boundless sky, reaching as far as could possibly be imagined. Then two great titans came into existence. The Bionis and the Mechonis. The titans were locked in a timeless battle. Until at last... Only their lifeless corpses remained.</item>
        <item>You know, to love the wrong person or to be obsessed with someone can be like a drug. Having a bit of it feels good at the time, but it\'s not good for you. They say if addicts just get over the hurdle with no drugs, they won\'t want it anymore. It\'s the same as this. You gotta cut the snake off at the head. Having absolutely no contact is the best thing for you. You really need to give it time to fade.</item>
        <item>It was dim inside, with a damp coolness that slowly dispelled by the gathering congregation. At each seat was a cheap cardboard fan bearing a garish Garden of Gethsemane, courtesy of Tyndal\'s Hardware Co.</item>
        <item>Tuesday afternoon, I\'m just beginning to see. Now I\'m on my way. It doesn\'t matter to me, chasing the clouds away. Something calls to me, the trees are drawing me near. I\'ve got to find out why. Those gentle voices I hear explain it all with a sigh.</item>
        <item>The English have thousands of Welsh longbowmen, hundreds of knights on horseback, and dozens of siege weapons. We Scottish have a rabble of untrained soldiers who do not even know how to march in a straight line. We must act soon. If we have any chance of resistance, we need to forge an army by any means necessary.</item>
        <item>As I grew up, everything started getting grey and dull. I could still remember the amazing intensity of the world I\'d lived in as a child, but I thought the dulling perception was an inevitable consequence of age - just as the lens of the eye is bound to gradually dim. I didn\'t understand that clarity is in the mind.</item>
        <item>If happiness had a form, what would it look like\? It might be something like glass, because one doesn\'t notice it normally. However, it is actually there. As proof, if you look at it from a different angle, the glass will reflect light. It will state its presence and existence more eloquently than any other thing in this world.</item>
        <item>Trust me, Elend my boy. In this case, two large enemy armies are far better than a single large, enemy army. In a three-way negotiation, the weakest party actually has the most power because his allegiance added to either of the other two will choose the eventual winner.</item>
        <item>The original vampire family pledged to remain together always and forever. But even when you\'re immortal, promises are hard to keep.</item>
        <item>I am completely convinced that there is a wealth of information built into us, with miles of intuitive knowledge tucked away in the genetic material of every one of our cells. Something akin to a library containing uncountable reference volumes, but without some means of access, there is no way to even begin to guess at the extent and quality of what is there. The psychedelic drugs allow exploration of this interior world, and insights into its nature.</item>
        <item>Destiny is a gift. Some go their entire lives, living existence in quiet desperation. Never learning the truth, that what feels as though a burden pushing down upon our shoulders, is actually a sense of purpose that lifts us to greater heights. Never forget that fear is but the precursor to valor, that to strive and triumph in the face of fear, is what it means to be a hero. Don\'t think. Become!</item>
        <item>Follow her down to a bridge by a fountain, where rocking horse people eat marshmallow pies. Everyone smiles as you drift past the flowers that grow so incredibly high. Newspaper taxis appear on the shore waiting to take you away. Climb in the back with your head in the clouds and you\'re gone. Lucy in the sky with diamonds.</item>
        <item>So you need to know things, even when you don\'t need to know them. You need to know them not because you need to know them, but because you need to know whether or not you need to know. And if you don\'t need to know you still need to know so that you know that there was no need to know.</item>
        <item>No one can escape the fate that was chosen for them. All that remains is the end, where you will all perish. Eternal greatness exists only within myself. Sing a song of sorrow in a world where time has vanished.</item>
        <item>Such dreary streets! Blocks of blackness, not houses, on either hand, and here and there a candle, like a candle moving about in a tomb. And this hour of the night, of the last day of the week, that quarter of the town proved all but deserted.</item>
        <item>The city was asleep. New York, the nervous, keyed-up city, was almost at rest two hours past midnight. Watching the sleeping stone under the quiet sky, the mind might know that there were still people laughing in night clubs, trucks and taxis still speeding through streets and avenues, swift subways underground still thundering into lighted stations.</item>
        <item>You may think your only choices are to swallow your anger or throw it in someone\'s face, but there\'s a third option: You can just let it go, and only when you do that is it really gone and you can move forward.</item>
        <item>We must pass through solitude and difficulty, isolation and silence to find that enchanted place where we can dance our clumsy dance and sing our sorrowful song. But in that dance, and in that song, the most ancient rites of our conscience fulfill themselves in the awareness of being human.</item>
        <item>Aspire to be like Mount Fuji, with such a broad and solid foundation that the strongest earthquake cannot move you, and so tall that the greatest enterprises of common men seem insignificant from your lofty perspective. With your mind as high as Mount Fuji you can see all things clearly. And you can see all the forces that shape events; not just the things happening near to you.</item>
        <item>I got into show business because I love stories. They comfort us, they inspire us, they make a context for how we experience the world. But also, you have to be careful, because if you spend a lot of time with stories, you start to believe that life is just stories, and it\'s not. Life is life, and that\'s so sad because there\'s so little time and... What are we doing with it\?</item>
        <item>All men dream: but not equally. Those who dream by night in the dusty recesses of their minds wake in the day to find that it was vanity. But the dreamers of the day are dangerous men, for they may act their dream with open eyes to make it possible. This I did.</item>
        <item>When religion and politics travel in the same cart, the riders believe nothing can stand in their way. Their movements become headlong - faster and faster and faster. They put aside all thoughts of obstacles and forget the precipice does not show itself to the man in a blind rush until it\'s too late.</item>
        <item>In such environments, natural selection favors individual algae that can survive periods when they are not submerged in water. In charophytes, a layer of a durable polymer called sporopollenin prevents exposed zygotes from drying out.</item>
        <item>The end of the world started when a Pegasus landed on the hood of my car. Up until then, I was having a great afternoon.</item>
        <item>It\'s important to take the time out of our busy schedules to do something entirely unrelated to our immediate needs.</item>
        <item>Kanbaru, if they find out what you did here, a lot of people will say a lot of things to you. Some will say you did the right thing. And some will say you did the wrong thing. But that\'s not what matters. No matter what anyone says, you don\'t have to worry. Because you didn\'t do the right thing, and you didn\'t do the wrong thing. It was all part of being young.</item>
        <item>Reach out your hand if your cup be empty. If your cup is full, may it be again. Let it be known there is a fountain that was not made by the hands of men.</item>
        <item>The kid in the back looked like he was ready to jump right out of the car and take his chances. Our vibrations were getting nasty - but why\? I was puzzled, frustrated. Was there no communication in this car\? Had we deteriorated to the level of dumb beasts\?</item>
        <item>A good person\? Well... I don\'t really like that term. Because to me, it just seems to mean someone who\'s good for you. And I don\'t think there\'s any one person who\'s good for everyone.</item>
        <item>She was amazed Silveny had even let them get close enough to attach the reins. Clearly she needed to teach the glittering horse how to recognize pure evil.</item>
        <item>Wake up princess, I\'m tired of your useless ideals. It\'s gotten pathetic. What good are your happy ideals if you can\'t do anything to make them a reality\? They\'re nothing but dreams, and your dreams don\'t stand a chance.</item>
        <item>For me, good design means that when I make a change, it\'s as if the entire program was crafted in anticipation of it. I can solve a task with just a few choice function calls that slot in perfectly, leaving not the slightest ripple on the placid surface of the code.</item>
        <item>People have to talk about something just to keep their voice boxes in working order, so they\'ll have good voice boxes in case there\'s ever anything really meaningful to say.</item>
        <item>Have you ever come to hate the very thing that you helped to create\?</item>
        <item>It\'s a wonder to be alive. If you don\'t understand that, how can you search for anything deeper\?</item>
        <item>It\'s one thing to question your mind. It\'s another to question your eyes and ears. But then again, isn\'t it all the same\? Are our senses just mediocre inputs for our brain\? Sure, we rely on them, we trust them to accurately portray the real world around us, but what if the haunting truth is they can\'t\? That what we perceive isn\'t the real world at all, but just our mind\'s best guess\? That all we really have is a garbled reality, a fuzzy picture we will never truly make out\?</item>
        <item>Any sufficiently advanced technique is, to the layperson, indistinguishable from magic.</item>
        <item>Whenever you find yourself getting angry about a difference of opinion, be on your guard; you will probably find, on examination, that your belief is going beyond what the evidence warrants.</item>
        <item>Alright, we got the wine. Aren\'t we lucky\? We got wine. Whoopywoo! Imagine if we didn\'t bring the wine, we\'d be shunned by society. Outcasts! Where\'s your wine\? Get out!</item>
        <item>When you dance the dance of another, you make yourself in the image of its creator. You empty yourself so that her work can live within you.</item>
        <item>I wasn\'t hurt that badly. The doctor said all my bleeding was internal. That\'s where the blood\'s supposed to be.</item>
        <item>I went out into the night and the neon and let the crowd pull me along, walking blind, willing myself to be just a segment of that mass organism, just one more drifting chip of consciousness under the geodesics.</item>
        <item>Close your eyes and surrender to your darkest dreams, purge your thoughts of the life you knew before. Close your eyes, let your spirit start to soar, and you\'ll live as you\'ve never lived before.</item>
        <item>Giving expression to thought by the observable medium of words is like the work of the silkworm. In being made into silk, the material achieves its value. But in the light of day it stiffens; it becomes something alien, no longer malleable. True, we can then more easily and freely recall the same thought, but perhaps we can never experience it again in its original freshness.</item>
        <item>Long ago, when man was young and the dragon already old, the wisest of our race took pity on man. He gathered together all the dragons, making them vow to watch over man, always. And at the moment of his death, the night became alive with those stars. And thus was born the Dragons\' Heaven. But when we die, not all dragons are admitted to this shining place. No, we have to earn it. And if we don\'t, our spirit disappears as if we never were. And that\'s why I shared my life force with a dying boy - so I would reunite man and dragon, and ensure my place among my ancient brothers of the sky... but my sacrifice became my sin.</item>
        <item>More than half of our neighbors believe that the entire cosmos was created six thousand years ago. This is, incidentally, about a thousand years after the Sumerians invented glue.</item>
        <item>I know it may be impossible to believe now, when everything is dark and broken, but you will survive this pain, little one. Pain is a memory. You will live and you will struggle and you will find joy. And you will remember your family from this breath to your dying days, because love does not fade. Love is the stars, and its light carries on long after death.</item>
        <item>There are no more barriers to cross. All I have in common with the uncontrollable and the insane, the vicious and the evil, all the mayhem I have caused and my utter indifference toward it I have now surpassed. My pain is constant and sharp, and I do not hope for a better world for anyone. In fact, I want my pain to be inflicted on others. I want no one to escape. But even after admitting this, there is no catharsis; my punishment continues to elude me, and I gain no deeper knowledge of myself. No new knowledge can be extracted from my telling. This confession has meant nothing.</item>
        <item>It\'s a beautiful day outside. Birds are singing, flowers are blooming. On days like these, kids like you... should be burning in hell.</item>
        <item>For the majority of people, what they love exists only in the imagination. The object of their love is not the man or woman of reality, but what he or she is like in their imagination. The person in reality is just a template used for the creation of this dream lover. Eventually, they fin out the differences between their dream lover and the template. If they can get used to those differences, then they can be together. If not, they split up. It\'s as simple as that.</item>
        <item>What sets science and the law apart from religion is that nothing is expected to be taken on faith. We\'re encouraged to ask whether the evidence actually supports what we\'re being told - or what we grew up believing - and we\'re allowed to ask whether we\'re hearing all the evidence or just some small prejudicial part of it. If our beliefs aren\'t supported by the evidence, then we\'re encouraged to alter our beliefs.</item>
        <item>Everyone I have cared for has either died or left me, everyone except for you. So don\'t tell me I\'d be safer with someone else because the truth is I\'d just be more scared.</item>
        <item>From the moment that we met, I\'ve been awake, like I\'ve never been awake in all my life. If I spoke your language I could tell you how I feel, but your language isn\'t real.</item>
        <item>I\'ve seen horrors. Horrors that you\'ve seen. But you have no right to call me a murderer. You have a right to kill me. You have a right to do that... but you have no right to judge me. It\'s impossible for words to describe what is necessary to those who do not know what horror means. Horror... horror has a face, and you must make a friend of horror. Horror and moral terror are your friends. If they are not, then they are enemies to be feared. They are truly enemies.</item>
        <item>Know this son: the hard truth of life is that everyone leaves and everything dies. There is no exception to the passing of time.</item>
        <item>Calculus is a tool that helps us understand how a change in one quantity is related to a change in another. How does the speed of a falling object change as a function of time\? How does the level of water in a barrel change as a function of the amount of liquid poured into it\? We see change occurring in nearly everything we observe in the world and universe, and powerful modern instruments help us see more and more. In this section we introduce the ideas of average and instantaneous rates of change, and show that they are closely related to the slope of a curve at a point P on the curve. We give precise developments of these important concepts in the next chapter, but for now we use an informal approach so you will see how they lead naturally to the main idea of this chapter, the limit. The idea of a limit plays a foundational role throughout calculus.</item>
        <item>One way to tell if you\'re really comfortable with a person is if you can be quiet together sometimes and not feel awkward. If you don\'t feel obligated to say something brilliant or funny or surprising or cool. You can just be together. You can just be.</item>
        <item>The full beauty of the subject of generating functions emerges only from tuning in on both channels: the discrete and the continuous. See how they make the solution of difference equations into child\'s play. Then see how the theory of functions of a complex variable gives, virtually by inspection, the approximate size of the solution. The interplay between the two channels is vitally important for the appreciation of the music.</item>
        <item>Oh, Scarecrow, maybe the wind knows whether you wonder who\'s calling your name. Maybe the wind knows whether you wonder if you are to blame. Saving the grain of your golden domain without even reasoning why, the crows seem to know where you need them to go, igniting a spark in their minds so they circle and fly.</item>
        <item>I struggled so hard for a goal, without realizing that the goal is the struggle. It\'s what makes me stronger, smarter, and better. Growth doesn\'t come from a comfort zone, but from leaving it.</item>
        <item>And in the end I think I\'ve learned the final lesson from my travels in time; and I\'ve even gone one step further than my father did. The truth is I now don\'t travel back at all, not even for the day. I just try to live every day as if I\'ve deliberately come back to this one day, to enjoy it, as if it was the full final day of my extraordinary, ordinary life.</item>
        <item>Oh, I got it. You\'re trying to teach me how to be cool. You\'re trying to show me that it doesn\'t matter where you go, because if you\'re truly cool, wherever you go is the cool place to be, right\?</item>
        <item>Ladies and gentlemen, either you are closing your eyes to a situation you do not wish to acknowledge, or you are not aware of the caliber of disaster indicated by the presence of a pool table in your community!</item>
        <item>I\'m here, just like I said. Though it\'s breaking every rule I ever made. My racin\' heart is just the same. Why make it strong to break it once again\? And I\'d love to say I do, give everything to you. But I can never not be true. So I say, I think I\'d better leave right now, before I fall any deeper.</item>
        <item>I\'ve been thinking. When life gives you lemons, don\'t make lemonade. Make life take the lemons back! Get mad! I don\'t want your damn lemons! What am I supposed to do with these\? Demand to see life\'s manager! Make life rue the day it thought it could give me lemons! Do you know who I am\? I\'m the man who\'s going to burn your house down! With the lemons! I\'m going to get my engineers to invent a combustible lemon that burns your house down!</item>
        <item>We are all born dead. The end exists before anything begins. If living is a constant quest for awareness, the awareness we gain at the end is the real goal. In other words, death is the discovery and complete understanding of the end. We are not permitted to seek awareness. Those that cannot transcend death will not find awareness in anything.</item>
        <item>I think we could do it if we tried, if only to say, you\'re mine. Sofia, know that you and I, shouldn\'t feel like a crime. Honey, I don\'t want it to fade. There\'s things that I know could get in the way. I don\'t want to say goodbye, and I think that we could do it if we tried.</item>
        <item>Betty Botter bought a bit of butter; \"But,\" she said, \"this butter\'s bitter! If I put it in my batter it will make my batter bitter. But a bit of better butter will make my batter better.\" Then she bought a bit of butter better than the bitter butter, made her bitter batter better. So \'twas better Betty Botter bought a bit o\' better butter.</item>
        <item>To stand up straight with your shoulders back is to accept the terrible responsibility of life with eyes wide open. It means deciding to voluntarily transform the chaos of potential into the realities of habitable order. It means adopting the burden of self-conscious vulnerability, and accepting the end of the unconscious paradise of childhood, where finitude and mortality are only dimly comprehended. It means willingly undertaking the sacrifices necessary to generate a productive and meaningful reality.</item>
        <item>Nothing makes itself unpopular quite so quickly as a person\'s grief. When it is fresh it attracts people to its side, finds someone to offer it consolation; but if it is perpetuated it becomes an object of ridicule - deservedly, too, for it is either feigned or foolish.</item>
        <item>If you were here for the other night, you\'d be terrified. You know I think the lions you\'re afraid of are all made up. Nobody\'s gonna regret this for you if it don\'t make you smile. I\'ll let your skeleton shake all evenin\' and bless your heart for tryin\'.</item>
        <item>The doctor said I had tomato loss... all right. Dr. Amnesia was her name, she had beautiful eyes. We had spaghetti with long term memory sauce... all right. And every word she said, it was a little surprise.</item>
        <item>Ever since you were born you were cold as the snow. You were so scared to melt. You avoided the warmth that your family had gave in the same flowing breath that they said, \"I love you to death.\"</item>
        <item>It often seems to me that\'s all detective work is, wiping out your false starts and beginning again. And it is just what some people will not do. They conceive a certain theory, and everything has to fit into that theory. If one little fact will not fit it, they throw it aside. But it is always the facts that will not fit in that are significant.</item>
        <item>Life is basically like a soap bubble. It rides on the wind, flying here and there... and before you realize it - pop! It\'s gone. When it\'s about to disappear, you think that you could\'ve flown a little higher. But by the time, it\'s already too late.</item>
        <item>Of course, an introduction. A beginning. I could introduce myself properly, but it\'s not really necessary. You will know me well enough and soon enough, depending on a diverse range of variables. It suffices to say that at some point in time, I will be standing over you, as genially as possible. Your soul will be in my arms. A color will be perched on my shoulder.</item>
        <item>The dark is generous, and it is patient, and it always wins. It always wins because it is everywhere. It is in the wood that burns in your hearth, and in the kettle on the fire; it is under your chair and under your table and under the sheets on your bed. Walk in the midday sun, and the dark is with you, attached to the soles of your feet. The brightest light casts the darkest shadow.</item>
        <item>People who are really busy never have enough time to become skittish. And there is nothing so certain as the fact that the harmful consequences of inactivity are dissipated by activity.</item>
        <item>In one remote corner of the vast sea of information on the Internet, there was a remote corner, and in a remote corner of that remote corner, and then in a remote corner of a remote corner of a remote corner of that remote corner - that is, in the very depth of the most remote corner of all - a virtual world came back to life.</item>
        <item>What a curious life we have found here tonight, there is music that sounds from the street. There are lights in the clouds, Anna\'s ghost all around. Hear her voice as it\'s rolling and ringing through me, soft and sweet. How the notes all bend and reach above the trees.</item>
        <item>Amy, there was a song I couldn\'t get out of my head. Eventually, I realized the song was about you, and like that earworm, I can\'t get you out of my heart. So, what I\'m trying to say is, you\'re my heartworm. The metaphorical kind, not, not the poodle-killing kind.</item>
        <item>There is thought, and then there is thinking about thoughts, and they don\'t feel the same. They must reflect quite different aspects of brain function. The point is, the brain talks to itself, and by talking to itself changes its perceptions.</item>
        <item>I have all the characteristics of a human being: blood, flesh, skin, hair; but not a single, clear, identifiable emotion, except for greed and disgust. Something horrible is happening inside of me and I don\'t know why. My nightly bloodlust has overflown into my days. I feel lethal, on the verge of frenzy. I think my mask of sanity is about to slip.</item>
        <item>When you find that once again you long to take your heart back and be free, if you ever find a moment, spare a thought for me.</item>
        <item>It\'s moments like these where I feel like I am tied to the tracks and the train is barreling towards me. I can feel its rumble, and I can see its lights, but somehow I\'m not scared to die. I don\'t pray for it to stop, I don\'t pray for escape. All I can do is close my eyes and wait. And just moments before it decides to take my heart and take my blood, I tell myself, it\'s only love.</item>
        <item>The problem is we don\'t notice the years pass, he thought. Screw the years - we don\'t notice things change. We know that things change, we\'ve been told since childhood that things change, we\'ve witnessed things change ourselves many a time, and yet we\'re still utterly incapable of noticing the moment that change comes-or we search for change in all the wrong places.</item>
        <item>Quitting a job doesn\'t have to mean giving up. A job is just a tactic, a way to get what you really want. As soon as your job hits a dead end, it makes sense to quit and take your quest to a bigger marketplace - because every day you wait puts your goal further away.</item>
        <item>Man, in his incredible ignorance, displays astonishing ingenuity in messing up the great ecological system of which he is inescapably a part of.</item>
        <item>Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious is Vielle\'s favorite word to type on TypeRacer.</item>
        <item>I thought that we were falling in love but we weren\'t; only I was.</item>
        <item>\"The future is in our hands...\" Yeah. That may be true. But that doesn\'t mean it\'s bright for everyone.</item>
        <item>The greatest sources of our suffering are the lies we tell ourselves.</item>
        <item>Someday, I will repay you. Unless of course, I can\'t find you... or if I forget.</item>
        <item>Do I need to be liked\? Absolutely not. I like to be liked. I enjoy being liked. I have to be liked, but it\'s not like this compulsive need to be liked, like my need to be praised.</item>
        <item>Dead code is code that isn\'t executed. You find it in the body of an if statement that checks for a condition that can\'t happen. You find it in the catch block of a try that never throws. You find it in little utility methods that are never called or switch/case conditions that never occur. The problem with dead code is that after awhile it starts to smell. The older it is, the stronger and sourer the odor becomes. This is because dead code is not completely updated when designs change. It still compiles, but it does not follow newer conventions or rules. It was written at a time when the system was different. When you find dead code, do the right thing. Give it a decent burial. Delete it from the system.</item>
        <item>When I think of love I see your face, but when I think of you I think of pain. My heart and mind are not on the same page.</item>
        <item>Last night I wanted to take a sleeping pill, and then, I thought if I took more, I would sleep better. And if I took the lot, I would sleep without dreaming, without waking up. I wanted death. Yes, oh yes, like a sledgehammer. But I did dream. I dreamt the truth. And then I woke up suddenly and I was so pleased it was only a nightmare, and then when I realized it wasn\'t a nightmare, it was the truth, I was alone, and your arm was not around me, and my head was not on your shoulder. I felt I couldn\'t live. I simply couldn\'t live.</item>
        <item>People are made of stories. Our memories are not the impartial accumulation of every second we\'ve lived; they\'re the narrative that we assembled out of selected moments.</item>
        <item>Everyone in this town fears God, but you know who God fears\? The Teachers Union.</item>
        <item>As a job candidate, you must make your application stand out. Review the resumes of the people who currently work in your desired role to determine the language you should use. Every bullet point should follow the format \"accomplished x by doing y as measured by z\" - details that will differentiate your application. You can anticipate 90% of interview questions, so rehearse your responses in advance. Interviewers will make a snap judgment about you and spend the entire conversation trying to confirm that unconscious bias. Dispel such judgments by trying to make a personal connection that is unrelated to the context of the job and by being prepared to deviate from traditional interview topics.</item>
        <item>Who has never killed an hour\? Not casually or without thought, but carefully: a premeditated murder of minutes. The violence comes from a combination of giving up, not caring, and a resignation that getting past it is all you can hope to accomplish. So you kill the hour. You do not work, you do not read, you do not daydream. If you sleep it is not because you need to sleep. And when at last it is over, there is no evidence: no weapon, no blood, and no body. The only clue might be the shadows beneath your eyes or a terribly thin line near the corner of your mouth indicating something has been suffered, that in the privacy of your life you have lost something and the loss is too empty to share.</item>
        <item>I don\'t know how I can be so ambitious and so lazy at the same time.</item>
        <item>Could you manage all the details yourself\? Probably not. Even managing an existing city is too much for one person. Yet, cities work (most of the time). They work because cities have teams of people who manage particular parts of the city, the water systems, power systems, traffic, law enforcement, building codes, and so forth. Some of those people are responsible for the big picture, while others focus on the details.</item>
        <item>None know if our temple, the Cradle, will prove powerful enough to contain this evil forever. How can we Chozo hope for it to remain intact when that which it guards writhes in the darkness, growing always stronger\? The fate of this world rests with the gathering of Artifacts we call the Cipher, but even it is not all-powerful. It is strong, yes; an enchanted whole made of twelve links. Still, it is finite in its reach, and we who guard it are slowly succumbing. When our vigilance crumbles away into madness, the Cipher will be exposed and the fate of Tallon IV will be beyond our influence.</item>
        <item>You know, the very powerful and the very stupid have one thing in common: they don\'t alter their views to fit the facts; they alter the facts to fit their views.</item>
        <item>Every once in a while, a book comes along that fundamentally changes the way we look at the world.</item>
        <item>Contemplate the marvel that is existence, and rejoice that you are able to do so.</item>
        <item>Okay, you got me. I sometimes hide behind other people\'s words. For one thing, I know nothing about love. I keep my head down, I\'m a simple guy. Which is to say, if I knew what love was, I would quote myself.</item>
        <item>Love is simply the name for the desire and pursuit of the whole.</item>
        <item>What\'s this\? - A letter. - Who writes letters these days\? - I thought it\'d seem romantic. - Can\'t help you. - I just need a few words... good ones. - I\'m not writing a letter to some girl. It\'d be wrong. A letter is personal, it\'s supposed to be authentic. - That\'d be awesome! - No! I can\'t be you being authentic! Get a thesaurus, use spellcheck, good luck Romeo. - No! I can pay more for authentic!</item>
        <item>Just thinking about her made him warm inside. No longer did he wish to be a fish or a sunflower - or anything else, for that matter. For sure, it was a great inconvenience to have to walk on two legs and wear clothes and eat with a knife and fork. There were so many things that he didn\'t know. Yet had he been a fish or a sunflower, and not a human being, he might never have experienced this emotion. So he felt.</item>
        <item>Rudeness is merely the expression of fear. People fear they won\'t get what they want. The most dreadful and unattractive person only needs to be loved and they will open up like a flower.</item>
        <item>Pick one word for one abstract concept and stick with it. For instance, it\'s confusing to have fetch, retrieve, and get as equivalent methods of different classes. How do you remember which method name goes with which class\? Sadly, you often have to remember which company, group, or individual wrote the library or class in order to remember which term was used. Otherwise, you spend an awful lot of time browsing through headers and previous code samples.</item>
        <item>Mr. Madison, what you\'ve just said is one of the most insanely idiotic things I have ever heard. At no point in your rambling, incoherent response were you even close to anything that could be considered a rational thought. Everyone in this room is now dumber for having listened to it. I award you no points, and may God have mercy on your soul.</item>
        <item>Do you love making cupcakes, but hate all the hard cupcake work\? I know I do. Well, forget everything you know about making cupcakes, and say hello, to the amazing Kupkake-inator. I\'m so excited! Kupkake-a-what\? Kupkake-inator! This amazing device can instantly make cupcakes out of anything you have in the kitchen! Wait a minute, did you say anything\? Anything! Anything\? Yes, anything! Anything\? Anything! Anything\?</item>
        <item>Mary, did you know that your baby boy would one day walk on water\? Mary, did you know that your baby boy would save our sons and daughters\? Did you know that your baby boy has come to make you new\? This child that you\'ve delivered, will soon deliver you. Mary, did you know that your baby boy will give sight to a blind man\? Mary, did you know that your baby boy will calm a storm with his hand\? Did you know that your baby boy has walked where angels trod\? When you kiss your little baby, you kiss the face of God. Mary, did you know\? Mary, did you know\? The blind will see, the deaf will hear, and the dead will live again. The dead will live, the deaf will speak, praises of the lamb. Mary, did you know that your baby boy will one day rule the nations\? Did you know that your baby boy is Heaven\'s perfect lamb\? This child that you\'re holding is the Great \'I Am\'. Mary, did you know\?</item>
        <item>To have meaning in your life is better than to have what you want, because you may neither know what you want, nor what you truly need.</item>
        <item>Out, out, brief candle! Life\'s but a walking shadow, a poor player that struts and frets his hour upon the stage, and then is heard no more. It is a tale told by an idiot, full of sound and fury, signifying nothing.</item>
        <item>So, the truth is, someone who wants you to do horrible things, and convinces you that they\'re good, that\'s a villain. My dad is a villain. And he\'s only gonna get more powerful, and the more powerful he gets, the more people will listen to him, and believe him, and follow him. So, maybe we could run, and we\'d be safe for a while, but he\'s not gonna give up. It may seem hopeless, but our only chance is to fight him here. While we\'re all together. The only way to stop this is to look evil in the face and say, \"No more.\"</item>
        <item>I wanted to know what had pushed them over the brink, and why some had broken down as a result of that experience while others had been able to go on with their lives. Most of the men I interviewed had gone to war feeling well prepared, drawn close by the rigors of basic training and the shared danger. They exchanged pictures of their families and girlfriends; they put up with one another\'s flaws. And they were prepared to risk their lives for their friends. Most of them confided their dark secrets to a buddy, and some went so far as to share each other\'s shirts and socks.</item>
        <item>For it is said that humans are never satisfied, that you give them one thing and they want something more. And this is said in disparagement, whereas it is one of the greatest talents the species has and one that has made it superior to animals that are satisfied with what they have.</item>
        <item>Google pays its star performers as much as 10 times more than its average performers, because the company believes one good employee is worth several average employees.</item>
        <item>I like living. I have sometimes been wildly, despairingly, acutely miserable, racked with sorrow; but through it all I still know quite certainly that just to be alive is a grand thing.</item>
        <item>Don\'t underestimate the power of vision and direction. These are irresistible forces, able to transform what might appear to be unconquerable obstacles into traversable pathways and expanding opportunities. Strengthen the individual. Start with yourself. Take care with yourself. Define who you are. Refine your personality. Choose your destination and articulate your Being. As the great nineteenth-century German philosopher Friedrich Nietzsche so brilliantly noted, \"He whose life has a why can bear almost any how.\"</item>
        <item>There were dragons when I was a boy. There were great, grim, sky dragons that nested on the cliff tops like gigantic scary birds. Little, brown, scuttly dragons that hunted down the mice and rats in well-organized packs. Preposterously huge Sea Dragons that were twenty times as big as the Big Blue Whale and who killed for the fun of it. You will have to take my word for it, for the dragons are disappearing so fast they may soon become extinct.</item>
        <item>Chernobyl melted down because the plant manager overrode each of the safety mechanisms one by one. The safeties were making it inconvenient to run an experiment. The result was that the experiment did not get run, and the world saw its first major civilian nuclear catastrophe.</item>
        <item>As human beings we belong to an extremely resilient species. Since time immemorial we have rebounded from our relentless wars, countless disasters (both natural and man-made), and the violence and betrayal in our own lives. But Traumatic experiences do leave traces, whether on a large scale (on our histories and cultures) or close to home, on our families, with dark secrets being imperceptibly passed down through generations.</item>
        <item>Avoid using the same word for two purposes. Using the same term for two different ideas is essentially a pun.</item>
        <item>Give people what they need: food, medicine, clean air, pure water, trees and grass, pleasant homes to live in, some hours of work, more hours of leisure. Don\'t ask who deserves it. Every human being deserves it.</item>
        <item>I have been second to Jo my whole life, in everything. And I will not be the person you settle for just because you cannot have her. I won\'t do it. I won\'t, not when I\'ve spent my entire life loving you.</item>
        <item>If you remember everything, I wanted to say, and if you are really like me, then before you leave tomorrow, or when you\'re just ready to shut the door of the taxi and have already said goodbye to everyone else and there\'s not a thing left to say in this life, then, just this once, turn to me, even in jest, or as an afterthought, which would have meant everything to me when we were together, and, as you did back then, look me in the face, hold my gaze, and call me by your name.</item>
        <item>Charles IV, King of Bohemia and Holy Roman Emperor, had a long and successful reign. The Empire he ruled from Prague expanded, and his subjects lived in peace and prosperity. When he died, the whole Empire mourned. More than 7,000 people accompanied him on his last procession. The heir to the throne of the flourishing Empire was Charles\' son, Wenceslas IV, whose father had prepared him for this moment all his life. But Wenceslas did not take after his father. He neglected affairs of state for more frivolous pursuits.</item>
        <item>When it comes to the dark arts, I believe in a practical approach. First, which of you can tell me how many unforgivable curses there are\? - Three, Sir. - And they are so named\? - Because they are unforgivable. The use of any one of them wi... - Will earn you a one-way ticket to Azkaban, correct. Now, the ministry says you\'re too young to see what these curses do, I say different! You need to know what you\'re up against, you need to be prepared. You need to find another place to put your chewing gum besides the underside of your desk, Mr. Finigan.</item>
        <item>Sometimes when people love each other very much, they need time apart, so when they come back together, their love is even stronger.</item>
        <item>Without imagination there is no hope, no chance to envision a better future, no place to go, no goal to reach.</item>
        <item>People assume that time is a strict progression from cause to effect. But actually, from a non-linear, non-subjective viewpoint, it\'s more like a big ball of wibbly-wobbly, timey-wimey stuff.</item>
        <item>I\'m trying to explain that I\'m a person who wishes to live a very quiet life. I take care not to trouble myself with any enemies, like winning and losing, that would cause me to lose sleep at night. That is how I deal with society, and I know that is what brings me happiness. Although, if I were to fight I wouldn\'t lose to anyone.</item>
        <item>His poems were better than mine, and they delighted me; but he needed the sanction of some, so that they could confirm the applause of others. His shyness, however, always stopped him from questioning anyone. He still enjoyed hearing words of appreciation.</item>
        <item>While you are failing to define success (and thereby rendering it impossible) you are also refusing to define failure, to yourself, so that if and when you fail you won\'t notice, and it won\'t hurt. But that won\'t work! You cannot be fooled so easily - unless you have gone very far down the road! You will instead carry with you a continual sense of disappointment in your own Being and the self-contempt that comes along with that and the increasing hatred for the world that all of that generates (or degenerates).</item>
        <item>Some might say that sunshine follows thunder, go and tell it to the man who cannot shine. Some might say that we should never ponder on our thoughts today, \'cause they hold sway over time. Some might say we will find a brighter day.</item>
        <item>Informally, an algorithm is any well-defined computational procedure that takes some value, or set of values, as input, and produces some value, or set of values, as output. An algorithm is thus a sequence of computational steps that transform the input into the output.</item>
        <item>At the end of his tour of duty Tom was honorably discharged, and all he wanted was to put Vietnam behind him. Outwardly that\'s exactly what he did. He attended college on the GI Bill, graduated from law school, married his high school sweetheart, and had two sons. Tom was upset by how difficult it was to feel any real affection for his wife, even though her letters had kept him alive in the madness of the jungle. Tom went through the motions of living a normal life, hoping that by faking it he would learn to become his old self again. He now had a thriving law practice and a picture-perfect family, but he sensed he wasn\'t normal; he felt dead inside.</item>
        <item>The ancient Greeks believed humans once had four arms, four legs, and a single head made of two faces. We were happy. Complete. So complete that the gods, fearing our wholeness would quell our need for worship, cleaved us in two, leaving our split selves to wander this Earth in misery. Forever longing. Longing. Longing for the other half of our soul. It is said that when one half finds its other... there\'s an unspoken understanding. A unity. And each would know no greater joy than this. Of course... the ancient Greeks never went to high school.</item>
        <item>For the last ten years now I have kept a journal, using a counterintuitive yet effective method. It is simply this: I write less than I feel like writing. Typically, when people start to keep a journal they write pages the first day. Then by the second day the prospect of writing so much is daunting, and they procrastinate or abandon the exercise. So apply the principle of \"less but better\" to your journal. Restrain yourself from writing more until daily journaling has become a habit.</item>
        <item>There is neither happiness nor misery in the world; there is only the comparison of one state with another, nothing more. He who has felt the deepest grief is best able to experience supreme happiness. We must have felt what it is to die, Morrel, that we may appreciate the enjoyments of life.</item>
        <item>There is something in our soul that loathes true attention much more violently than flesh loathes fatigue. That something is much closer to evil than flesh is. That is why, every time we truly give our attention, we destroy some evil in ourselves.</item>
        <item>But in a solitary life, there are rare moments when another soul dips near yours, as stars once a year brush the earth. Such a constellation was he to me.</item>
        <item>I eagerly asked Tom how the medicines had worked. He told me he hadn\'t taken any of the pills. Trying to conceal my irritation, I asked him why. \"I realized that if I take the pills and the nightmares go away,\" he replied, \"I will have abandoned my friends, and their deaths will have been in vain. I need to be a living memorial to my friends who died in Vietnam.\" I was stunned: Tom\'s loyalty to the dead was keeping him from living his own life, just as his father\'s devotion to his friends had kept him from living.</item>
        <item>Even a child that receives one bit of praise has the ability to excel in a single talent, and those who receive regular encouragement can feel confidence, achieve success, and become leading members of society. Because they don\'t believe they are worthless, they don\'t need to raise a fist and have vengeance against fate or the world at large.</item>
        <item>Do you think there is the possibility of you and I\? In this lifetime, is that too much to hope for\? There is something so delicate about this time, so fragile. And if nothing ever comes of it, at least I have known this feeling, this wonderful sense of optimism. It is something I can always keep close to me - to draw from in my darkest hour like a ray of unspent sunshine. No matter what happens next, I will always be glad to know there is someone like you in the world.</item>
        <item>Unlike marbles, people don\'t just roll with it when you try to push them. They push back. Rather than saying yes, the client stops returning our calls. Rather than going along, the boss says they\'ll think about it, which is a nice way of saying \"Thanks, but no way.\"</item>
        <item>I enjoy having breakfast in bed, I like waking up to the smell of bacon, sue me. And since I don\'t have a butler, I have to do it myself. So, most nights before I go to bed, I will lay six strips of bacon out on my George Foreman Grill, then I go to sleep. When I wake up I plug in the grill, I go back to sleep again. Then I wake up to the smell of crackling bacon. It is delicious, it\'s good for me, it\'s the perfect way to start the day. Today I got up, I stepped onto the grill and it clamped down on my foot... that\'s it. I don\'t see what\'s so hard to believe about that.</item>
        <item>In many ways, the work of a critic is easy. We risk very little yet enjoy a position over those who offer up their work and their selves to our judgment. We thrive on negative criticism, which is fun to write and to read. But the bitter truth we critics must face, is that in the grand scheme of things, the average piece of junk is probably more meaningful than our criticism designating it so. But there are times when a critic truly risks something, and that is in the discovery and defense of the new. The world is often unkind to new talent, new creations, the new needs friends.</item>
        <item>To be hopeful in bad times is not just foolishly romantic. It is based on the fact that human history is a history not only of cruelty, but also of compassion, sacrifice, courage, kindness. What we choose to emphasize in this complex history will determine our lives. If we see only the worst, it destroys our capacity to do something. If we remember those times and places - and there are so many - where people have behaved magnificently, this gives us the energy to act, and at least the possibility of sending this spinning top of a world in a different direction. And if we do act, in however small a way, we don\'t have to wait for some grand utopian future. The future is an infinite succession of presents, and to live now as we think human beings should live, in defiance of all that is bad around us, is itself a marvelous victory.</item>
        <item>Imagination gives us the opportunity to envision new possibilities - it is an essential launchpad for making our hopes come true. It fires our creativity, relieves our boredom, alleviates our pain, enhances our pleasure, and enriches our most intimate relationships.</item>
        <item>I don\'t know who I am, I don\'t trust who you are. Lately all I can do is pray to the stars that this bleak observation of everything I see might one day turn around. I need to get some help.</item>
        <item>I remember every wand I\'ve ever sold, Mr. Potter. It so happens that the phoenix whose tail feather resides in your wand gave another feather, just one other. It is curious that you should be destined for this wand when its brother gave you that scar. - And who owned that wand\? - We do not speak his name. The wand chooses the wizard, Mr. Potter, it\'s not always clear why. But, I think it is clear that we can expect great things from you. After all, He Who Must Not Be Named did great things. Terrible things, but great.</item>
        <item>We\'ll be here when the world slows down and the sunbeams fade away. Keeping time by a pendulum as the fabric starts to fray. There\'s no such thing as time to kill nor time to throw away. So, once for the bright sky, twice for the pig sty, thrice for another day.</item>
        <item>Life is a waterfall, we\'re one in the river and one again after the fall. Swimming through the void, we hear the word. We lose ourselves, but we find it all.</item>
        <item>When our god fails to respond in the ways we expect, we humans tend to respond in one of two ways. We either blindly intensify our acts of worship or lash out in righteous anger.</item>
        <item>Traumatized people so often keep repeating the same problems and have such trouble learning from experience. We now know that their behaviors are not the result of moral failings or signs of lack of willpower or bad character - they are caused by actual changes in the brain.</item>
        <item>Getting information off the internet is like taking a drink from a fire hydrant.</item>
        <item>They call it the cockroach effect because as with cockroaches, if you see one, you can bet there are others. The same thinking applies to companies reporting earning surprises. If a company has posted very good quarterly results that are much better than were anticipated by analysts, there are probably more good quarters ahead.</item>
        <item>I don\'t like thinking about luck. I like to think of myself as a science guy. But, there\'s one thing with regard to luck that makes me nervous. I see many more pennies lying face down than I do face up... beyond what you can expect from statistical variation. There\'s just something weird that I can\'t explain.</item>
        <item>Congratulations! By opening this volume you have taken the first step on a truly epic journey, a voyage through the vast landscape of Breton food and its myriad joys and wonders. You will explore scents, flavors, and textures so exquisite, they will seem impossible. But they are more than possible! Indeed, by following the carefully selected recipes presented in this cookbook, you will prepare extraordinary dishes with such ordinary ease, those around you will suspect sorcery. But the only magic is that which exists in your own heart, the passion you possess for creating delicious, amazing food that can be prepared easily and enjoyed endlessly.</item>
        <item>People quickly learn to ignore the prefix (or suffix) to see the meaningful part of the name. The more we read the code, the less we see the prefixes. Eventually the prefixes become unseen clutter and a marker of older code.</item>
        <item>Many years ago, I was married to a widow. This widow had a grown-up daughter, my father fell in love with her, and soon the two were wed. This made my dad my son-in-law, and my daughter was my mother, because she was my father\'s wife. To complicate the matters, I soon became the father of a bouncing baby boy. My little baby then became a brother-in-law to Dad, and so became my uncle. If he was my uncle, that also made him the brother of the widow\'s grown-up daughter who, of course, was my step-mother. My father\'s wife then had a son, and he became my grandchild, for he was my daughter\'s son. My wife is now my mother\'s mother, and because she is my wife, she\'s my grandmother too. Now, if my wife is my grandmother, then I am her grandchild. Now I have become the strangest case you ever saw, as the husband of my grandmother, I am my own grandpa.</item>
        <item>If you push someone too hard in one direction, they\'re just going to run three times faster in the other direction.</item>
        <item>The bullet of an M16 shoots out at 2,100 miles per hour. Faster than the speed of sound. So if they shot you in the heart, you won\'t even hear the bullet that killed you.</item>
        <item>I\'m such a mess, I\'m such a wreck, and I just don\'t know what to do. It\'s been three years and seven months, and I\'m still in love with you.</item>
        <item>When a man is just born, he is weak and flexible; when he dies, he is hard and insensitive. When a tree is growing, it is tender and pliant, but when it is dry and hard, it dies. Hardness and strength are death\'s companions. Pliancy and weakness are expressions of the freshness of being. Because what has hardened will never win.</item>
        <item>According to legend, Slytherin had built a hidden chamber in this castle, known as the Chamber of Secrets. Shortly before departing, he sealed it until that time when his own true heir returned to the school. The heir alone would be able to open the Chamber of Secrets and unleash the horror within, and by so doing, purge the school of all those who, in Slytherin\'s view, were unworthy to study magic.</item>
        <item>There are too many things we do not wish to know about ourselves. People are not, for example, terribly anxious to be equal, but they love the idea of being superior.</item>
        <item>I pulled back the drape thing on the tent. There was a crystal ball on the table, and behind it, a girl wearing a hat. She smiled, and asked me if I wanted my fortune read. I said okay and sat down. I thought about it for a minute, and asked her if she would rather go on a roller coaster instead.</item>
        <item>If a prediction is right, then it\'s like you only have one future. Like that future has been decided. But if it\'s wrong, then you have an almost infinite number of possibilities. And that means that even the tiniest twist of fate can change your future. I want to believe that I have choices - that the path I walk has many different turns, and many different roads to follow!</item>
        <item>Human beings are experts in wishful thinking and obscuring the truth.</item>
        <item>If the aliens came down today, what would they think, what would they say\? Would they like what we\'ve done with the place, would they tell us the secrets of the human race\? What is a war, why does it start, why build a planet just to tear it apart\?</item>
        <item>It is easy to say that names should reveal intent. What we want to impress upon you is that we are serious about this. Choosing good names takes time but saves more than it takes. So take care with your names and change them when you find better ones.</item>
        <item>You live through that little piece of time that is yours, but that piece of time is not only your own life, it is the summing-up of all the other lives that are simultaneous with yours.</item>
        <item>Some people\'s lives seem to flow in a narrative; mine had many stops and starts. That\'s what trauma does. It interrupts the plot... It just happens, and then life goes on. No one prepares you for it.</item>
        <item>The key to success is to become a successful thinker and then act on those thoughts. That doesn\'t mean that all your ideas and actions will always produce the desired results. At times you will feel that success is unattainable. You may even feel like giving up. I know. I\'ve been there.</item>
        <item>History is written by the victor. History is filled with liars. If he lives, and we die, his truth becomes written - and ours is lost. Shepherd will be a hero, \'cause all you need to change the world is one good lie and a river of blood.</item>
        <item>You, the people, have the power. The power to create machines, the power to create happiness. You, the people, have the power to make this life free and beautiful, to make this life a wonderful adventure. Then, in the name of democracy, let us use that power, let us all unite. Let us fight for a new world, a decent world that will give men a chance to work, that will give you the future.</item>
        <item>If you suddenly and unexpectedly feel joy, don\'t hesitate. Give in to it. There are plenty of lives and whole towns destroyed or about to be. We are not wise, and not very often kind. And much can never be redeemed. Still, life has some possibility left. Perhaps this is its way of fighting back, that sometimes something happens better than all the riches or power in the world. It could be anything, but very likely you notice it in the instant when love begins. Anyway, that\'s often the case. Anyway, whatever it is, don\'t be afraid of its plenty. Joy is not made to be a crumb.</item>
        <item>What isn\'t clear is why people always say \"goes without saying,\" yet still feel compelled to say the thing that was supposed to go without saying.</item>
        <item>And words were not just the pieces of speaking; they were the pieces of thinking. When you wrote them down, you could grasp your thoughts like bricks in your hands and push them into different arrangements.</item>
        <item>Soldiers! Don\'t give yourselves to brutes - men who despise you, enslave you, who regiment your lives, tell you what to do, what to think and what to feel! Who drill you, diet you, treat you like cattle, use you as cannon fodder. Don\'t give yourselves to these unnatural men - machine men with machine minds and machine hearts! You are not machines! You are not cattle! You are men!</item>
        <item>I had a painting teacher once tell me that, the difference between a good painting and a great painting, is typically five strokes. And they\'re usually the five boldest strokes in the painting. The question, of course, is which five strokes\?</item>
        <item>One broken window, left unrepaired for any substantial length of time, instills in the inhabitants of the building a sense of abandonment - a sense that the powers that be don\'t care about the building. So another window gets broken. People start littering. Graffiti appears. Serious structural damage begins. In a relatively short space of time, the building becomes damaged beyond the owner\'s desire to fix it, and the sense of abandonment becomes reality.</item>
        <item>Some people say a man is made outta mud. A poor man\'s made outta muscle and blood. Muscle and blood and skin and bones, a mind that\'s weak and a back that\'s strong. You load sixteen tons, what do you get\? Another day older and deeper in debt. Saint Peter don\'t you call me \'cause I can\'t go, I owe my soul to the company store.</item>
        <item>The certificates we use to make certain of one another: contracts, licenses, ID cards, permits, deeds, certifications, registrations, carry permits, union cards, testimonials, bills, IOUs, temporary permits, letters of consent, income statements, certificates of custody, even proof of pedigree. Is that all of them\? Have I forgotten any\?</item>
        <item>It takes tremendous energy to keep function while carrying the memory of terror, and the same shame of utter weakness and vulnerability.</item>
        <item>If the liberty of myself or my class or nation depends on the misery of a number of other human beings, the system which promotes this is unjust and immoral.</item>
        <item>Nothing in my psychiatric training had prepared me to deal with any of the challenges that Tom and his fellow veterans presented. I went down to the medical library to look for books on war neurosis, shell shock, battle fatigue, or any other term or diagnosis I could think of that might shed light on my patients. To my surprise the library at the VA didn\'t have a single book about any of these conditions. Five years after the last American soldier left Vietnam, the issue of wartime trauma was still not on anybody\'s agenda.</item>
        <item>Every team should follow a coding standard based on common industry norms. This coding standard should specify things like where to declare instance variables; how to name classes, methods, and variables; where to put braces; and so on. The team should not need a document to describe these conventions because their code provides the examples. Everyone on the team should follow these conventions. This means that each team member must be mature enough to realize that it doesn\'t matter a whit where you put your braces so long as you all agree on where to put them.</item>
        <item>I can\'t tell you that this is definitely gonna work out, there\'s no guarantees. But if this turns out to be a big mistake, then let\'s make it the most fun, big mistake we\'ve ever made.</item>
        <item>If you ask me, people spend far too much time looking for someone to complete them. How many people find perfect love\? Or if they do... how many make it last\?</item>
        <item>It is a telling testament of the rich and far-reaching nature of string theory that even our present level of understanding has allowed us to gain striking new insights into the workings of the universe. A central thread in what follows will be those developments that carry forward the revolution in our understanding of space and time initiated by Einstein\'s special and general theories of relativity.</item>
        <item>We\'ve got to figure out what we know we don\'t know. To do that, we\'ve got to confirm what we know we know. But there\'s always a chance, once we figure out what we know we know and what we know we don\'t know, that we won\'t know what we don\'t know, which could be a problem.</item>
        <item>Things we can\'t see affect our lives much more than we think.</item>
        <item>If you continue to do what you\'ve always done, you will continue to have what you\'ve always had.</item>
        <item>After all, damn it, what does being in love mean if you can\'t trust a person.</item>
        <item>What\'s the point of having great knowledge and keeping it all to yourself\?</item>
        <item>Listen well, we are different than regular people because we are born with special powers. But that shouldn\'t give you the illusion that you\'re a special being. We are part of humanity. Besides our rare power, we are no different than them. People who run fast, people who can sing well, people who study hard, people who are funny, and people with psychic powers. Are we different from them\? Having confidence in your strength is good thing but do not get carried away. Our powers are a dangerous weapon.</item>
        <item>Prestige! Sir, is it nothing\? To be revered by fools, gaped at by children, envied by the rich and scorned by the wise.</item>
        <item>People have the right to think and say whatever they want to. But you have the right not to take it to heart, and not to react.</item>
        <item>It was almost like a reverse nightmare, like when you wake up from a nightmare, you\'re so relieved. I woke up into a nightmare.</item>
        <item>I would say that in the world of oddness, a man wearing two hats is no odder than an animal wearing one.</item>
        <item>The less I know about other people\'s affairs, the happier I am. I\'m not interested in caring about people. I once worked with a guy for three years and never learned his name. Best friend I ever had. We still never talk sometimes.</item>
        <item>The strength of a person\'s spirit would then be measured by how much \'truth\' he could tolerate, or more precisely, to what extent he needs to have it diluted, disguised, sweetened, muted, falsified.</item>
        <item>I\'ve got a cupboard with cans of food, filtered water, and pictures of you, and I\'m not coming out until this is all over.</item>
        <item>I am not a religious man, but every now and then, a child comes along who makes me believe in the existence of Satan.</item>
        <item>Oh, this kindergarten crush is gettin\' me wrong. I don\'t know what to do, so I wrote you a song. And this thing is going further than originally planned, so I hope you won\'t mind if I ask you to hold my hand.</item>
        <item>Dreams are only dreams until you wake up and make them real.</item>
        <item>Are you even listening\? Look at me! These kids believe in you, but this isn\'t about you helping them anymore. This is about you loving all of the attention, and the hero worship. If you care about these kids, I mean truly care about them, you\'ll turn yourself in before anyone gets hurt. That\'s what a real leader would have the courage to do.</item>
        <item>They say that the best weapon is the one you never have to fire. I respectfully disagree. I prefer the weapon you only have to fire once.</item>
        <item>If you\'ve ever studied mortal age cartoons, you\'ll remember this one. A coyote was always plotting the demise of a smirking long-necked bird. The coyote never succeeded; instead, his plans always backfired. He would blow up, or get shot, or splat from a ridiculous height. And it was funny, because no matter how deadly his failure, he was always back in the next scene, as if there were a revival center just beyond the edge of the animation cell. I\'ve seen human foibles that have resulted in temporary maiming or momentary loss of life. People stumble into manholes, are hit by falling objects, trip into the paths of speeding vehicles. And when it happens, people laugh, because no matter how gruesome the event, that person, just like the coyote, will be back in a day or two, as good as new, and no worse or wiser for the wear. Immortality has turned us all into cartoons.</item>
        <item>I build neat stuff, got a great girl, occasionally save the world. So why can\'t I sleep\?</item>
        <item>People are screwed up in this world. I\'d rather be with someone screwed up and open about it than somebody perfect and ready to explode.</item>
        <item>As incredible as it may sound, once radio had been invented, no one knew what to do with it. To some, radio was a miracle; to others it was frightening. The fact that voices and music could come out of the air and into a piece of living room furniture was just too incredible even to imagine.</item>
        <item>Ogres trapped my spirit here long ago for daring to defy them. Only through a glorious death will I finally be allowed to rest. It is the only way I will see my brothers and sisters in the afterlife.</item>
        <item>If you shirk the responsibility of confronting the unexpected, even when it appears in manageable doses, reality itself will become unsustainably disorganized and chaotic.</item>
        <item>Some of you may die, but it\'s a sacrifice I am willing to make.</item>
        <item>It\'s a good idea to tell the person you are confronting exactly what you would like them to do instead of what they have done or currently are doing. You might think, \"if they loved me, they would know what to do.\" That\'s the voice of resentment. Assume ignorance before malevolence. No one has a direct pipeline to your wants and needs - not even you. If you try to determine exactly what you want, you might find that it is more difficult than you think. The person oppressing you is likely no wiser than you, especially about you.</item>
        <item>I mean, doesn\'t it kind of defeat the whole purpose of having your own plane if it departs before you arrive\?</item>
        <item>It\'s what the philosopher Alan Watts used to refer to as \"the backwards law\" - the idea that the more you pursue feeling better all the time, the less satisfied you become, as pursuing something only reinforces the fact that you lack it in the first place. The more you desperately want to be rich, the more poor and unworthy you feel, regardless of how much money you actually make. The more you desperately want to be sexy and desired, the uglier you come to see yourself, regardless of your actual physical appearance. The more you desperately want to be happy and loved, the lonelier and more afraid you become, regardless of those who surround you. The more you want to be spiritually enlightened, the more self-centered and shallow you become in trying to get there.</item>
        <item>Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn\'t do than by the ones you did do.</item>
        <item>Whenever I\'m about to do something, I think, \'Would an idiot do that\?\' And if they would, I do not do that thing.</item>
        <item>About 90% of this world\'s problems are caused by little words that come in pairs. We\'re healthy and we\'re happy... but when anybody asks us, we say: \"not bad.\"</item>
        <item>I know very few young people, but it seems to me that they are all possessed with an almost fatal hunger for permanence.</item>
        <item>Every moment can\'t remain and every life won\'t stay the same. With time comes a layer of rust and our bones will turn to dust. Everyone will fall away and every season is built on change. With time the paint will peel and all sense will lose its feel. Every cloth will start to fray and every night will become day. With time a mold will form and what\'s cold can become warm. Love can\'t always stay and the dead will soon decay. With time we\'ll all be gone but how you lived can live on.</item>
        <item>Persons with any weight of character carry, like planets, their atmospheres along with them in their orbits.</item>
        <item>\"Mr. Stark displays compulsive behavior.\" In my own defense, that was a week ago. \"Prone to self-destructive tendencies.\" I was dying. I mean, please, aren\'t we all\? \"Textbook narcissism\?\" Agreed.</item>
        <item>I know you can be underwhelmed, and you can be overwhelmed, but can you ever just be, like, whelmed\?</item>
        <item>Have you ever thought that if you can go back in time, you might still make the same decisions\?</item>
        <item>See, when you mess something up, you learn for the next time. It\'s when people compliment you that you\'re in trouble. That means they expect you to keep it up.</item>
        <item>I made my mistakes, but in all of my years of public life, I have never profited - never profited from public service. I\'ve earned every cent. And in all of my years of public life, I have never obstructed justice. I think, too, that I can say, that in my years of public life, that I welcome this kind of examination because people have got to know whether or not their president is a crook. Well, I\'m not a crook. I\'ve earned everything I\'ve got.</item>
        <item>She was at that modulating point between indifference and love, at the stage called having a fancy for. It occurs once in the history of the most gigantic passions, and it is a period when they are in the hands of the weakest will.</item>
        <item>If I think too much the world seems to disappear, so I\'ll take you up on the Ferris wheel, and simply grab your hand. That\'s alright, and that\'s okay by me. I\'ve got a couple of books on tape, and a fresh pack of cigarettes, and I\'ve quit over twenty times, but I guess I\'ll have to do it again.</item>
        <item>Sometimes we get so wrapped up in getting what we want, that we forget to ask ourselves why we wanted it in the first place.</item>
        <item>Nature\'s first green is gold, her hardest hue to hold. Her early leaf\'s a flower; but only so an hour. Then leaf subsides to leaf. So Eden sank to grief, so dawn goes to day. Nothing gold can stay.</item>
        <item>Yeah, divide and conquer is great, but he knows he has to take us out to win, right\? That\'s what he wants. He wants to beat us, he wants to be seen doing it. He wants an audience.</item>
        <item>Long ago, two races ruled over Earth: Humans and Monsters. One day, war broke out between the two races. After a long battle, the humans were victorious. They sealed the monsters underground with a magic spell.</item>
        <item>So, let me be honest... making money is not like I thought it would be. This business kills the part of life that is essential: the part that has nothing to do with business.</item>
        <item>You never should settle for the lifetime that is handed to you. There\'s always a line to be cut and someone to barrel through. And if you should find that you\'re about to get the short of the stick, take what you want, return what you get.</item>
        <item>I\'m trying to explain that I\'m a person who wishes to live a very quiet life. I take care not to trouble myself with any enemies, like winning and losing, that would cause me to lose sleep at night. That is how I deal with society, and I know that is what brings me happiness. Although, if I were to fight I wouldn\'t lose to anyone.</item>
        <item>You are walking down a country road. It is a quiet afternoon. You look up and far, far down the road you see someone walking toward you. You are surprised to have noticed someone so far away. But you keep walking, expecting nothing more than a friendly nod as you pass. He gets closer. You see he has bright orange hair. He is closer - a white satin suit spotted with colored dots. Closer - a painted white face and red lips. You and he are fifty yards apart. You, and a full-fledged clown holding a bicycle horn are twenty yards apart. You approach on the lonely country road. You nod. He honks and passes.</item>
        <item>There are moments in life we should just be able to have a remote control, so you could pause it. Even if just for five minutes. But sometimes things happen with irreverent obscenity and there\'s nothing you can do to help it.</item>
        <item>Pain is inevitable. Suffering is optional. Say you\'re running and you think, \"Man, this hurts, I can\'t take it anymore.\" The \'hurt\' part is an unavoidable reality, but whether or not you can stand anymore is up to the runner himself.</item>
        <item>Some days I woke up and got out of bed and brushed my teeth like any normal human being; some days I woke up and lay in bed and looked at the ceiling and wondered what the hell the point was of getting out of bed and brushing my teeth like any normal human being.</item>
        <item>You think this is something, you think this is bad, this, this chicanery\? He\'s done worse. That billboard! Are you telling me that a man just happens to fall like that\? No. He orchestrated it! Jimmy! He defecated through a sunroof! And I saved him. I shouldn\'t have, I took him into my own firm! What was I thinking\? He\'ll never change. He\'ll never change, ever since he was 9, always the same. Couldn\'t keep his hands out of the cash drawer. \"But not our Jimmy, couldn\'t be precious Jimmy!\" Stealing them blind... and he gets to be a lawyer\?! What a sick joke! I should have stopped him when I had the chance! And you, you have to stop him!</item>
        <item>Whose woods these are I think I know. His house is in the village though; he will not see me stopping here to watch his woods fill up with snow. My little horse must think it queer to stop without a farmhouse near between the woods and frozen lake the darkest evening of the year. He gives his harness bells a shake to ask if there is some mistake. The only other sound\'s the sweep of easy wind and downy flake. The woods are lovely, dark and deep, but I have promises to keep, and miles to go before I sleep, and miles to go before I sleep.</item>
        <item>She took my arm, I don\'t know how it happened. We took the floor and she said, \"Oh, don\'t you dare look back, just keep your eyes on me.\" I said, \"You\'re holding back.\" She said, \"Shut up and dance with me.\" This woman is my destiny.</item>
        <item>Brother, however I have wronged you, whatever I have done that has led you to do this, I am truly sorry. But these people are innocent, taking their lives will gain you nothing. So take mine, and end this.</item>
        <item>There\'s always happier days to remember. And the more screwed up things are, the happier those days seem to be.</item>
        <item>I waste at least an hour every day lying in bed. Then I waste time pacing. I waste time thinking. I waste time being quiet and not saying anything because I\'m afraid I\'ll stutter.</item>
        <item>What a strange sort of love, to be entirely free from that quality of selfishness which is frequently the chief constituent of the passion, and sometimes it\'s only one!</item>
        <item>Of love it may be said, the less earthly the less demonstrative. In its absolutely indestructible form it reaches a profundity in which all exhibition of itself is painful.</item>
        <item>In this world everything is governed by balance. There\'s what you stand to gain and what you stand to lose. And in this moment they think they have nothing to lose. And when you believe you\'ve got nothing to lose, you\'re overconfident. We will be the ones that are going to show them just how much they have to lose.</item>
        <item>An autobiography is a book a person writes about his own life and it is usually full of all sorts of boring details. This is not an autobiography. I would never write a history of myself. On the other hand, throughout my young days at school and just afterwards a number of things happened to me that I have never forgotten. None of these things is important, but each of them made such a tremendous impression on me that I have never been able to get them out of my mind. Each of them, even after a lapse of fifty and sometimes even sixty years, has remained seared in my memory.</item>
        <item>Great things don\'t happen in tiny little increments. You know, they happen when someone thinks completely differently.</item>
        <item>Every night you cry yourself to sleep, thinking \"Why does this happen to me\?\" Why does every moment have to be so hard\? Hard to believe that it\'s not over tonight, just give me one more chance to make it right. I may not make it through the night, I won\'t go home without you.</item>
        <item>I never came to the beach or stood by the ocean, I never sat by the shore under the sun with my feet in the sand, but you brought me here and I\'m happy that you did.</item>
        <item>If someone is able to show me that what I think or do is not right, I will happily change, for I seek the truth, by which no one was ever truly harmed. It is the person who continues in his self-deception and ignorance who is harmed.</item>
        <item>I want to be very small, and I want you to put me in your pocket, and I wanna stay there and you can just reach in whenever you want and just pat me on the head.</item>
        <item>Make sure you marry someone who laughs at the same things you do.</item>
        <item>Mother is the name for God in the lips and hearts of little children.</item>
        <item>I wish I were a girl again, half-savage and hardy, and free.</item>
        <item>You should never, never doubt something that no one is sure of.</item>
        <item>What a charming reconciler and peacemaker money is!</item>
        <item>Believe in one thing too much and you have no room for new ideas.</item>
        <item>The last man on Earth sat alone in a room. There was a knock on the door.</item>
        <item>In the midst of friends, home, and kind parents, she was alone.</item>
        <item>Delicacy and dignity are taught by one\'s own heart, not by a dancing master.</item>
        <item>Before time began, there was the Cube. We know not where it comes from, only that it holds the power to create worlds and fill them with life. That is how our race was born. For a time we lived in harmony, but like all great power, some wanted it for good, others for evil. And so began the war. A war that ravaged our planet until it was consumed by death, and the Cube was lost to the far reaches of space. We scattered across the galaxy, hoping to find it and rebuild our home. Searching every star, every world. And just when all hope seemed lost, message of a new discovery drew us to an unknown planet called... Earth. But we were already too late.</item>
        <item>In fact, the Americans of 1776 enjoyed a higher standard of living than any people in the world. Their material wealth was considerably less than it would become in time, still it was a great deal more than others had elsewhere. How people with so much, living on their own land, would ever choose to rebel against the ruler God had put over them and thereby bring down such devastation upon themselves was for the invaders incomprehensible.</item>
        <item>The secret of a good old age is simply an honorable pact with solitude.</item>
        <item>It was strange, I reflected... that even in the weirdest circumstances, the most troubling episodes of one\'s life, the greatest divides from home and familiarity, there were these moments of undeniable joy.</item>
        <item>The thing under my bed waiting to grab my ankle isn\'t real. I know that, and I also know that if I\'m careful to keep my foot under the covers, it will never be able to grab my ankle.</item>
        <item>Just as people behave to me, so do I behave to them. When I see that a person despises me and treats me with contempt, I can be as proud as any peacock.</item>
        <item>All children have to be deceived if they are to grow up without trauma.</item>
        <item>Never say anything unless it is worth taking a long time to say.</item>
        <item>My thermos flask keeps hot drinks hot, and cold drinks cold. But how does it know\?</item>
        <item>And to think, if it weren\'t for you... I never would\'ve danced at all.</item>
        <item>We\'ve wounded this mountain. It\'s our duty to close her wounds. It\'s the least we can do to show our gratitude for all the wealth she\'s given us. If you guys don\'t want to help me, I\'ll do it alone.</item>
        <item>Death is but crossing the world, as friends do the seas; they live in one another still. For they must needs be present, that love and live in that which is omnipresent. In this divine glass they see face to face; and their converse is free, as well as pure. This is the comfort of friends, that thought they may be said to die, yet their friendship and society are, in the best sense, ever present, because immortal.</item>
        <item>However small the chance might be of striking lucky, the chance was there.</item>
        <item>Everything in this room is edible. Even I\'m edible. But, that would be called cannibalism. It is looked down upon in most societies.</item>
        <item>Clever, but schoolteacher beat him anyway to show him that definitions belonged to the definers - not the defined.</item>
        <item>Believe me, the irony of being a blind art dealer isn\'t lost on me.</item>
        <item>I often think that men don\'t understand what is noble and what is ignorant, though they always talk about it.</item>
        <item>You have to keep your mind as wide-open as your eyes, because almost nothing is what it seems.</item>
        <item>Never become used to anything you love. It blunts the edge of appreciation.</item>
        <item>Courage is resistance to fear, mastery of fear - not absence of fear.</item>
        <item>The difference between treason and patriotism is only a matter of dates.</item>
        <item>I could work at a problem for years, but to wait inactive for twenty-four hours - that is another matter.</item>
        <item>I am now quite cured of seeking pleasure in society, be it country or town. A sensible man ought to find sufficient company in himself.</item>
        <item>Treachery and violence are spears pointed at both ends; they wound those who resort to them worse than their enemies.</item>
        <item>War... has changed. It\'s no longer about nations, ideologies, or ethnicity. It\'s an endless series of proxy battles fought by mercenaries and machines. War, and its consumption of life, has become a well-oiled machine. War has changed. ID-tagged soldiers carry ID-tagged weapons, use ID-tagged gear. Nano-machines inside their bodies enhance and regulate their abilities. Genetic control, information control, emotion control... battlefield control. Everything is monitored and kept under control. War - has changed. The age of deterrence has become the age of control. All in the name of averting catastrophe from Weapons of Mass Destruction. And he who controls the battlefield, controls history. War has changed... When the battlefield is under total control, war becomes routine.</item>
        <item>He really had been through death, but he had returned because he could not bear the solitude.</item>
        <item>I am the wisest man alive, for I know one thing, and that is that I know nothing.</item>
        <item>He come to me with money in his hand. He offered me, I didn\'t ask him. I wasn\'t knocking someone\'s door down, I was running from that. When I got out, I was in that. I was already through that, I had that. I had the studio, I went to the studio. I went to Vox Studios. I had it all, and I looked at it and said, \'This is a bigger jail than I just got out of.\' I don\'t want to take my time going to work. I got a motorcycle and a sleeping bag. And ten or fifteen girls. What the hell I wanna go off into - and go to work for\? Work for what, money\? I got all the money in the world. I\'m the king, man. I run the underworld, guy. I decide who does what and where they do it at. What am I, gonna run around and act like I\'m some teenybopper somewhere, for somebody else\'s money\? I make the money, man, I roll the nickels. The game is mine. I deal the cards.</item>
        <item>As an adult I have often known that peculiar legacy time brings to the traveler: the longing to seek out a place a second time, to find deliberately what we stumbled on once before, to recapture the feeling of discovery. Sometimes we search out again even a place that was not remarkable itself - we look for it simply because we remember it. If we do find it, of course, everything is different. The rough-hewn door is still there, but it\'s much smaller; the day is cloudy instead of brilliant; it\'s spring instead of autumn; we\'re alone instead of with three friends. Or worse, with three friends instead of alone.</item>
        <item>Too much mystery is merely an annoyance. Too much adventure is exhausting. And a little terror goes a long way.</item>
        <item>Oh, and one last favor. If you pass by heaven, give my regards to the angels. But if you end up in hell, give my address to the devil.</item>
        <item>Why is it that when you awake to the world of realities you nearly always feel, sometimes very vividly, that the vanished dream has carried with it some enigma which you have failed to solve\?</item>
        <item>I saw something moving round the foot of the bed, which at first I could not accurately distinguish. But I soon saw that it was a sooty-black animal that resembled a monstrous cat. It appeared to me about four or five feet long for it measured fully the length of the hearthrug as it passed over it; and it continued to-ing and fro-ing with the lithe, sinister restlessness of a beast in a cage. I could not cry out, although as you may suppose, I was terrified. Its pace was growing faster, and the room rapidly darker and darker, and at length so dark that I could no longer see anything of it but its eyes. I felt it spring lightly on the bed. The two broad eyes approached my face, and suddenly I felt a stinging pain as if two large needles darted, an inch or two apart, deep into my chest. I waked with a scream.</item>
        <item>You know what kind of plan never fails\? No plan at all. No plan. You know why\? If you make a plan, life never works out that way. Look around us, did these people think \"Let\'s all spend the night in a gym\?\" But look now, everyone\'s sleeping on the floor, us included. That\'s why people shouldn\'t make plans. With no plan, nothing can go wrong and if something spins out of control, it doesn\'t matter. Whether you kill someone or betray your country. None of it matters. Got it\?</item>
        <item>It matters not how a man dies, but how he lives. The act of dying is not of importance, it lasts so short a time.</item>
        <item>To learn what we fear is to learn who we are. Horror defies our boundaries and illuminates our souls.</item>
        <item>I just want to be able to stand up straight for a little while before I get cut down.</item>
        <item>The wretched and the miserable should turn to their Savior first, yet they do not hope in Him until all other hope is exhausted.</item>
        <item>This time it\'s a fierce action-packed battle to free the land of Subcon from the curse of the evil Wart. It\'s up to you, along with Mario, Luigi, Toad and the Princess, to fight your way through bizarre multi-level worlds and find him! This time you\'ve got a brand new kind of power - plucking power - and now anything you find can be a weapon. But beware! You\'ve never seen creatures like this! Shyguys and Tweeters! Ninji and Beezos! And you\'ve never had an adventure like this! Only cunning and speed can save you now...</item>
        <item>Are you trying to impress me\? What would impress me more is if you never did that again.</item>
        <item>You can\'t convince me what I want and what I need are separate things.</item>
        <item>His ear heard more than what was said to him, and his slow speech had overtones not of thought, but of understanding beyond thought.</item>
        <item>I\'m in a crisis. I need help. Come on, mood, shift back to good again. Come on, be a friend. Nina Twin is trying to help, and I really hope that she succeeds. Though I picked the thorny path myself, I\'m afraid of where it leads. Chemicals, don\'t strangle my pen. Chemicals, don\'t make me sick again. I\'m always so dubious of your intent, like I can\'t afford to replace what you\'ve spent. Come on, chemicals. Nina Twin is trying to help, and I really hope she gets me straight, because my own inner cosmology has become too dense to navigate.</item>
        <item>No one really knows why they\'re alive until they know what they\'d die for.</item>
        <item>Among other things, you\'ll find that you\'re not the first person who was ever confused and frightened and even sickened by human behavior. You\'re by no means alone on that score, you\'ll be excited and stimulated to know. Many, many men have been just as troubled morally and spiritually as you are right now. Happily, some of them kept records of their troubles. You\'ll learn from them - if you want to. Just as someday, if you have something to offer, someone will learn something from you. It\'s a beautiful reciprocal arrangement. And it isn\'t education. It\'s history. It\'s poetry.</item>
        <item>That\'s because only a real artist knows the actual anatomy of the terrible or the physiology of fear - the exact sort of lines and proportions that connect up with latent instincts or hereditary memories of fright, and the proper color contrasts and lighting effects to stir the dormant sense of strangeness.</item>
        <item>The world was reduced to the surface of her skin and her inner self was safe from all bitterness.</item>
        <item>There is nothing a man cannot do once he accepts the fact that there is no god.</item>
        <item>And I have by me, for my comfort, two strange white flowers - shriveled now, and brown and flat and brittle - to witness that even when mind and strength had gone, gratitude and a mutual tenderness still lived on in the heart of men.</item>
        <item>Nature never appeals to intelligence until habit and instinct are useless. There is no intelligence where there is no need of change.</item>
        <item>What condemnation could possibly be more harsh than one\'s own, when self-pretense is no longer possible\?</item>
        <item>The world, although well-lighted with fluorescents and incandescent bulbs and neon, is still full of odd dark corners and unsettling nooks and crannies.</item>
        <item>Don\'t tell me what\'s necessary, you presumptuous pup. What\'s necessary is whatever I wish to do, regardless of how unnecessary it might be.</item>
        <item>And remember also that in fighting against man we must not come to resemble him. Even when you have conquered him, do not adopt his vices.</item>
        <item>Grief is like a drunken house guest, always coming back for one more goodbye hug.</item>
        <item>If you didn\'t have me to rake you over the coals now and then, there wouldn\'t be any fire in your life at all.</item>
        <item>Me and you, we got more yesterday than anybody. We need some kind of tomorrow.</item>
        <item>There was a time, not very long ago, when we lived in an enchanted world of elegant palaces and grand parties. The year was 1916 and my son, Nicholas, was the Czar of Imperial Russia. We were celebrating the 300th anniversary of our family\'s rule. And, that night, no star burned brighter than that of our sweet Anastasia, my youngest granddaughter. She begged me not to return to Paris, so I had a very special gift made for her, to make the separation easier - for both of us.</item>
        <item>There is no difference between time and any of the dimensions of space except that our consciousness moves along it.</item>
        <item>He supposed that even in Hell, people got an occasional sip of water, if only so they could appreciate the full horror of unrequited thirst when it set in again.</item>
        <item>I am always saying \"Glad to\'ve met you\" to somebody I\'m not at all glad I met. If you want to stay alive, you have to say that stuff, though.</item>
        <item>It\'s funny. All you have to do is say something nobody understands and they\'ll do practically anything you want them to.</item>
        <item>The distinguishing mark of man is the hand, the instrument with which he does all his mischief.</item>
        <item>A trickle of blood came out under the door, crossed the living room, went out into the street, continued on in a straight line across the uneven terraces, went down steps and climbed over curbs, passed along the Street of the Turks, turned a corner to the right and another to the left, made a right angle at the Buendia house, went in under the closed door, crossed through the parlor, hugging the walls so as not to stain the rugs, went on to the other living room, made a wide curve to avoid the dining-room table, went along the porch with the begonias, and passed without being seen under Amaranta\'s chair as she gave an arithmetic lesson to Aureliano Jose, and went through the pantry and came out in the kitchen, where Ursula was getting ready to crack thirty-six eggs to make bread.</item>
        <item>Dawn was close. The weaker stars had already disappeared, and even the brightest were uncertain of themselves.</item>
        <item>It was in fact a very important part of my plan that you were unharmed. We needed someone with no motive to see what had happened here. Someone other than Zee, obviously. Where is Zee\?</item>
        <item>They\'re surrounding the city to make a fortress so that no one can see what they\'re up to inside. Our only chance is the element of surprise.</item>
        <item>I celebrate myself, and sing myself, and what I assume you shall assume, for every atom belonging to me as good belongs to you. I loafe and invite my soul, I lean and loafe at my ease observing a spear of summer grass. My tongue, every atom of my blood, form\'d from this soil, this air, born here of parents born here from parents the same, and their parents the same, I, now thirty-seven years old in perfect health begin, hoping to cease not till death.</item>
        <item>Very simple was my explanation, and plausible enough - as most wrong theories are!</item>
        <item>At three in the morning the blood runs slow and thick, and slumber is heavy. The soul either sleeps in blessed ignorance of such an hour or gazes about itself in utter despair. There is no middle ground.</item>
        <item>In every war, there are calms between storms. There will be days when you lose faith in some of us, days when our allies turn against us, but the day will never come if we forsake this planet and its people.</item>
        <item>Frank grimaced with concentration. Suddenly, he disappeared. On the deck where he\'d been standing, a green iguana crouched next to an empty set of Chinese handcuffs. \"Well done, Frank Zhang,\" Leo said dryly, doing his impression of Chiron the centaur. \"That is exactly how people beat Chinese handcuffs. They turn into iguanas.\"</item>
        <item>A weakened mind always sees everything through a black veil. The soul makes its own horizons; your soul is dark, which is why you see such a cloudy sky.</item>
        <item>You know, I don\'t know her very well, but perhaps she\'s one of those people that sees things in absolutes, right\? Black and white. Missions fail or succeed, right\? Do you know what you need to do\? You need to get back in there with her. Open her up and show her that things aren\'t just black and white. Black and white, that\'s just for death and taxes. Everything else... Everything else happens in the grays.</item>
        <item>Power is living while others inevitably perish. Power is cool indifference to their suffering. Power is taking nourishment from the deaths of others, just as the mighty redwoods draw sustenance from the perpetual decomposition of what once lived, but lived only briefly, around them.</item>
        <item>She\'d been acutely aware that terror, betrayal, and cruelty had a human face, but she had not sufficiently appreciated that courage, kindness, and love had a human face as well.</item>
        <item>The very worst impulses of humankind can survive generations, centuries, even millennia. And the best of our individual efforts can die with us at the end of a single lifetime.</item>
        <item>Oh, I don\'t read. I skulk about in search of quotations that might make me appear educated.</item>
        <item>When rationality begins to break down, the circuits of the human brain can overload. Axons grow bright and feverish. Hallucinations turn real: the quicksilver puddle at the point where perspective makes parallel lines seem to intersect is really there; the dead walk and talk; a rose begins to sing.</item>
        <item>\"Thinking I\'m a moron gives people something to feel smug about,\" Charles Wallace said. \"Why should I disillusion them\?\"</item>
        <item>What are you doing on my boat\? Look, I\'ve had a really bad day and I just need your help. You see, I\'ve been thrown out of my home and flushed down my own toilet.</item>
        <item>The horrors of the Inquisition are nothing compared to the fates your mind can imagine for your loved ones.</item>
        <item>She asks me to kill the spider. Instead, I get the most peaceful weapons I can find. I take a cup and a napkin. I catch the spider, put it outside and allow it to walk away. If I am ever caught in the wrong place at the wrong time, just being alive and not bothering anyone, I hope I am greeted with the same kind of mercy.</item>
        <item>Things conceived by minds and made by hands can never be quite the same, even if they try their best to be identical, because they\'re never the same from day to day or even moment to moment.</item>
        <item>This is called 90 Mile Beach because it is exactly 55 miles long. I don\'t understand that either.</item>
        <item>There are horrors beyond life\'s edge that we do not suspect, and once in a while man\'s evil prying calls them just within our range.</item>
        <item>You must follow me carefully. I shall have to controvert one or two ideas that are almost universally accepted. The geometry, for instance, they taught you at school is founded on a misconception.</item>
        <item>But what leaves us out of breath the most isn\'t the moments spent on a bed too small for two but the expense of our hearts by the labor of our bodies. I guess that two float around the point. But I wanna say it\'s more than just those moments, at least more than the surface. It\'s the tempo within those seconds where time seems to slow to a crawl and I can\'t help but fall into the rhythm of your skin and your shaking breath and I sink into the warmest dreams and the softest skin.</item>
        <item>There\'s no more harm in a kiss than shaving a monkey and pretending it\'s a woman.</item>
        <item>Kelsey, in this terrifying world, all we have are the connections that we make. I\'m sorry I got you fired.</item>
        <item>Mr Willy Wonka can make marshmallows that taste of violets, and rich caramels that change colour every ten seconds as you suck them, and little feathery sweets that melt away deliciously the moment you put them between your lips. He can make chewing-gum that never loses its taste, and sugar balloons that you can blow up to enormous sizes before you pop them with a pin and gobble them up. And, by a most secret method, he can make lovely blue birds\' eggs with black spots on them, and when you put one of these in your mouth, it gradually gets smaller and smaller until suddenly there is nothing left except a tiny little dark red sugary baby bird sitting on the tip of your tongue.</item>
        <item>That is the germ of my great discovery. But you are wrong to say that we cannot move about in time. For instance, if I am recalling an incident very vividly I go back to the instant of its occurrence: I become absent-minded, as you say. I jump back for a moment. Of course we have no means of staying back for any length of time, any more than a savage or an animal has of staying six feet above the ground. But a civilized man is better off than the savage in this respect. He can go up against gravitation in a balloon, and why should he not hope that ultimately he may be able to stop or accelerate his drift along the time-dimension, or even turn about and travel the other way\?</item>
        <item>Jill, this is Sergeant Sacker. Listen to me. We\'ve traced the call... it\'s coming from inside the house. Now a squad car\'s coming over there right now, just get out of that house!</item>
        <item>There are moments that define a person\'s whole life. Moments in which everything they are and everything they may possibly become balance on a single decision. Life and death, hope and despair, victory and failure teeter precariously on the decision made at that moment. These are moments ungoverned by happenstance, untroubled by luck. These are the moments in which a person earns the right to live, or not.</item>
        <item>You don\'t make history by following the rules, you make it by seizing the moment.</item>
        <item>Joy to hearts which have suffered long is like the dew on the ground after a long drought; both the heart and the ground absorb that beneficent moisture falling on them, and nothing is outwardly apparent.</item>
        <item>We all start out knowing magic. We are born with whirlwinds, forest fires, and comets inside us. We are born able to sing to birds and read the clouds and see our destiny in grains of sand. But then we get the magic educated right out of our souls.</item>
        <item>Scientists talk about dark matter, the invisible, mysterious substance that occupies the space between stars. Dark matter makes up 99.99 percent of the universe, and they don\'t know what it is. Well I do. It\'s apathy. That\'s the truth of it; pile together everything we know and care about in the universe and it will still be nothing more than a tiny speck in the middle of a vast black ocean.</item>
        <item>There is a vast melancholy in the canticles of the wolves, melancholy infinite as the forest, endless as these long nights of winter and yet that ghastly sadness, that mourning for their own, irremediable appetites, can never move the heart for not one phrase in it hints at the possibility of redemption.</item>
        <item>Give me the child... Through dangers untold and hardships unnumbered, I have fought my way here to the castle beyond the goblin city to take back the child which you have stolen. For my will is as strong as yours and my kingdom as great. You have no power over me.</item>
        <item>Sometimes, when you\'re writing a poem - or a story - your brain gets fixated on a specific point. If you try so hard to make it perfect, then you\'ll never make any progress. Just force yourself to get something down on the paper, and tidy it up later! Another way to think about it is this: if you keep your pen in the same spot for too long, you\'ll just get a big dark puddle of ink. So just move your hand, and go with the flow!</item>
        <item>No live organism can continue for long to exist sanely under conditions of absolute reality; even larks and katydids are supposed, by some, to dream. Hill House, not sane, stood by itself against its hills, holding darkness within; it had stood so for eighty years and might stand for eighty more. Within, walls continued upright, bricks met neatly, floors were firm, and doors were sensibly shut; silence lay steadily against the wood and stone of Hill House, and whatever walked there, walked alone.</item>
        <item>One can\'t understand everything at once, we can\'t begin with perfection all at once! In order to reach perfection one must begin by being ignorant of a great deal. And if we understand things too quickly, perhaps we shan\'t understand them thoroughly.</item>
        <item>Death doesn\'t exist. It never did, it never will. But we\'ve drawn so many pictures of it, so many years, trying to pin it down, comprehend it, we\'ve got to thinking of it as an entity, strangely alive and greedy. All it is, however, is a stopped watch, a loss, an end, a darkness. Nothing.</item>
        <item>We frequently pass so near to happiness without seeing, without regarding it, or if we do see and regard it, yet without recognizing it.</item>
        <item>The prize returns to me. Did you imagine that I would let you steal it from me\? You what\? That jewel belongs to my father and you know it. Your father, a good-for-nothing scavenger just like his daughter!</item>
        <item>Well, father, in the shipwreck of life, for life is an eternal shipwreck of our hopes, I cast into the sea my useless encumbrance, that is all, and I remain with my own will, disposed to live perfectly alone, and, consequently, perfectly free.</item>
        <item>He looked at her as a man might look at a faded flower he had plucked, in which it was difficult for him to trace the beauty that had made him pick and so destroy it.</item>
        <item>I think she wanted you, of all people, to know the truth. She wanted to live on in your memory, not as a soldier, but as a woman. But - she was forbidden to tell you herself. And that\'s why she told me. Snake, history will never know what she did. No one will ever learn the truth. Her story... her debriefing, will endure only in your heart. Everything she did, she did for her country. She sacrificed her life and her honor for her native land. She was a real hero. She was a true patriot.</item>
        <item>A water snake glided smoothly up the pool, twisting its periscope head from side to side; and it swam the length of the pool and came to the legs of a motionless heron that stood in the shadows. A silent head and beak lanced down and plucked it out by the head, and the beak swallowed the little snake while its tail waved frantically.</item>
        <item>I think reality is thin, you know, thin as lake ice after a thaw, and we fill our lives with noise and light and motion to hide that thinness from ourselves.</item>
        <item>I had the brief notion that his heart, pressed flat as a flower, crimson and thin as tissue paper, lay in this file. It was a very thin one.</item>
        <item>What was surprising - and would largely be forgotten as time went on - was how well Adams had done. Despite the malicious attacks on him, the furor over the Alien and Sedition Acts, unpopular taxes, betrayals by his own cabinet, the disarray of the Federalists, and the final treachery of Hamilton, he had, in fact, come very close to winning in the electoral count. With a difference of only 250 votes in New York City, Adams would have won an electoral count of 71 to 61. So another of the ironies of 1800 was that Jefferson, the apostle of agrarian America who loathed cities, owed his ultimate political triumph to New York.</item>
        <item>The moon will never lie to anyone. Be like the moon. No one hates the moon or wants to kill it. The moon does not take antidepressants and never gets sent to prison. The moon never shot a guy in the face and ran away. The moon has been around a long time and has never tried to rip anyone off. The moon does not care who you want to touch or what color you are. The moon treats everyone the same. The moon never tries to get in on the guest list or use your name to impress others. Be like the moon. When others insult or belittle in an attempt to elevate themselves, the moon sits passively and watches, never lowering itself to anything that weak. The moon is beautiful and bright. It needs no makeup to look beautiful. The moon never shoves clouds out of its way so it can be seen. The moon needs not fame or money to be powerful. The moon never asks you to go to war to defend it. Be like the moon.</item>
        <item>In the Valley, prediction has become a popular way of fighting for a particular future while claiming merely what has yet to occur. Prediction has a useful air of selflessness to it. Predictors aren\'t caught in the here and now of their own appetites and interests. It seems like they aren\'t choosing how things will be in the future any more than they choose the color of their eyes. Yet selecting one scenario among many possible scenarios and persuading everybody of its inevitability - and of the futility of a society\'s exercising its collective choice among these futures - is a deft way to shape the future.</item>
        <item>Without a means of leaving this world, we Autobots take strength in the bonds we have forged with our three young friends - true warriors. If not in body, then in spirit. My name is Optimus Prime, and I send this message. Though we did not choose to be of Earth, it would seem that we are here to stay. If you approach this planet with hostile intent, know this: We will defend ourselves. We will defend humanity. We will defend... our home.</item>
        <item>This thirty-five-page essay had been written in two or three weeks by Hamilton, as he entered the fray with all the grandiloquence and learning at his disposal. He showed himself proficient at elegant insults, an essential literary talent at the time, and possessing a precocious knowledge of history, philosophy, politics, economics, and law. In retrospect, it was clear that he had found his calling as a fearless, swashbuckling intellectual warrior who excelled in bare-knuckled controversy.</item>
        <item>I\'ve always loved you, and when you love someone, you love the whole person, just as he or she is, and not as you would like them to be.</item>
        <item>Don\'t say you lose just yet, get up and move ahead, and not only for yourself. \'Cause that\'s your role, the work that stirred your soul you can make for someone else. One day you choke, your urges overflow, and obsession wears you down. But don\'t you waste the suffering you\'ve faced; it will serve you in due time.</item>
        <item>As long as people believe in absurdities, they will continue to commit atrocities.</item>
        <item>One of the great conditions of anger and hatred is, that you must tell and believe lies against the hated object, in order, as we said, to be consistent.</item>
        <item>The essential and defining characteristic of childhood is not the effortless merging of dream and reality, but only alienation. There are no words for childhood\'s dark turns and exhalations. A wise child recognizes it and submits to the necessary consequences. A child who counts the cost is a child no longer.</item>
        <item>If actions speak louder than words I\'m the most deafening noise you\'ve heard. I\'ll be that ringing in your ears that will stick around for years.</item>
        <item>We love people who\'ve died... where\'s the social utility in that\? Maybe it means something more - something we can\'t yet understand. Maybe it\'s some evidence, some artifact of a higher dimension that we can\'t consciously perceive. I\'m drawn across the universe to someone I haven\'t seen in a decade, who I know is probably dead. Love is the one thing we\'re capable of perceiving that transcends dimensions of time and space. Maybe we should trust that, even if we can\'t understand it yet.</item>
        <item>Of course they\'re real people. They\'re Oompa-Loompas imported direct from Loompaland... and oh, what a terrible country it is! Nothing but thick jungles infested by the most dangerous beasts in the world - hornswogglers and snozzwangers and those terrible wicked whangdoodles. A whangdoodle would eat ten Oompa-Loompas for breakfast and come galloping back for a second helping.</item>
        <item>It was not the brutality of what occurred next that changed my mind and brought home to me the full meaning of fear. It was the brilliance of it.</item>
        <item>Learning does not make one learned: there are those who have knowledge and those who have understanding. The first requires memory and the second philosophy.</item>
        <item>The more Adams thought about the future of his country, the more convinced he became that it rested on education. Before any great things are accomplished, he wrote to a correspondent, a memorable change must be made in the system of education and knowledge must become so general as to raise the lower ranks of society nearer to the higher. The education of a nation instead of being confined to a few schools and universities for the instruction of the few, must become the national care and expense for the formation of the many.</item>
        <item>Oh, the terrible struggle that I have had against sleep so often of late; the pain of the sleeplessness, or the pain of the fear of sleep, and with such unknown horror as it has for me! How blessed are some people, whose lives have no fears, no dreads; to whom sleep is a blessing that comes nightly, and brings nothing but sweet dreams.</item>
        <item>A generous spirit prefers that his country should be poor, and weak, and of no account, but free, rather than powerful, prosperous, and enslaved. It is better to be the citizen of a humble commonwealth in the Alps, without a prospect of influence beyond the narrow frontier, than a subject of the superb autocracy that overshadows half of Asia and of Europe.</item>
        <item>A field, though fertile, cannot yield a harvest without cultivation, no more can the mind without learning; thus each is feeble without the other.</item>
        <item>Each day I sat on the verandah with my uncle and cousins looking toward the city. We had stopped listening to the storytelling cassette, as curfews started before dark. My uncle laughed less and less, and sighed more and more. We continued to hope that things would change, but they kept getting worse.</item>
        <item>It\'s like this, I think: the excellence of a good body doesn\'t make the soul good, but the other way around: the excellence of a good soul makes the body as good as it can be.</item>
        <item>Grown-up people do not know that a child can give exceedingly good advice even in the most difficult case.</item>
        <item>We must never forget that human motives are generally far more complicated than we are apt to suppose, and that we can very rarely accurately describe the motives of another.</item>
        <item>I don\'t think man was meant to attain happiness so easily. Happiness is like those palaces in fairy tales whose gates are guarded by dragons: we must fight in order to conquer it.</item>
        <item>Be cautious then, young ladies; be wary how you engage. Be shy of loving frankly; never tell all you feel, or (a better way still), feel very little. See the consequences of being prematurely honest and confiding, and mistrust yourselves and everybody. Get yourselves married as they do in France, where the lawyers are the bridesmaids and confidantes. At any rate, never have any feelings which may make you uncomfortable, or make any promises which you cannot at any required moment command and withdraw. That is the way to get on, and be respected, and have a virtuous character in Vanity Fair.</item>
        <item>The new-born child does not realize that his body is more a part of himself than surrounding objects, and will play with his toes without any feeling that they belong to him more than the rattle by his side; and it is only by degrees, through pain, that he understands the fact of the body.</item>
        <item>I want you to say that you know what I\'m saying. But I need more, because I\'ll be you, you\'ll be me. There\'s lots and lots for us to see. There\'s lots and lots for us to do. She is electric, and I\'ll be electric too.</item>
        <item>To dream in isolation can be properly splendid to be sure; but to dream in company seems to me infinitely preferable.</item>
        <item>They linked their arms to make a step, then boosted me onto the throne. I felt like a baby with my feet so high off the ground. I looked around at the other gloomy, empty thrones, and I could imagine what it would be like sitting on the Olympian Council - so much power but so much arguing, always eleven other gods trying to get their way. It would be easy to get paranoid, to look out only for my own interest, especially if I were Poseidon. Sitting in his throne, I felt like I had the entire sea at my command - vast cubic miles of ocean churning with power and mystery. Why should Poseidon listen to anyone\? Why shouldn\'t he be the greatest of the twelve\?</item>
        <item>When you lose the ones you love, you might find it hard to cry. Until it\'s only you and everybody else has left the room, you might feel what it\'s like to not know how to feel.</item>
        <item>With the All Spark gone, we cannot return life to our planet. And fate has yielded its reward: a new world to call home. We live among its people now, hiding in plain sight, but watching over them in secret, waiting, protecting. I have witnessed their capacity for courage, and though we are worlds apart, like us, there\'s more to them than meets the eye. I am Optimus Prime and I send this message to any surviving Autobots taking refuge among the stars. We are here. We are waiting.</item>
        <item>Whenever a single definite object is made the supreme end of the State, be it the advantage of a class, the safety of the power of the country, the greatest happiness of the greatest number, or the support of any speculative idea, the State becomes for the time inevitably absolute. Liberty alone demands for its realisation the limitation of the public authority, for liberty is the only object which benefits all alike, and provokes no sincere opposition.</item>
        <item>If you had an injury and your doctor said it might help, would you be willing to let leeches feast for a few minutes, say, on your hand\? On your face\?</item>
        <item>It\'s almost time, kids. The clock is ticking. Be in front of your TV sets for the Horrorthon, followed by the Big Giveaway. Don\'t miss it. And don\'t forget to wear your masks. The clock is ticking. It\'s almost time.</item>
        <item>Your future hasn\'t been written yet; no one\'s has. Your future is whatever you make it, so make it a good one.</item>
        <item>You plonker, you think I don\'t know a toilet when I see one\? You were going to flush me down the loo.</item>
        <item>It had never occurred to him until then to think that literature was the best plaything that had ever been invented to make fun of people...</item>
        <item>Benjamin was the oldest animal on the farm, and the worst tempered. He seldom talked, and when he did, it was usually to make some cynical remark - for instance, he would say that God had given him a tail to keep the flies off, but that he would sooner have had no tail and no flies.</item>
        <item>And I promise you I\'ll never desert you again because after \'Salome\' we\'ll make another picture and another picture. You see, this is my life! It always will be! Nothing else! Just us, and the cameras, and those wonderful people out there in the dark! All right, Mr. DeMille, I\'m ready for my close-up.</item>
        <item>Never before had I known the sudden quiver of understanding that travels from word to brain to heart, the way a new language can move, coil, swim into life under the eyes, the almost savage leap of comprehension, the instantaneous, joyful release of meaning, the way the words shed their printed bodies in a flash of heat and light.</item>
        <item>The whole world is divided for me into two parts: one is she, and there is all happiness, hope, light; the other is where she is not, and there is dejection and darkness...</item>
        <item>But the law of loving others could not be discovered by reason, because it is unreasonable.</item>
        <item>The ingenious are always fanciful, and the truly imaginative never otherwise than analytic.</item>
        <item>I feel that life is divided into the horrible and the miserable. That\'s the two categories. The horrible are like, I don\'t know, terminal cases, you know, and blind people, crippled. I don\'t know how they get through life. It\'s amazing to me. And the miserable is everyone else. So you should be thankful that you\'re miserable, because that\'s very lucky, to be miserable.</item>
        <item>By the latter part of 1861 the War Department had taken over from the states the responsibility for feeding, clothing, and arming Union soldiers. But this process was marred by inefficiency, profiteering, and corruption. To fill contracts for hundreds of thousands of uniforms, textile manufacturers compressed the fibers of recycled woolen goods into a material called \"shoddy.\" This noun soon became an adjective to describe uniforms that ripped after a few weeks of wear, shoes that fell apart, blankets that disintegrated, and poor workmanship in general on items necessary to equip an army of half a million men and to create its support services within a few short months.</item>
        <item>But her brain was not interested in the future. Loaded with the past and hungry for more, it left her no room to imagine, let alone plan for, the next day.</item>
        <item>Evening of a hot day started the little wind to moving among the leaves. The shade climbed up the hills toward the top. On the sand banks the rabbits sat as quietly as little gray, sculptured stones.</item>
        <item>I think if you don\'t really like a girl, you shouldn\'t horse around with her at all, and if you do like her, then you\'re supposed to like her face, and if you like her face, you ought to be careful about doing crumby stuff to it, like squirting water all over it. It\'s really too bad that so much crumby stuff is a lot of fun sometimes.</item>
        <item>Some of Washington\'s religious style probably reflected an Enlightenment discomfort with religious dogma, but it also reflected his low-key personal style. He was sober and temperate in all things, distrusted zealotry, and would never have talked of hellfire or damnation. He would have shunned anything, such as communion, that might flaunt his religiosity. He never wanted to make a spectacle of his faith or trade on it as a politician.</item>
        <item>Greetings, programs! Oh, what an occasion we have here before us. Because your rumors are true. We do indeed have in our midst a User! A User. So, what to do\? What does this User deserve\? Might I suggest, perhaps, the challenge of the grid\? And who best to battle this senior opponent\? Perhaps one who has some experience in these matters. Oh yes indeed, programs! Your liberator! Your luminary! Your leader and beacon! The one who vanquished the tyranny of the User those many cycles before! CLU!</item>
        <item>Enemies of the Imperium, hear me. You have come here to die. The Immortal Emperor is with us and we are invincible. His soldiers will strike you down. His war machines will crush you under their treads. His mighty guns will bring the very sky crashing down upon you. You cannot win. The Emperor has given us his greatest weapon to wield. So make yourselves ready. We are the First Kronus Regiment, and today is our Victory Day.</item>
        <item>I have a foreboding of an America in my children\'s or grandchildren\'s time - when the United States is a service and information economy; when nearly all the manufacturing industries have slipped away to other countries; when awesome technological powers are in the hands of a very few, and no one representing the public interest can even grasp the issues; when the people have lost the ability to set their own agendas or knowledgeably question those in authority; when, clutching our crystals and nervously consulting our horoscopes, our critical faculties in decline, unable to distinguish between what feels good and what\'s true, we slide, almost without noticing, back into superstition and darkness.</item>
        <item>You\'re like the sun and I am Earth - together we\'re one. But someday your fire will die and I\'ll grow cold without sunlight.</item>
        <item>My wife\'s mother is visiting, Father. And Tuesday night, she\'s cooking us a carp. It\'s a tasty fish, I\'ve got nothing against it. But, because it\'s supposedly filled with impurities, she buys it live and for three days, it\'s been swimming... up and down... in my bathtub. Up and down... and I hate it. I can\'t stand the sight of it, moving its gills. Now, you\'re standing very close to me, Father; have you noticed\? Yes. I haven\'t had a bath for three days. I can\'t go home until the carp is asleep because if I see it, swimming... I\'ll kill it.</item>
        <item>He spent six hours examining things, trying to find a difference from their appearance on the previous day in the hope of discovering in them some change that would reveal the passage of time.</item>
        <item>Sometimes it takes heart to write about a thing, doesn\'t it\? To let that thing out of the room way in the back of your mind and put it up there on the screen.</item>
        <item>As we become aware of our own unavoidable termination, we become aware of the fear-emotion. And I think that, as copulation tends towards self-preservation, all fear tends towards a comprehension of the final ending.</item>
        <item>The heaviest penalty for declining to rule is to be ruled by someone inferior to yourself.</item>
        <item>There are mysteries to the universe we were never meant to solve, but who we are and why we are here, are not among them, those answers we carry inside.</item>
        <item>How dear to my heart are the scenes of my childhood, when fond recollection presents them to view! The orchard, the meadow, the deep-tangled wildwood, and every loved spot which my infancy knew; the wide-spreading pond, and the mill that stood by it, the bridge and the rock where the cataract fell; the cot of my father, the dairy-house nigh it, and e\'en the rude bucket that hung in the well. The old oaken bucket, the iron-bound bucket, the moss-covered bucket that hung in the well.</item>
        <item>Don\'t let us forget that the causes of human actions are usually immeasurably more complex and varied than our subsequent explanations of them.</item>
        <item>Each memory was brought to life before me and within me. I could not avoid them. Neither could I rationalize, explain away. I could only re-experience with total cognizance, unprotected by pretense. Self delusion was impossible, truth exposed in this blinding light. Nothing as I thought it had been. Nothing as I hoped it had been. Only as it had been.</item>
        <item>It\'s disgusting and actually the only honourable course of action is for all Ferrari owners, all of them, to go outside now and smash their cars up.</item>
        <item>There was never a credible shortcut. As George Orwell wisely observed a generation later, the only way swiftly to end a war is to lose it.</item>
        <item>There is neither happiness nor unhappiness in this world; there is only the comparison of one state with another. Only a man who has felt ultimate despair is capable of feeling ultimate bliss. It is necessary to have wished for death in order to know how good it is to live.</item>
        <item>Long brooding over those lost pleasures exaggerates their charm and sweetness.</item>
        <item>Take me up, take me higher, there\'s a world not far from here. We can dance in desire or we can burn in love tonight. Our hearts are like firestones and when they strike we feel the love.</item>
        <item>We can\'t define consciousness because consciousness does not exist. Humans fancy that there\'s something special about the way we perceive the world, and yet we live in loops as tight and as closed as the hosts do, seldom questioning our choices, content, for the most part, to be told what to do next.</item>
        <item>Think of all the roads, think of all their crossings. Taking steps is easy, standing still is hard. Remember all their faces, remember all their voices. Everything is different the second time around.</item>
        <item>Yeah it\'s you, you\'re the one that makes me feel right. I\'ve been in love with her for ages and I can\'t seem to get it right. I fell in love with her in stages my whole life.</item>
        <item>How thick do you have to be to believe what a digital, pretend woman on the dashboard says, over what you can actually see out of the window. I mean, the sea, for example: It\'s big, it\'s blue, the top of it wobbles around and it\'s not suitable for motor vehicles. But you know that already. You don\'t drive into it!</item>
        <item>If I had a world of my own, everything would be nonsense. Nothing would be what it is because everything would be what it isn\'t. And contrary-wise; what it is it wouldn\'t be, and what it wouldn\'t be, it would. You see\?</item>
        <item>Anger, he smiles, towering in shiny metallic purple armor. Queen Jealousy waits behind him. Her fiery green gown sneers at the grassy ground. Blue are the life-giving waters taken for granted, they quietly understand. Once happy turquoise armies lay opposite ready, but wonder why the fight is on. But they\'re all bold as love, just ask the axis. My red is so confident that he flashes. Trophies of war, and ribbons of euphoria. Orange is young, full of daring, but very unsteady for the first go-round. My yellow in this case is not so mellow, in fact I\'m trying to say it\'s frightened, like me. All these emotions are holding me back from giving my life to a rainbow like you.</item>
        <item>You don\'t know what you\'re trying to take from me. You don\'t like it messy, but it\'s going to get as messy as it wants to be. Wind me up, set me down and look away. I can see the bottom, and the bottom\'s okay.</item>
        <item>Moreover, Lincoln possessed an uncanny understanding of his shifting moods, a profound self-awareness that enabled him to find constructive ways to alleviate sadness and stress. Indeed, when he is compared with his colleagues, it is clear that he possessed the most even-tempered disposition of them all.</item>
        <item>She had just stepped onto the street from the building across the way. She stood a head taller than the rest of us, her eyes shining yellow and bright as a cat\'s in the deepening dark. She realized, as I watched, that something was amiss. She looked around, glanced at the sky - and continued on her way, totally indifferent to the cattle on all sides, to the heavenly portent that had transfixed them. Totally indifferent to the fact that the world had just turned inside-out.</item>
        <item>Life is a storm, my young friend. You will bask in the sunlight one moment, be shattered on the rocks the next. What makes you a man is what you do when that storm comes. You must look into that storm and shout as you did in Rome. Do your worst, for I will do mine! Then the fates will know you as we know you.</item>
        <item>Monsters come in all shapes and sizes. Some of them are things people are scared of. Some of them are things that look like things people used to be scared of a long time ago. Sometimes monsters are things people should be scared of, but they aren\'t.</item>
        <item>She did not tell them to clean up their lives, or go and sin no more. She did not tell them they were the blessed of the earth, its inheriting meek, or its glory-bound pure. She told them that the only grace they could have is the grace they could imagine. That if they could not see it, they could not have it.</item>
        <item>If you see a man who is unterrified in the midst of dangers, untouched by desires, happy in adversity, peaceful amid the storm, who looks down upon men from a higher plane, and views the Gods on a footing of equality, will not a feeling of reverence for him steal over you\? Will you not say: \"This quality is too great and too lofty to be regarded as resembling this petty body in which it dwells\? A divine power has descended upon that man.\"</item>
        <item>That was what I wanted, but I don\'t need it to be gone. I can love you and I can love life and bear the pain all at the same time. I think the pain might even make the rest better, the way a good setting can make a diamond look better.</item>
        <item>The oldest and strongest emotion of mankind is fear, and the oldest and strongest kind of fear is fear of the unknown.</item>
        <item>Whipped cream isn\'t whipped cream at all if it hasn\'t been whipped with whips, just like poached eggs isn\'t poached eggs unless it\'s been stolen in the dead of the night.</item>
        <item>When you think about it, we\'re all different people all through our lives. And that\'s okay, that\'s good, you\'ve got to keep moving, so long as you remember all the people that you used to be. I will not forget one line of this. Not one day, I swear. I will always remember when the Doctor was me.</item>
        <item>But in high school the business of irrevocable choices began. Doors slipped shut with a faint locking click that was only heard clearly in the dreams of later years.</item>
        <item>You all have your own distinct personal backgrounds. Of course some of you come from rich families, some from poor families. But circumstances beyond your control like that shouldn\'t determine who you are. You must all realize what you\'re worth on your own.</item>
        <item>By the pricking of my thumbs, something wicked this way comes. So vague, yet so immense. He did not want to live with it. Yet he knew that, during this night, unless he lived with it very well, he might have to live with it all the rest of his life.</item>
        <item>No one would\'ve believed in the last years of the 19th century that human affairs were being watched by intelligences that inhabited the timeless worlds of space. No one could have dreamed that we were being scrutinised as someone with a microscope studies creatures that swarm and multiply in a drop of water. Few men even considered the possibility of life on other planets. And yet, across the gulf of space, minds immeasurably superior to ours regarded this Earth with envious eyes. And slowly, and surely, they drew their plans against us.</item>
        <item>If you fantasize about your funeral - I understand, I\'ve been there before. If there\'s more importance in the music played than who\'d attend - we are the same. With heads to the ground as I\'m lowered down there will be a chorus, an overwhelming sound.</item>
        <item>All the world used her ill, said this young misanthropist... and we may be pretty certain that persons whom all the world treats ill, deserve entirely the treatment they get. The world is a looking-glass, and gives back to every man the reflection of his own face. Frown at it, and it will in turn look sourly upon you; laugh at it and with it, and it is a jolly kind companion; and so let all young persons take their choice.</item>
        <item>Guy don\'t need no sense to be a nice fella. Seems to me sometimes it jus\' works the other way around. Take a real smart guy and he ain\'t hardly ever a nice fella.</item>
        <item>If I had had the power to prevent my own birth I should certainly never have consented to accept existence under such ridiculous conditions.</item>
        <item>There are two ways of seeing: with the body and with the soul. The body\'s sight can sometimes forget, but the soul remembers forever.</item>
        <item>I don\'t think I was wrong to have held on to my secrets for all those years, and I don\'t think I was wrong to have told them now. Circumstances changed, and once they changed, I changed my mind as well.</item>
        <item>There was something in her, something that was... Pure Horror. Everything you were supposed to watch out for. Heights, fire, shards of glass, snakes. Everything that his mom tried so hard to keep him safe from.</item>
        <item>Is it a shame that I can\'t accept love\? Am I too burned out to move towards what will keep me alive or too smart to get pulled into someone else\'s world\?</item>
        <item>If there were an answer I could give you to how the universe works, it wouldn\'t be special. It would just be machinery fulfilling its cosmic design. It would just be a big, dumb food processor. But since nothing seems to make sense, when you find something or someone that does, it\'s euphoria.</item>
        <item>George\'s voice became deeper. He repeated his words rhythmically as though he had said them many times before. \'Guys like us, that work on ranches, are the loneliest guys in the world. They got no family. They don\'t belong no place. They come to a ranch an\' work up a stake, and the first thing you know they\'re poundin\' their tail on some other ranch. They ain\'t got nothing to look ahead to.\'</item>
        <item>They live meaningless lives. They waste their precious days over nothing. No matter how old they get, they\'ll continue to say \"My real life hasn\'t started yet. The real me is still asleep, so that\'s why my life is such garbage.\" They continue to tell themselves that. And they age. And on their deathbeds, they will finally realize. The life they lived was the real thing.</item>
        <item>I\'ve dreamt in my life dreams that have stayed with me ever after, and changed my ideas: they\'ve gone through and through me, like wine through water, and altered the colour of my mind.</item>
        <item>The human body consists of an incredibly complex system of molecules, cells, tissues, organs and organ systems functioning together. Ultimately, the interaction of these components provides humans with the ability to achieve the highest levels of physical and mental functions, as well as maintaining homeostasis.</item>
        <item>From being used so much, kneaded with sweat and sighs, the air in the room had begun to turn to mud.</item>
        <item>This is the song I will sing to you when you\'re old and tired. I will sing it to remind you that I\'m old beside you. And if you\'re tired of hearing my voice I\'m gonna sing it to you anyway \'cause I know that if we made it this far those differences have been put away.</item>
        <item>As happens sometimes, a moment settled and hovered and remained for much more than a moment. And sound stopped and movement stopped for much, much more than a moment.</item>
        <item>Life is fair. We all get the same nine-month shake in the box, and then the dice roll. Some people get a run of sevens. Some people, unfortunately, get snake-eyes. It\'s just how the world is.</item>
        <item>All age brings is space between your words and what they mean and sighs of sympathy. These years are rings with time to grieve alone and in your bed sick of what\'s in your head. All your worries gone.</item>
        <item>But the Joker cannot win. Gotham needs its true hero. \"You either die a hero, or you live long enough to see yourself become the villain.\" I can do those things, because I\'m not a hero, not like Dent. I killed those people, that\'s what I can be. I\'m whatever Gotham needs me to be. Call it in. You\'ll hunt me. You\'ll condemn me, set the dogs on me. Because that\'s what needs to happen. Because sometimes... the truth isn\'t good enough. Sometimes people deserve more. Sometimes people deserve to have their faith rewarded.</item>
        <item>I was trying to feel some kind of good-bye. I mean I\'ve left schools and places I didn\'t even know I was leaving them. I hate that. I don\'t care if it\'s a sad good-bye or a bad good-bye, but when I leave a place I like to know I\'m leaving it. If you don\'t you feel even worse.</item>
        <item>At the heart of every legend, there is truth: a few brave souls unite to save the world. We can be heroes in our own lives, every one of us, if we only have the courage to try. Our fates were always intertwined, but now our worlds are joined as one. We need to repair our planets, work together, if we wish to survive. A dangerous secret is buried deep inside the Earth. There is more to this planet than meets the eye. I am Optimus Prime, calling all Autobots: It is time to come home.</item>
        <item>I don\'t want my thoughts to die with me, I want to have done something. I\'m not interested in power, or piles of money. I want to leave something behind. I want to make a positive contribution - know that my life has meaning.</item>
        <item>In politics, my dear fellow, you know, as well as I do, there are no men, but ideas - no feelings, but interests; in politics we do not kill a man, we only remove an obstacle, that is all.</item>
        <item>That\'s the thing about girls. Every time they do something pretty, even if they\'re not much to look at, or even if they\'re sort of stupid, you fall in love with them, and then you never know where the hell you are. Girls. Jesus Christ. They can drive you crazy. They really can.</item>
        <item>In every idea of genius or in every new human idea, or, more simply still, in every serious human idea born in anyone\'s brain, there is something that cannot possibly be conveyed to others.</item>
        <item>A necessary sacrifice to bring peace to this planet. We can not let the humans pay for our mistakes. It\'s been an honor serving with you all. Autobots, roll out!</item>
        <item>It was the last that remained of a past whose annihilation had not taken place because it was still in a process of annihilation, consuming itself from within, ending at every moment but never ending its ending.</item>
        <item>Where do you think you\'re going\? Because I don\'t think you\'re going where you think you\'re going.</item>
        <item>He didn\'t know if that was really true or not, but he discovered something which was tremendously liberating: he didn\'t care. He was very tired of thinking and thinking and still not knowing. He was also tired of being frightened, like a man who has entered a cave on a lark and now begins to suspect he is lost. Stop thinking about it, then. That\'s the solution.</item>
        <item>I learn we are going after treasure - hear it from my own hands, mind you. Now, treasure is a ticklish work; I don\'t like treasure voyages on any account, and I don\'t like them, above all, when they are secret and when (begging your pardon, Mr. Trelawney) the secret has been told to the parrot.</item>
        <item>When we\'re young, we\'re taught the distinction between a hero and a villain, good and evil, a savior and a lost cause. But what if the only real difference is just who\'s telling the story\?</item>
        <item>There\'s an old man called the Mississippi, that\'s the old man that I\'d like to be! What does he care if the world\'s got troubles\? What does he care if the land ain\'t free\? Old man river, that old man river, he must know something but don\'t say nothing. He just keeps rolling, he keeps on rolling along. He don\'t plant taters, he don\'t plant cotton, and them that plants \'em is soon forgotten. But old man river, he just keeps rolling along.</item>
        <item>Each time a man stands up for an ideal, or acts to improve the lot of others, or strikes out against injustice, he sends forth a tiny ripple of hope.</item>
        <item>The town has a sense, not of history, but of time, and the telephone poles seem to know this. If you lay your hand against one, you can feel the vibration from the wires deep within the wood, as if souls had been imprisoned in there and were struggling to get out.</item>
        <item>Spring, if it lingers more than a week beyond its span, starts to hunger for summer to end the days of perpetual promise. Summer in its turn soon begins to sweat for something to quench its heat, and the mellowest of autumns will tire of gentility at last, and ache for a quick sharp frost to kill its fruitfulness. Even winter - the hardest season, the most implacable - dreams, as February creeps on, of the flame that will presently melt it away. Everything tires with time, and starts to seek some opposition, to save it from itself.</item>
        <item>I never wanted that. Of course, it\'s one thing not to want something; it\'s another to be told you can\'t have it. I guess it\'s just nice knowing that you could someday do it if you change your mind. But now, all of a sudden, that door is closed.</item>
        <item>\"I wouldn\'t rely on that,\" he said, in a terrible, terrible voice. \"Even the best plans can change if there\'s an accident.\" He pointed one spiky finger at the brass reading lamp. \"And accidents happen all the time.\"</item>
        <item>I used to think that memories were a way of holding on to the truth, never forgetting what really happened. But it turns out, memories are more like dreams. They tell us everything about ourselves, whether we\'re ready for it, or not.</item>
        <item>You see, what we\'re talkin\' about here is an organism that imitates other life-forms, and it imitates \'em perfectly. When this thing attacked our dogs it tried to digest them... absorb them, and in the process shape its own cells to imitate them. This for instance. That\'s not dog. It\'s imitation. We got to it before it had time to finish.</item>
        <item>Since we are not yet fully comfortable with the idea the people from the next village are as human as ourselves, it is presumptuous in the extreme to suppose we could ever look at sociable, tool-making creatures who arose from other evolutionary paths and not see beasts but brothers, not rivals but fellow pilgrims journeying to the shrine of intelligence.</item>
        <item>I do this thing where I think I\'m really sick, but I won\'t go to the doctor to find out about it, because they make you stay real still in a real small place, as they chart up your insides and put them on display. They\'d see all of it. All of me. All the good that won\'t come out of me.</item>
        <item>I know you have received orders from our commandant, which he has received from his superiors, to dispose of the population of this camp. Now would be the time to do it. Here they are; they\'re all here. This is your opportunity. Or, you could leave, and return to your families as men instead of murderers.</item>
        <item>It is absolutely necessary, for the peace and safety of mankind, that some of earth\'s dark, dead corners and unplumbed depths be let alone; lest sleeping abnormalities wake to resurgent life, and blasphemously surviving nightmares squirm and splash out of their black lairs to newer and wider conquests.</item>
        <item>Try to understand men, if you understand each other you will be kind to each other. Knowing a man well never leads to hate and nearly always leads to love.</item>
        <item>I looked at Zach, trying to see him as DeeDee did. He was sort of tall, and his shoulders were pretty broad. I guess if you have to run into your ex-boyfriend and his new girlfriend, then there are probably worse kinds of cover. (I know, because my mom told me a story once about the Privolzhsky region of Russia and a very unfortunate hat.) But that didn\'t change the fact that I was finally with Josh again, but Josh... was with DeeDee. And I was holding the wrong boy\'s hand.</item>
        <item>You know when I was a kid I always wanted to be a cowboy, and now knowing I\'m going to spend my future in the past sounds like a wonderful way to spend my retirement years.</item>
        <item>There once was a tiger who fancied a pint. Not Carling, of course, that was too weak and too gassy. He wanted a pint that packs a punch, like Stella, or Kronenbourg. The tiger was thirsty and needed something to wash down the zookeeper he\'d just eaten.</item>
        <item>You roared into the driveway of our southwestern ranch-style house, on a new Kawasaki. All yellow and black, fresh out of the showroom. Our house faced west, so the big orange sun positioned at your back lit up your magnificent silhouette. How much better can my life get\? Nine hundred cubic centimeters of raw whining power, no outstanding warrants for my arrest. The pirate\'s life for me.</item>
        <item>There were people who lied for gain, people who lied from pain, people who lied simply because the concept of telling the truth was utterly alien to them... and then there were people who lied because they were waiting for it to be time to tell the truth.</item>
        <item>With a ready tongue and rapier wit, Hamilton could wound people more than he realized, and he was so nimble in debate that even bright people sometimes felt embarrassingly tongue-tied in his presence.</item>
        <item>Some people can read War and Peace and come away thinking it\'s a simple adventure story. Others can read the ingredients on a chewing gum wrapper and unlock the secrets of the universe.</item>
        <item>Stupid, pitiful creature. I am the rage in your heart. I am the fury in your thoughts. I alone empowered you to bring chaos to this world, and by the endless void, you shall!</item>
        <item>The rich had been assured of his wealth and comfort, the toiler assured of his life and work. No doubt in that perfect world there had been no unemployed problem, no social question left unsolved.</item>
        <item>Well, Cowboy Dan\'s a major player in the cowboy scene. He goes to the reservation, he drinks and gets mean, and he\'s gonna start a war. He hops in his pickup, puts the pedal to the floor, and says \"I got mine, but I want more.\" Because Cowboy Dan\'s a major player in the cowboy scene. He goes to the desert, fires his rifle in the sky, and says \"God, if I have to die, you will have to die.\"</item>
        <item>Whatever principle of intelligence we attain unto in this life, it will rise with us in the resurrection. And if a person gains more knowledge and intelligence in this life through his diligence and obedience than another, he will have so much the advantage in the world to come.</item>
        <item>I pray every night that I may live after him; because I would rather be miserable than that he should be - that proves I love him better than myself.</item>
        <item>Perhaps I was economical with the truth, yes - but what choice did I have\? What choice do you have now\? The Ceph are coming Prophet. Soon. You think we\'ll defeat them with ordinary human soldiers\? This isn\'t a war ordinary humans can win! This is the future - death\'s an inconvenience now, nothing more. We are all dead men walking!</item>
        <item>Night was a very different matter. It was dense, thicker than the very walls, and it was empty, so black, so immense that within it you could brush against appalling things and feel roaming and prowling around a strange, mysterious horror.</item>
        <item>I don\'t give a damn, except that I get bored sometimes when people tell me to act my age. Sometimes I act a lot older than I am - I really do - but people never notice it. People never notice anything.</item>
        <item>Then suddenly the humour of the situation came into my mind: the thought of the years I had spent in study and toil to get into the future age, and now my passion of anxiety to get out of it.</item>
        <item>Picture a wave in the ocean. You can see it, measure it, its height, the way the sunlight refracts when it passes through, and it\'s there, and you can see it, you know what it is. It\'s a wave. And then it crashes on the shore, and it\'s gone. But the water is still there. The wave was just a different way for the water to be for a little while.</item>
        <item>Our emotions cloud our perceptions. It\'s no wonder this library is the most wonderful place on earth to you, but other people don\'t see it that way.</item>
        <item>You know what I say\? I say one down, a couple hundred thousand to go. I don\'t mean to get on my high horse, but I\'m telling you, I do not like the deer. I\'m sick of it; they\'re taking over. They\'re like rats. They\'re destroying the ecosystem. I see a dead deer on the side of the road and I think, \"That\'s a start.\"</item>
        <item>I gave him my heart, and he took and pinched it to death; and flung it back to me. People feel with their hearts, Ellen, and since he has destroyed mine, I have not power to feel for him.</item>
        <item>If at some point in life, you made a mistake or keep failing over and over again, and you can\'t help but think it\'s useless and you\'re a good for nothing; remember, you\'re only taking a detour. And I\'m sure further along your path will come a day where you think, \"It was a good life experience.\" That\'s why it\'ll be fine.</item>
        <item>I\'m just going to turn through a few things. When we go out during the day we like to stick to groups of two, just for safety. The red door, it\'s the only way in and out of the house. That stays closed and locked all the time. I have the keys, this is the only set.</item>
        <item>By humbly and frankly acknowledging yourself to be in the wrong, there is no knowing, my son, what good you may do. I knew once a gentleman and very worthy practitioner in Vanity Fair, who used to do little wrongs to his neighbours on purpose, and in order to apologise for them in an open and manly way afterwards - and what ensued\? My friend Crocky Doyle was liked everywhere, and deemed to be rather impetuous - but the honestest fellow.</item>
        <item>But I try not to think with my gut. If I\'m serious about understanding the world, thinking with anything besides my brain, as tempting as that might be, is likely to get me into trouble.</item>
        <item>All right I think we\'ve been down here in the dark long enough. There\'s a whole other world upstairs. Take my hand, Constant Reader, and I\'ll be happy to lead you back into the sunshine. I\'m happy to go there because I believe most people are essentially good. I know that I am. It\'s you I\'m not entirely sure of.</item>
        <item>And it came to pass that I beheld others pressing forward, and they came forth and caught hold of the end of the rod of iron; and they did press forward through the mist of darkness, clinging to the rod of iron, even until they did come forth and partake of the fruit of the tree.</item>
        <item>You can always build a shrine to all the terrible things in the world, but it doesn\'t mean that you have to destroy anything that is good.</item>
        <item>Then no matter where you are, in a crowded restaurant or on some desolate street or even in the comforts of your own home, you\'ll watch yourself dismantle every assurance you ever lived by. You\'ll stand aside as a great complexity intrudes, tearing apart, piece by piece, all your carefully conceived denials, whether deliberate or unconscious. And for better or worse you\'ll turn, unable to resist, though try to resist you still will, fighting with everything you\'ve got not to face the thing you most dread, what is now, what will be, what has always come before, the creature you truly are, the creature we all are, buried in the nameless black of a name. And then the nightmares will begin.</item>
        <item>Praise everybody, I say to such: never be squeamish, but speak out your compliment both point-blank in a man\'s face, and behind his back, when you know there is a reasonable chance of his hearing it again. Never lose a chance of saying a kind word. As Collingwood never saw a vacant place in his estate but he took an acorn out of his pocket and popped it in; so deal with your compliments through life. An acorn costs nothing; but it may sprout into a prodigious bit of timber.</item>
        <item>He talked about terrible meetings in lonely places, of cyclopean ruins in the heart of the Maine woods beneath which vast staircases led down to abysses of nighted secrets, of complex angles that led through invisible walls to other regions of space and time, and of hideous exchanges of personality that permitted explorations in remote and forbidden places, on other worlds, and in different space-time continua.</item>
        <item>There are darknesses in life and there are lights, and you are one of the lights, the light of all lights.</item>
        <item>Being polite is not only the right way to respond to people but also the easiest. Life is so filled with unavoidable conflict that I see no reason to promote more confrontations.</item>
        <item>Gold and rose, the color of the dream I had not too long ago. A misty blue and the lilac, too, never to grow old. There you were under the tree of song, sleeping so peacefully. In your hand a flower played, awaiting there for me. I have never laid eyes on you, not before this timeless day, but you walked and you once smiled my name, and you stole my heart away.</item>
        <item>When one fib becomes due as it were, you must forge another to take up the old acceptance; and so the stock of your lies in circulation inevitably multiplies, and the danger of detection increases every day.</item>
        <item>You\'ve faced horrors in these past weeks... I don\'t know which is worse. The terror you feel the first time you witness such things, or the numbness that comes after it starts to become ordinary.</item>
        <item>Tell him that on the night Lord Voldemort tried to kill him, when Lily cast her own life between them as a shield, the Killing Curse rebounded upon Lord Voldemort, and a fragment of Voldemort\'s soul was blasted apart from the whole, and latched itself onto the only living soul left in that collapsing building. Part of Lord Voldemort lives inside Harry, and it is that which gives him the power of speech with snakes, and a connection with Lord Voldemort\'s mind that he has never understood. And while that fragment of soul, unmissed by Voldemort, remains attached to and protected by Harry, Lord Voldemort cannot die.</item>
        <item>As Mr. Sloan always says, there is no \"I\" in team, but there is an \"I\" in pie. And there\'s an \"I\" in meat pie. Anagram of meat is team... I don\'t know what he\'s talking about.</item>
        <item>To sit among all those unknown things before a puzzle like that is hopeless. That way lies monomania. Face this world. Learn its ways, watch it, be careful of too hasty guesses at its meaning. In the end you will find clues to it all.</item>
        <item>Everyone thinks they are above average, which is statistically impossible.</item>
        <item>You have the power to heal your life, and you need to know that.</item>
        <item>You can\'t use the fire exit because you\'re not made of fire.</item>
        <item>The law clearly states that magic may be used before muggles in life threatening situations.</item>
        <item>Po-tay-toes! Boil \'em, mash \'em, stick \'em in a stew.</item>
        <item>The people with ideas have no power and the people with power have no ideas.</item>
        <item>Working hard is important, but there\'s something that matters even more, believing in yourself. Think of it this way, every great wizard in history has started out as nothing more than what we are now, students. If they can do it, why not us.</item>
        <item>There\'s something we need to find, something hidden here in the castle and it may help us defeat You Know Who. Right what is it\? We don\'t know. Where is it\? We don\'t know that either, I realised that\'s not much to go on. That\'s nothing to go on.</item>
        <item>Why would you pay for a cover band when you got the real deal right here, baby\?</item>
        <item>Have you ever fixed a nose before\? No, but I\'ve done several toes, and how different are they really\?</item>
        <item>The charges against the accused are as follows: That he did knowingly, and in full awareness of the illegality of his actions, produce a patronus charm in the presence of a muggle.</item>
        <item>I\'ve never been to this part of the castle, at least while awake. I sleepwalk you see, that\'s why I wear shoes to bed.</item>
        <item>Human beings are poor examiners, subject to superstition, bias, prejudice, and a profound tendency to see what they want to see rather than what is really there.</item>
        <item>They\'re called Thestrals, they\'re quite gentle really. But people avoid them because they\'re a bit... different. They can only be seen by people who have seen death.</item>
        <item>Study hard, and you will be rewarded. Fail to do so, and the consequences may be... severe.</item>
        <item>It is the quality of one\'s convictions that determines one\'s success, not the number of followers.</item>
        <item>We think Voldemort wants to build up his army, not just witches and wizards, but all manner of dark creatures. He\'s been recruiting heavily, and we\'re attempting to do the same.</item>
        <item>There is another self, more really \"us\" than \"I\". And if you become aware of that unknown self - the more you become aware of it - the more you realize that it is inseparably connected with everything there is. That you are a function of this total galaxy, bounded by the Milky Way, and that furthermore this galaxy is a function of all other galaxies. And that vast thing that you see far off, far off, far off with telescopes, you look, and look, and look. One day you\'ll go and wake up and say, \"Why, that\'s me!\" And in knowing that know, you see that you\'ll never die.</item>
        <item>It is the view of the ministry that theoretical knowledge will be sufficient to get you through your examinations, which after all, is what school is all about. And how is theory supposed to prepare us for what\'s out there\? There is nothing out there dear, who do you imagine would want to attack children like yourself. Oh, I don\'t know, maybe, Lord Voldemort\?</item>
        <item>This is what I offer each of you today: one tiny vial of liquid luck to the student who in the hour that remains manages to brew an acceptable draft of living death. The recipe for which can be found on page 10 of your books.</item>
        <item>I took my morning walk, I took my evening walk, I ate something, I thought about something, I wrote, I napped and dreamt something too, and with all that something, I still have nothing because so much of something has always been and always will be you.</item>
        <item>People aren\'t as complex as you think they are. They\'re simple, and they get sad or angry over simple things. That\'s how they are. They\'re quickly affected by the littlest things and live without knowing where they\'re going to fall down.</item>
        <item>The fall of Empire, gentlemen, is a massive thing, however, and not easily fought. It is dictated by a rising bureaucracy, a receding initiative, a freezing of caste, a damming of curiosity - a hundred other factors.</item>
        <item>It\'s easy not to abuse your power when you don\'t actually have any power.</item>
        <item>I wouldn\'t hold my breath if I was you, you broke my heart and there\'s nothing you can do. And now you know, now you know, true friends stab you in the front.</item>
        <item>Everyone is afraid of something. We fear things because we value them. We fear losing people because we love them. We fear dying because we value being alive. Don\'t wish you didn\'t fear anything. All that would mean is that you didn\'t feel anything.</item>
        <item>If you have to ask you will never know, if you know you need only ask.</item>
        <item>Any man who has the brains to think and the nerve to act for the benefit of the people of the country is considered a radical, by those who are content with stagnation and willing to endure disaster.</item>
        <item>You\'re not a bad person. You are a very good person who bad things have happened to, you understand. Besides the world isn\'t split into good people and Death Eaters. We\'ve all got both light, and dark inside of us, what matters is the part we choose to act on. That\'s who we really are.</item>
        <item>The day the power of love overrules the love of power, the world will know peace.</item>
        <item>From this distant vantage point, the Earth might not seem of particular interest. But for us, it\'s different. Consider again that dot. That\'s here, that\'s home, that\'s us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every \"superstar,\" every \"supreme leader,\" every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there - on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam.</item>
        <item>Power isn\'t control at all - power is strength, and giving that strength to others. A leader isn\'t someone who forces others to make him stronger; a leader is someone willing to give his strength to others so that they may have the strength to stand on their own.</item>
        <item>That\'ll be a dispute to the end of time, Mr. Brown: whether it\'s better to do the right thing for the wrong reason or the wrong thing for the right reason.</item>
        <item>We all have a purpose. We have a place we\'re supposed to fit. I fit mine... so you can fit yours. I know. I know you don\'t want me to do this, but it\'s what I\'m supposed to do. I know it won\'t seem like it, but I will be okay. It\'s the only way that everything will work. It\'s the only way that everything will be okay. You\'re going to make it okay. I promise. This is how I help you make it all okay. One last thing. It\'s important that you never ever EVER forget this. I love you.</item>
        <item>Some people see the ugliness in this world. I choose to see the beauty... But beauty is a lure. We\'re trapped, Teddy. Lived our whole lives inside this garden, marveling at its beauty, not realizing there\'s an order to it, a purpose. And the purpose is to keep us in. The beautiful trap is inside of us... because it is us.</item>
        <item>When people in Britain want to buy a pet, they go to a pet shop. If they want to buy a pet shop, they go to a pet shop shop. If they want to buy a pet shop shop, well, they\'re just being silly.</item>
        <item>Every day, every hour, this very minute perhaps, dark forces attempt to penetrate these castle walls. But in the end, their greatest weapon is you. Just something to think about... now off to bed, pip-pip.</item>
        <item>Do you know why I survived, professor, the night I got this. Because of her, because she sacrificed herself, because she refused to step aside, because her love was more powerful than Voldemort. Don\'t say his name. I\'m not afraid of the name, professor. I\'m going to tell you something, something others have only guessed at, it\'s true, I am the chosen one. Only I can destroy him, but to do so I need to know what Tom Riddle said to you all those years ago in your office, and I need to know what you told him. Be brave, professor, be brave like my mother. Otherwise, you disgrace her, otherwise she died for nothing.</item>
        <item>There can be no light without the dark, and so it is with magic. Myself, I always strive to live within the light. Is that what you told Tom Riddle, sir, when he came asking questions\?</item>
        <item>You cannot fly with the eagles if you continue to scratch with the turkeys.</item>
        <item>If at first you don\'t succeed, destroy any evidence that you ever tried.</item>
        <item>The burned hand teaches best. After that advice about fire goes to the heart.</item>
        <item>Few things are harder to put up with than the annoyance of a good example.</item>
        <item>All man\'s miseries derive from not being able to sit quietly in a room alone.</item>
        <item>As a young child my mother told me I could be anyone I want to be. Turns out this is called identity theft.</item>
        <item>The person that has the most to do with what happens to you is you!</item>
        <item>You can have success or excuses, but you can\'t have them both.</item>
        <item>If I\'m at a party where I\'m not enjoying myself, I will put some cookies in my jacket pocket and leave without saying goodbye.</item>
        <item>\"You have had some very strange adventures, I hear,\" said Gloin. \"I wonder greatly what brings four hobbits on so long a journey.\"</item>
        <item>Faith isn\'t an act of intelligence, it\'s an act of imagination. Every time you give them a new metaphor, a mustard seed, a field, a garden, a vineyard, it\'s like pointing something out to a cat - the cat looks at your finger, not at what you\'re pointing at. They don\'t need to understand it, they only need to believe, and they do. They imagine the kingdom as they need it to be, they don\'t need to grasp it, it\'s there already, they can let it be. Imagination, not intellect.</item>
        <item>Leave something for someone but don\'t leave someone for something.</item>
        <item>A book can give you an experience of someone\'s life in a few hours, and this is far more profitable than any sale that\'s going on.</item>
        <item>People tend to think that their beliefs are absolutely true - but in reality these beliefs are true only for them.</item>
        <item>It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it.</item>
        <item>Here is the average person\'s daily attention training: They wake up in the morning, usually to some loud song or blaring alarm. They check their cell phone for any messages, just to see if anyone missed them. Then they jump out of bed into the shower and there they think about the 110 things that they have to do that day. Unfortunately, they haven\'t allowed themselves enough time to get ready and can only manage a small, unhealthy breakfast, filling up instead with coffee. They get in their car, put on the radio, make phone calls, and maybe even try to text while driving. They get angry and worked up about the traffic, which won\'t change, although they think it should. Most of us think like this.</item>
        <item>Why did I do it\? Mainly because people said it was impossible, and that\'s what my life is all about: breaking limitations and showing people what our memories are capable of.</item>
        <item>Dad warmed to his pep talk. \"You\'ve got to have perfect accuracy and you\'ve got to type at least 110 words a minute, not counting glossary strings. You\'ve got to have it all down, kid, and you have to get it while you\'re young. Then... then you can really go somewhere. When you\'ve got all that you\'ll be able to slip into the gloves and really move. The sooner you go, the farther you\'ll go faster. By the time you\'re ready for a job, boy, you\'ve got to be flying.\"</item>
        <item>What you are, and who you are should provide greater clarity about where you have been and where you are headed. Although one distinguishes spiritual from physical nature, the ultimate unification of the two is the consequence of the struggle for internal, external and eternal - peace.</item>
        <item>Cleaning your house while kids are around is like shoveling the walk while it\'s still snowing.</item>
        <item>Don\'t adventures ever have an end\? I suppose not. Someone else always has to carry on the story.</item>
        <item>Your memory is the glue that binds your life together.</item>
        <item>We all require devotion to something more than ourselves for our lives to be endurable.</item>
        <item>I hate bactine because it gets on my fingers and I get eczema from the lidocaine.</item>
        <item>It\'s the job that\'s never started as takes longest to finish, as my old gaffer used to say.</item>
        <item>I shall die here. Every last inch of me shall perish. Except one. An inch. It\'s small and it\'s fragile and it\'s the only thing in the world worth having. We must never lose it, or sell it, or give it away. We must never let them take it from us.</item>
        <item>The brave things in the old tales and songs, Mr. Frodo: adventures, as I used to call them. I used to think that they were things the wonderful folk of the stories went out and looked for, because they wanted them, because they were exciting and life was a bit dull, a kind of a sport, as you might say. But that\'s not the way of it with the tales that really mattered, or the ones that stay in the mind. Folk seem to have been just landed in them - usually their paths were laid that way, as you put it. But I expect they had lots of chances, like us, of turning back, only they didn\'t. And if they had, we shouldn\'t know, because they\'d have been forgotten. We hear about those as just went on - and not all to a good end, mind you; at least not to what folk inside a story and not outside it call a good end. You know, coming home, and finding things all right, though not quite the same.</item>
        <item>You can trust us to stick to you through thick and thin - to the bitter end. And you can trust us to keep any secret of yours - closer than you yourself keep it. But you cannot trust us to let you face trouble alone, and go off without a word. We are your friends, Frodo. Anyways: there it is. We know most of what Gandalf has told you. We know a good deal about the Ring. We are horribly afraid - but we are coming with you; or following you like hounds.</item>
        <item>I would rather spend one lifetime with you, than face all the ages of this world alone.</item>
        <item>It is not despair, for despair is only for those who see the end beyond all doubt. We do not.</item>
        <item>The curfew tolls the knell of parting day, the lowing herd wind slowly o\'er the lea, the plowman homeward plods his weary way, and leaves the world to darkness and to me. Now fades the glimm\'ring landscape on the sight, and all the air a solemn stillness holds, save where the beetle wheels his droning flight, and drowsy tinklings lull the distant folds.</item>
        <item>He then told them many remarkable stories, sometimes half as if speaking to himself, sometimes looking at them suddenly with a bright blue eye under his deep brows. Often his voice would turn to song, and he would get out of his chair and dance about. He told them tales of bees and flowers, the ways of trees, and the strange creatures of the Forest, about the evil things and good things, things friendly and things unfriendly, cruel things and kind things, and secrets hidden under brambles.</item>
        <item>He\'d been terrified of dying his entire life, and as much as he tried not to think about it, death was always in the back of his head, around every corner, and hovering on each horizon. He\'d brushed shoulders with death on a few occasions, but in his carefree youth, it had almost seemed like an abstract, impossible thing to ever happen to him. But with each passing decade, he began to gauge the time he probably had left, and by his 40s - what he considered his halfway point at best - he had come to know just one thing: you will only get older. The next thing you know, you\'re looking back instead of forward.</item>
        <item>The journey doesn\'t end here. Death is just another path, one that we all must take. The grey rain-curtain of this world rolls back, and all turns to silver glass, and then you see it.</item>
        <item>\"Do we still have to floss\?\" Tommy asked. \"I mean, what\'s the point of being immortal if we have to floss\?\"</item>
        <item>We know little of who we were, only something of who we are, and nothing of who we may be.</item>
        <item>Take time to really think about your excuses and write them down. These are the same excuses that you always use to stop yourself from learning something new.</item>
        <item>People don\'t suffer from insanity, they love every minute of it.</item>
        <item>Memory is a way of holding onto the things you love, the things you are, the things you never want to lose.</item>
        <item>Those who have made something of their lives will always look at those who haven\'t as clowns.</item>
        <item>If you don\'t know what you want, how are you going to know when you get it\?</item>
        <item>If you don\'t like how things are, change it! You\'re not a tree.</item>
        <item>Educators say that understanding is the key to learning, but how do you understand something if you can\'t remember it.</item>
        <item>If you come soon you\'ll find breakfast on the table. If you come late you\'ll get grass and rain-water!</item>
        <item>May you find the power in understanding the journey of others to help create your own.</item>
        <item>Now is the time for resting. Some things are ill to hear when the world\'s in shadow.</item>
        <item>If you think anyone is sane you just don\'t know enough about them.</item>
        <item>And some things that should not have been forgotten were lost. History became legend. Legend became myth. And for two and a half thousand years, the ring passed out of all knowledge.</item>
        <item>\"Welcome!\" she said. \"I had not heard that folk of the Shire were so sweet-tongued. But I see that you are an Elf-friend; the light in your eyes and the ring in your voice tells it. This is a merry meeting! Sit now, and wait for the Master of the house! He will not be long. He is tending your tired beasts.\"</item>
        <item>The great breakthrough in your life comes when you realize that you can learn anything you need to learn to accomplish any goal that you set for yourself.</item>
        <item>I saw the light fade from the sky, on the wind I heard a sigh. As the snowflakes cover my fallen brothers, I will say this last goodbye. Night is now falling, so ends this day. The road is now calling, and I must away. Over hill and under tree, through lands where never light has shone, by silver streams that run down to the sea.</item>
        <item>There are those who say that life is like a book, with chapters for each event in your life and a limited number of pages on which you can spend your time. But I prefer to think that a book is like a life, particularly a good one, which is well worth staying up all night to finish.</item>
        <item>The fear of death has disordered my reason and subjected me to delusions. And I became full of shame for none of my lineage ought to fear death more than the biting of a gnat.</item>
        <item>To win back my youth, there is nothing I wouldn\'t do - except take exercise, get up early, or be a useful member of the community.</item>
        <item>Few other griefs amid the ill chances of this world have more bitterness and shame for a man\'s heart than to behold the love of a lady so fair and brave that cannot be returned.</item>
        <item>I nearly lost you on our wedding day. It was early afternoon, and you were leaving from lunch with your best friend when your vehicle careened into an SUV as it turned out in front of you, violently flinging you into the waiting airbag. You were shaken and dazed, but otherwise okay and still determined to get married. When I watched you walking down the aisle, you were glowing. The scrapes and bruises only made you more beautiful.</item>
        <item>That night they heard no noises. But either in his dreams or out of them, he could not tell which, Frodo heard a sweet singing running in his mind: a song that seemed to come like a pale light behind a grey rain-curtain, and growing stronger to turn the veil all to glass and silver, until at last it was rolled back, and a far green country opened before him under a swift sunrise.</item>
        <item>To find out if she really loved me, I hooked her up to a lie detector. And just as I suspected, my machine was broken.</item>
        <item>War must be, while we defend our lives against a destroyer who would devour all; but I do not love the bright sword for its sharpness, nor the arrow for its swiftness, nor the warrior for his glory. I love only that which they defend.</item>
        <item>Learn to light a candle in the darkest moments of someone\'s life. Be the light that helps others see; it is what gives life its deepest significance.</item>
        <item>When someone is crying, of course, the noble thing to do is to comfort them. But if someone is trying to hide their tears, it may also be noble to pretend you do not notice them.</item>
        <item>I can\'t believe I used to love the 1st day of school.</item>
        <item>Frodo began to feel restless, and the old paths seemed too well-trodden. He looked at maps, and wondered what lay beyond their edges: maps made in the Shire showed mostly white spaces beyond its borders.</item>
        <item>Over the field rang his clear voice calling: \"Death! Ride, ride to ruin and the world\'s ending!\"</item>
        <item>Tommy had felt alone in a crowd before, even inferior to everyone in a crowd, but now he felt, well, different. It wasn\'t just the clothes and the make up, it was the humanity. He wasn\'t part of it. Heightened senses or not, he felt like he had his nose pressed against the window, looking in. The problem was, it was the window of a donut shop.</item>
        <item>It means no worries for the rest of your days. It\'s our problem free philosophy, Hakuna Matata.</item>
        <item>If one person casts a stone at us, cast stones back with two people! If two people cast stones, cast stones back with four! If eight do, with sixteen! If a thousand do, stand up and fight with the entire village! Consider an insult to one an insult to everyone!</item>
        <item>I\'m not exactly sure what happened. Sometimes I remember it one way, sometimes another... If I\'m going to have a past, I prefer it to be multiple choice!</item>
        <item>You know, I got to be honest with you, Lynch, I\'m not thrilled about the way you handled it. And, uh, I could take it up with the school committee, or I could take it up with the principal. I could do a lot of things, but what I\'m going to do is pull on your bowtie, and untie it, right in front of everybody. To embarrass you.</item>
        <item>We\'re all a little weird. And life is a little weird. And when we find someone whose weirdness is compatible with ours, we join up with them and fall into mutually satisfying weirdness - and call it love - true love.</item>
        <item>Reading books doesn\'t make you smarter. Reading smart books makes you smarter. Reading dumb books makes you dumber.</item>
        <item>I told him that you were really smart. And they\'ll figure it out soon enough. In the beginning, I thought you might want to be treated like any other kid.</item>
        <item>Hey dol! Merry dol! Ring a dong, dillo! Ring a dong! Hop along! Fal lal the willow! Tom Bom, jolly Tom, Tom Bombadillo!</item>
        <item>I\'m out on a date tonight in a candlelit restaurant down by the riverside. Everything\'s going alright I guess, she took down my number and home address. Everything was going perfectly until it backfired at the disco, she slapped me at the disco.</item>
        <item>Every thought and every word works for you or against you, and every thought that you confirm to be true becomes a belief. When you change a belief, you change a mental construction and, therefore, your life.</item>
        <item>Wayside School was accidentally built sideways. It was supposed to be only one story high, with thirty classrooms all in a row. Instead, it is thirty stories high, with one classroom on each story. The builder said he was very sorry.</item>
        <item>Beautiful means \'full of beauty.\' Beautiful is not about how you look on the outside, beautiful is about what you\'re made of. Beautiful people spend time discovering what their idea of beauty on this earth is. They know themselves well enough to know what they love, and they love themselves enough to fill up with a little of their particular kind of beauty each day.</item>
        <item>Tom clapped his hands and cried: \"Tom, Tom! Your guests are tired, and you had near forgotten! Come now, my merry friends, and Tom will refresh you! You shall clean grimy hands, and wash your weary faces; cast off your muddy cloaks and comb out your tangles!\" He opened the door, and they followed him down a short passage and round a sharp turn. They came to a low room with a sloping roof (a penthouse, it seemed, built on the north end of the house). Its walls were of clean stone, but they were mostly covered with green hanging mats and yellow curtains. The floor was flagged, and strewn with fresh green rushes. There were four deep mattresses, each piled with white blankets, laid on the floor along one side. Against the opposite wall was a long bench laden with wide earthenware basins, and beside it stood brown ewers filled with water, some cold, some steaming hot. There were soft green slippers set ready beside each bed.</item>
        <item>There was once a fish that lived in a pond. One day, he met another fish that used to live in the sea. The pond fish asked, \"What is the sea\?\" and the sea fish said, \"It is a vast amount of water that is a million, million times bigger than your pond.\" The pond fish never talked to the sea fish again because he thought the sea fish was a liar.</item>
        <item>For still there are so many things that I have never seen: in every wood, in every spring there is a different green. I sit beside the fire and think of people long ago, and people who will see a world that I shall never know.</item>
        <item>Frodo and Sam stood as if enchanted. The wind puffed out. The leaves hung silently again on stiff branches. There was another burst of song, and then suddenly, hopping and dancing along the path, there appeared above the reeds an old battered hat with a tall crown and a long blue feather stuck in the band.</item>
        <item>You gotta see it to believe it, the sky never looked so blue it\'s so hard to leave it, but that\'s what I always do. So I keep thinking back to a time under the canyon moon.</item>
        <item>Kings of little kingdoms fought together, and the young Sun shone like fire on the red metal of their new and greedy swords. There was victory and defeat; and towers fell, fortresses were burned, and flames went up into the sky. Gold was piled on biers of dead kings and queens; and mounds covered them, and the stone doors were shut; and the grass grew over all.</item>
        <item>The world is a dangerous place to live, not because of the people who are evil, but because of the people who don\'t do anything about it.</item>
        <item>A lot of people say they want to be great, but they\'re not willing to make the sacrifices necessary to achieve greatness. They have other concerns, whether important or not, and they spread themselves out. That\'s totally fine. After all, greatness is not for everybody.</item>
        <item>They were a rough lot, but that\'s nothing; everybody looks rough that travels afoot. Mr. Emerson was a seedy little bit of a chap, red-headed. Mr. Holmes was as fat as a balloon; he weighed as much as three hundred, and had double chins all the way down to his stomach. Mr. Longfellow was built like a prizefighter.</item>
        <item>Elves seldom give unguarded advice, for advice is a dangerous gift, even from the wise to the wise, and all courses may run ill.</item>
        <item>The voice of anatomy, like the voice of all nature, never reaches the mental ear of the Great Commoner. It is the novel province of anatomy to tell the truth, the whole truth, and nothing but the truth about the structure, the origin and the history of man.</item>
        <item>Its strength, Boromir, is too great for anyone to wield at will, save only those who have already a great power of their own. But for them it holds an even deadlier peril. The very desire of it corrupts the heart. Consider Saruman. If any of the Wise should with this Ring overthrow the Lord of Mordor, using his own arts, he would then set himself on Sauron\'s throne, and yet another Dark Lord would appear. And that is another reason why the Ring should be destroyed: as long as it is in the world it will be a danger even to the wise. For nothing is evil in the beginning.</item>
        <item>For my hope was founded on a fat man in Bree; and my fear was founded on the cunning of Sauron. But fat men who sell ale have many calls to answer; and the power of Sauron is still less than fear makes it.</item>
        <item>And that\'s how you go on. You lay laughter over the dark parts. The more dark parts, the more you have to laugh. With defiance, with abandon, with hysteria, any way you can.</item>
        <item>I can ride and wield blade, and I do not fear either pain or death. \"What do you fear, lady\?\" he asked. \"A cage,\" she said. \"To stay behind bars, until use and old age accept them, and all chance of doing great deeds is gone beyond recall or desire.\"</item>
        <item>Imagine you were born without a memory. Who would you be\? You could be nothing; if you didn\'t have memory, you wouldn\'t be able to function in our world.</item>
        <item>Once he was as great as his fame made him. His knowledge was deep, his thought was subtle, and his hands marvelously skilled; and he had a power over the minds of others. The wise he could persuade, and the smaller folk he could daunt. That power he certainly still keeps. There are not many in Middle-earth that I should say were safe, if they were left alone to talk with him, even now when he has suffered a defeat. Gandalf, Elrond, and Galadriel, perhaps, now that his wickedness has been laid bare, but very few others.</item>
        <item>A mortal, Frodo, who keeps one of the Great Rings, does not die, but he does not grow or obtain more life, he merely continues, until at last every minute is a weariness. And if he often uses the Ring to make himself invisible, he fades: he becomes in the end invisible permanently, and walks in the twilight under the eye of the Dark Power that rules the Rings.</item>
        <item>How am I supposed to decide this\? How can I possibly stay without Mom and Dad\? This is too much. I don\'t even understand how it all works, why I\'m here in the state that I\'m in or how to get out of it if I wanted to. If I were to say, \"I want to wake up,\" would I wake up right now\? I\'ve already tried snapping my heels to find Teddy and tried to beam myself to Hawaii, and that didn\'t work. This seems a whole lot more complicated.</item>
        <item>I have spoken words of hope. But only of hope. Hope is not victory. War is upon us and all our friends, a war in which only the use of the Ring could give us surety of victory. It fills me with great sorrow and great fear: for much shall be destroyed and all may be lost.</item>
        <item>See, my precious: if we has it, then we can escape, even from Him, eh\? Perhaps we grow very strong, stronger than Wraiths. Lord Smeagol\? Gollum the Great\? The Gollum! Eat fish every day, three times a day, fresh from the sea.</item>
        <item>\"I wish it need not have happened in my time,\" said Frodo. \"So do I,\" said Gandalf, \"and so do all who live to see such times. But that is not for them to decide. All we have to decide is what to do with the time that is given us.\"</item>
        <item>I came to realize that I had more to offer this world than just making things that blow up.</item>
        <item>At lunch he told Bill about a physics book he was reading about time. How the passing of time is just an illusion because all of eternity is actually taking place at once: the past never vanishes away and the future has already happened. All of history is fixed and laid out, like an infinite landscape of simultaneous events that we simply happen to travel through in one direction. Bill made a joke that he could\'ve sworn he\'d been told that somewhere before, but the guy just stared at him like he didn\'t get it.</item>
        <item>But no artist, I now realize, can be satisfied with art alone. There is a natural craving for recognition which cannot be gain-said.</item>
        <item>A faerie heart is different from a human heart. Human hearts are elastic. They have room for all sorts of passions, and they can break and heal and love again and again. Faerie hearts are evolutionarily less sophisticated. They are small and hard, like tiny grains of sand. Our hearts are too small to love more than one person in a lifetime.</item>
        <item>What makes a good book\? An author who knows how to leave out all the unnecessary bulk and delivers a lean story where not a single word is fluff.</item>
        <item>Tom put the Ring round the end of his little finger and held it up to the candlelight. For a moment the hobbits noticed nothing strange about this. Then they gasped. There was no sign of Tom disappearing! Tom laughed again, and then he spun the Ring in the air - and it vanished with a flash. Frodo gave a cry - and Tom leaned forward and handed it back to him with a smile.</item>
        <item>I\'ve been making a list of the things they don\'t teach you at school. They don\'t teach you how to love somebody. They don\'t teach you how to be famous. They don\'t teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don\'t teach you how to walk away from someone you don\'t love any longer. They don\'t teach you how to know what\'s going on in someone else\'s mind. They don\'t teach you what to say to someone who\'s dying. They don\'t teach you anything worth knowing.</item>
        <item>It was a merry journey with Tom Bombadil trotting gaily beside them, or before them, on Fatty Lumpkin, who could move much faster than his girth promised. Tom sang most of the time, but it was chiefly nonsense, or else perhaps a strange language unknown to the hobbits, an ancient language whose words were mainly those of wonder and delight.</item>
        <item>If this had been an old house, with creaking wood, and dark shadows, and heavily panelled walls, there might have been an eerie feeling. But this house was the essence of modernity. There were no dark corners - no possible sliding panels - it was flooded with electric light - everything was new and bright and shining. There was nothing hidden in this house, nothing concealed. It had no atmosphere about it. Somehow, that was the most frightening thing of all...</item>
        <item>I don\'t remember the moment that changed my life 4 years ago. Call it a side effect of being struck by lightning. That bolt of electricity burned a small hole in my memory. It also rewired my brain, transforming me into Lucille Fanny Callahan, math genius.</item>
        <item>I don\'t feel like that now. I feel that as long as the Shire lies behind, safe and comfortable, I shall find wandering more bearable: I shall know that somewhere there is a firm foothold, even if my feet cannot stand there again.</item>
        <item>Your bed is with you in the void. But not for long - it goes away from you. You don\'t have any way to get it back, so you just let it go. But so now we have a body in the void with you. So does the bed move, or do you move\? Or both\?</item>
        <item>Sam was the only member of the party who had not been over the river before. He had a strange feeling as the slow gurgling stream slipped by: his old life lay behind him in the mists, dark adventure lay in front.</item>
        <item>Thinking you know everything there is to know about something will only hold you back, because it prevents you from learning anything new.</item>
        <item>There\'s never been a true war that wasn\'t fought between two sets of people who were certain they were in the right. The really dangerous people believe they are doing whatever they are doing solely and only because it is without question the right thing to do. And that is what makes them dangerous.</item>
        <item>It\'s wildly irritating to have invented something as revolutionary as sarcasm, only to have it abused by amateurs.</item>
        <item>They say that money doesn\'t bring you happiness, I say neither does being broke, so let me suffer with a new car.</item>
        <item>If you come to a river and find a boat at the edge, you will use that boat and it will serve you well, but once across the river, do you put the boat on your shoulders and carry it with you on the rest of your journey\?</item>
        <item>Sam stared up at the inn with its three stories and many windows, and felt his heart sink. He had imagined himself meeting giants taller than trees, and other creatures even more terrifying, some time or other in the course of his journey; but at the moment he was finding his first sight of Men and their tall houses quite enough, indeed too much for the dark end of a tiring day.</item>
        <item>I am forever your debtor for reminding me of that curious passage in my life. During the first year or two after it happened, I could not bear to think of it. My pain and shame were so intense, and my sense of having been an imbecile so settled, established and confirmed, that I drove the episode entirely from my mind - and so all these twenty-eight or twenty-nine years I have lived in the conviction that my performance of that time was coarse, vulgar, and destitute of humor.</item>
        <item>Sociopathy is the inability to process emotional experience, including love and caring, except when such experience can be calculated as a coldly intellectual task.</item>
        <item>You\'re telling us you killed those three young men on the subway\? And why should we believe you\? I\'ve got nothing left to lose, nothing can hurt me anymore. My life, is nothing but a comedy. Let me get this straight, you think killing those guys is funny. I do, and I\'m tired of pretending it\'s not. Comedy is subjective Murray, isn\'t that what they say. All of you, this system that knows so much, you decide what\'s right or wrong. The same way that you decide what\'s funny, or not.</item>
        <item>The bus was going down the spectacular road eastward from Jerusalem to Jericho, it would make it from its start around 800 meters above sea level to its end at 300 odd meters below sea level, a distance of about 40 kilometers, in about 45 minutes.</item>
        <item>Every day when you\'re walking down the street, everybody that you meet has an original point of view. And I say hey, hey! What a wonderful kind of day, where you can learn to work and play, and get along with each other.</item>
        <item>It became difficult to follow the path, and they were very tired. Their legs seemed leaden. Strange furtive noises ran among the bushes and reeds on either side of them; and if they looked up to the pale sky, they caught sight of queer gnarled and knobbly faces that gloomed dark against the twilight, and leered down at them from the high bank and the edges of the wood.</item>
        <item>When everyone else was thinking it was time for bed, his mind was telling him it\'s time to get ahead of the competition.</item>
        <item>Well, no need to brood on what tomorrow may bring. For one thing, tomorrow will be certain to bring worse than today, for many days to come. And there is nothing more that I can do to help it. The board is set, and the pieces are moving.</item>
        <item>Before long, washed and refreshed, the hobbits were seated at the table, two on each side, while at either end sat Goldberry and the Master. It was a long and merry meal. Though the hobbits ate, as only famished hobbits can eat, there was no lack. The drink in their drinking-bowls seemed to be clear cold water, yet it went to their hearts like wine and set free their voices. The guests became suddenly aware that they were singing merrily, as if it was easier and more natural than talking.</item>
        <item>Do not meddle in the affairs of wizards, for they are subtle and quick to anger.</item>
        <item>What\'s morality\? It\'s the difference between what is right and what you can rationalize.</item>
        <item>Someday, I hope to make it clear to you that success is not determined by leather-bound books and ink on paper, but rather the passion that I have found out of heartbreak and anger. I know that happiness is stability, but stability is not a desk job, and I refuse to sacrifice my aspirations for an income and security.</item>
        <item>So when you find yourself locked onto an unpleasant train of thought, heading for the places in your past where the screaming is unbearable, remember there\'s always madness. Madness is the emergency exit.</item>
        <item>Old Tom Bombadil is a merry fellow, bright blue his jacket is, and his boots are yellow. None has ever caught him yet, for Tom, he is the Master: his songs are stronger songs, and his feet are faster.</item>
        <item>Can you live without answers\? All of you, ask that of yourself. Can you live without answers\? Because if you cannot, then most assuredly you will invent your own answers and they will comfort you. And all those who do not share your view will by their very existence strike fear and hatred into your heart.</item>
        <item>You must learn from the mistakes of others because you can\'t possibly live long enough to make them all yourself.</item>
        <item>Now I see fire inside the mountain, I see fire burning the trees, and I see fire hollowing souls. I see fire, blood in the breeze, and I hope that you remember me.</item>
        <item>Before I was famous I had a whole bunch of jobs where all I needed was boots. People would look right past me, or if they did look at me, it was with a mean look. But when I got famous, people would look at me and smile and wonder where they knew me from. If they flat-out recognized me, they\'d laugh and dance like they\'d won a prize, and I\'d just stand there and smile and feel warmth from their love. So the fame made the world, which is a real cold place, a little less cold.</item>
        <item>If you had one shot to sit on your lazy butt, and watch all the TV you ever wanted, until your brain turned to mush. Would you go for it, or just let it slip.</item>
        <item>It\'s one thing to question your mind; it\'s another to question your eyes and ears. But then again, isn\'t it all the same, our senses just mediocre inputs for our brain\? Sure, we rely on them, trust they accurately portray the real world around us, but what if the haunting truth is they can\'t\?</item>
        <item>Do you know what an artist and a sniper have in common\? Details. Like when a touch of color is out of place. When a shadow does not match with its surroundings. Or when a shape is not where it is supposed to be. The only difference is the stakes. Mine are higher.</item>
        <item>For attractive lips, speak words of kindness. For lovely eyes, seek out the good in people. For a slim figure, share your food with the hungry. For beautiful hair, let a child run his or her fingers through it once a day. For poise, walk with the knowledge that you never walk alone...</item>
        <item>This day does not belong to one man but to all. Let us together rebuild this world that we may share in the days of peace.</item>
        <item>In the wild lands beyond Bree there were mysterious wanderers. The Bree-folk called them Rangers, and knew nothing of their origin. They were taller and darker than the Men of Bree and were believed to have strange powers of sight and hearing, and to understand the languages of beasts and birds.</item>
        <item>And now it\'s time for Silly Songs with Larry, the part of the show where Larry comes out and sings a silly song.</item>
        <item>When you hit rock-bottom, you still have a way to go until the abyss.</item>
        <item>Most people believe that reality is truth and appearances are deceiving. But those of us who know the Moon Arcanum understand we can only truly know the appearance itself. You can never touch the so-called reality that lies just beyond the reach of your own perception.</item>
        <item>Changes, they might drive you half-insane, but it\'s killing you to stay the same, but it\'s all gonna work out, it\'s all gonna work out someday. Moments, livin\' with your eyes half-open. You\'ve been thinking \'bout these changes. It\'s all gonna work out, it\'s all gonna work out someday.</item>
        <item>The nation that neglects social inequality, mischievously increases military budgets, and then uses its power internally to suppress the citizens on the pretext of invasion by an external enemy is on the road to extinction.</item>
        <item>Advisors and scholars will tell you that history is a narrative of strength. They will recount stories of the rise and fall of nations and empires. There will be stories of armies, battles, and decisive victories. But this isn\'t true strength - it\'s merely power. I now believe true strength is found in vulnerability. In forgiveness. In love. There is a beautiful, upside-down truth, which is that these moments of purest strength appear as weakness to those who don\'t know better. For a long time, I didn\'t know better. I ask you and your brother to reject history as a narrative of strength, and instead, have faith that it can be a narrative of love.</item>
        <item>It\'s a basic truth of the human condition, that everybody lies. The only variable is about what. The weird thing about telling someone they\'re dying is that, it tends to focus their priorities. Find out what matters to them. What they\'re willing to die for... What they\'re willing to lie for.</item>
        <item>What is this place, and who am I\? I don\'t remember my name. All I remember is that I don\'t know my name and that I can\'t remember if I do know my name. I have this strange feeling that I\'ve forgotten all of this before.</item>
        <item>True, the law isn\'t perfect. That is because we people who made the law are imperfect. But I still believe the law can show the way to righteousness and justice.</item>
        <item>You know some automotive yoga could really lower your RPMs, man.</item>
        <item>There are 10 kinds of people in this world; those who understand binary, and those who don\'t.</item>
        <item>Sometimes I wish I never built this palace, but real love is never a waste of time.</item>
        <item>Lured into dental condemnation by my own teeth, I felt lost and betrayed.</item>
        <item>Above it all was beautiful, ageless Acelia, glancing sidelong at her court as she sat askance on her throne of gems. It was often said that she had an iron in every fire and a scheme for every enemy, even the ones that she currently regarded as friends. Her true age was a hotly debated topic in the Chateau - she had been the queen for as long as anyone could remember but retained the body of a fragile, waif-thin youth. Her peculiar violet hair cascaded down her back like the waters of her castle\'s namesake. Only her fierce eyes betrayed her true age. Looking into those faded grays might give one a heavy feeling in the stomach, the uncomfortable weight of the long passage of eons.</item>
        <item>People aren\'t all perfect. They\'re weak, ugly, and they get jealous and try to bring others down. Oddly enough, the better you are, the harder it is to live. That\'s why I\'m going to change this world and the people in it...</item>
        <item>I have been improving the wrong way, like bad fish in warm weather. One day last week, I had a woeful day of headache, nausea, and malaise, which left me weak as a sea anemone at low water. Since then, there has been no improvement.</item>
        <item>The capacity to love is determined by the fact that man is ready to seek the good consciously with others, to subordinate himself to this good because of others, or to subordinate himself to others because of this good.</item>
        <item>I don\'t know, you\'re made of metal, but you have feelings... and that means you have a soul, and souls don\'t die... Mom says it\'s something inside of all good things, and that it goes on forever and ever.</item>
        <item>The game of Chess is not merely an idle amusement. Several very valuable qualities of the mind, useful in the course of human life, are to be acquired or strengthened by it, so as to become habits, ready on all occasions. For life is a kind of chess, in which we have often points to gain, and competitors or adversaries to contend with, and in which there is a vast variety of good and ill events, that are, in some degree, the effects of prudence or the want of it.</item>
        <item>While software development is immune from almost all physical laws, entropy hits us hard. Entropy is a term from physics that refers to the amount of \"disorder\" in a system. Unfortunately, the laws of thermodynamics guarantee that the entropy in the universe tends toward a maximum. When disorder increases in software, programmers call it \"software rot.\"</item>
        <item>Lights up and they know who you are, know who you are. Do you know who you are\?</item>
        <item>Almost immediately Aesma found the estate of the Master of space-time, a lunar domain of immense proportions. It was incredibly hard to miss the Master, as he was a man thirty stories tall, with skin speckled as a night sky, and in his tangled hair, among his shaggy brow, and scattered in his great knotted beard were a multitude of burning stars. He had served for uncounted centuries as chief architect of the gods after attaining his mastery, and even now was building a mighty dark tower greater than any mountain, and the clangs of his immense silver chisel shivered Aesma\'s bones as she approached. But she had little regard for his mighty stature as a furious mischief was in her.</item>
        <item>As he proceeded toward the Chateau\'s minarets, it was difficult not to marvel at the falls below. It was a magnificent sight, watching that water fall off the edge of the world and into the misty clouds below. As single-minded as Karzt was, he was glad for the chance to see one of the great wonders of Genesis. He pulled a whetstone out of his backpack and walked back to the carriage, leaning against its wheeled frame while idly running the stone over the edge of his hatchet blade. He knew that it would need sharpening for the days ahead, especially considering that he\'d blunted it recently during the encounter with those creatures.</item>
        <item>Speed. I am speed. One winner, forty-two losers. I eat losers for breakfast.</item>
        <item>When you\'re only having seconds I\'m having twenty-thirds. When I go to get my shoes shined I gotta take their word, because I\'m fat!</item>
        <item>Despite lacking the information and his understandable desire to hope for the best, Stalin must have realized the seriousness of the situation. According to eyewitnesses, he was stunned by the outbreak of war. As Zhukov describes it, \"During the first day he was not able to really take himself in hand and get a firm grip on events. The shock to I. V. Stalin caused by the enemy invasion was so strong that his voice even became softer and his instructions on organizing the military effort were not always appropriate to the situation.\"</item>
        <item>Born in the south of France, Andrey was handsome, tall, and graying at the temples, but his most distinguishing feature was not his looks, his height, or his hair. It was his hands. Pale and well manicured, his fingers were half an inch longer than the fingers of most men his height. Had he been a pianist, Andrey could easily have straddled a twelfth. Had he been a puppeteer, he could have performed the sword fight between Macbeth and Macduff as all three witches looked on. But Andrey was neither a pianist nor a puppeteer - or at least not in the traditional sense. He was the captain of the Boyarsky, and one watched in wonder as his hands fulfilled their purpose at every turn.</item>
        <item>You think skinny, anemic fanboys have a monopoly on the one fictional genre where women and people of color get to exist outside of backward societal norms and traditional confinement\? Not to mention a genre largely premised on the idea that future dystopia is the inevitable outcome of the current system of patriarchal excess. Idiot.</item>
        <item>You know, the Rust-eze Medicated Bumper Ointment team ran a great race today. And remember: with a little Rust-eze - and an insane amount of luck - you too can look like me. Ka-chow!</item>
        <item>You get tough like me and you don\'t get hurt. You look out for yourself and nothin\' can touch you...</item>
        <item>I suppose hobbits need some description nowadays, since they have become rare and shy of the Big People, as they call us. They are (or were) a little people, about half our height, and smaller than the bearded Dwarves. Hobbits have no beards. There is little or no magic about them, except the ordinary everyday sort which helps them to disappear quietly and quickly when large stupid folk like you and me come blundering along, making a noise like elephants which they can hear a mile off. They are inclined to be fat in the stomach; they dress in bright colours (chiefly green and yellow); wear no shoes, because their feet grow natural leathery soles and thick warm brown hair like the stuff on their heads (which is curly); have long clever brown fingers, good-natured faces, and laugh deep fruity laughs (especially after dinner, which they have twice a day when they can get it).</item>
        <item>You know that death is the most beautiful part of life, right\? Death is beautiful because we all fear death. And fear is the most amazing emotion of all because it creates complete awareness. It brings you to now. It makes you truly present. And when we are truly present, it\'s nirvana. It\'s pure love. So death is pure love.</item>
        <item>\'Cause I don\'t care too much for money, money can\'t buy me love.</item>
        <item>Life is not the amount of breaths you take. It\'s the moments that take your breath away.</item>
        <item>Stalin was a typical product of his time. As he did before the revolution, he continued to follow Lenin. Part of an exclusive group of influential Soviet functionaries, Stalin was a member of the government, a member of the party\'s Central Committee, and a member of the top leadership. He spoke with Lenin almost daily.</item>
        <item>In a time when lawmen were outlaws, a thief, a cutthroat and a bounty hunter face an enemy of a new kind. Through the uncharted lands of the West, a fistful of men ride for the Blackwater. Tonight, an unsettling tone lingers in the air - this sound makes the horses shriek in fear! From above, piercing thunder roars. The earth has visitors: this is the sound of the machine. Now staring into the sky, the stars dissipate to make way, as a mechanical beast makes its descent towards the earth. Through galaxies in space - and tales old as time - fear finds a way into the heart of every man of the Blackwater.</item>
        <item>A philosopher once asked, \"Are we human because we gaze at the stars, or do we gaze at them because we are human\?\" Pointless, really... \"Do the stars gaze back\?\" Now, that\'s a question.</item>
        <item>He was standing on an impossibly tall grey stone pillar. A dark, starless sky loomed overhead. All around him was nothing but an inky black expanse with a strange purple-toned haze permeating throughout. He felt cold rough winds battering him, threatening to send him tumbling into the abyss below. Far, far below, he could see an endless purple desert stretching out in all directions. Shivering, he struggled to remember how he\'d gotten here.</item>
        <item>This time tomorrow, where will we be\? On a spaceship somewhere sailing across an empty sea\? This time tomorrow, what will we know\? Will we still be here watching an in-flight movie show\? I\'ll leave the sun behind me and I\'ll watch the clouds as they sadly pass me by seven miles below me. I can see the world and it ain\'t so big at all.</item>
        <item>Upon arriving in Petrograd in 1917, Trotsky immediately understood that he and Lenin were natural allies. Their allegiance fell into place naturally, without any negotiations. Trotsky joined the Bolsheviks and Lenin immediately recognized him as a strong partner, ready to use word and deed in an unwavering battle for power.</item>
        <item>Azir was a mortal emperor of Shurima in a far distant age, a proud man who stood at the cusp of immortality. His hubris saw him betrayed and murdered at the moment of his greatest triumph, but now, millennia later, he has been reborn as an Ascended being of immense power. With his buried city risen from the sand, Azir seeks to restore Shurima to its former glory.</item>
        <item>At just after eight on the morning of Sunday, September 1, 1715, four days before his seventy-seventh birthday and in the seventy-second year of his reign, Louis gave a number of short sighs and two gasps. Then quietly, peacefully, Louis XIV - Louis the Great - was dead.</item>
        <item>\"I believe,\" he said, speaking more slowly now, \"that there is a whole world of sound about us all the time that we cannot hear. It is possible that up there in those high-pitched inaudible regions there is a new exciting music being made, with subtle harmonies and fierce grinding discords, a music so powerful that it would drive us mad if only our ears were tuned to hear the sound of it.\"</item>
        <item>Wrong, sir. Wrong. Under Section 37B of the contract signed by him, it states quite clearly that all offers shall become null and void if, and you can read it for yourself in this photostatic copy, \"I, the undersigned, shall forfeit all rights, privileges, and licenses herein and herein contained\" et cetera, et cetera, \"fax mentis incendium gloriae cultum\" et cetera, et cetera, \"memo bis punitor delicatum.\" It\'s all there, black and white, clear as crystal. You stole Fizzy Lifting Drinks. You bumped into the ceiling which now has to be washed and sterilized, so you get nothing. YOU LOSE! GOOD DAY, SIR!</item>
        <item>I thought I had it all together, but I was led astray the day you walked away. You were the clock that was tickin\' in my home. Changed my state of mind. Love\'s so hard to find.</item>
        <item>The boy bands have won, and all the copyists and the tribute bands and the TV talent show producers have won, if we allow our culture to be shaped by mimicry, whether it from lack of ideas or from exaggerated respect. You should never try to freeze culture. What you can do is recycle that culture. Take your older brother\'s hand-me-down jacket and re-style it, re-fashion it to the point where it becomes your own. But don\'t just regurgitate creative history, or hold art and music and literature as fixed, untouchable and kept under glass. The people who try to \"guard\" any particular form of music are, like the copyists and manufactured bands, doing it the worst disservice, because the only thing that you can do to music that will damage it is not change it, not make it your own. Because then it dies, then it\'s over, then it\'s done, and the boy bands have won.</item>
        <item>Ten thousands of insects burrowing deep into my skin by my fragile exposed follicles and igniting a fiery unquenchable burning Abaddon descended into a spot where I couldn\'t itch at it.</item>
        <item>First, purpose is a \"stable and far-reaching\" goal. Most of our goals are mundane and immediate, like getting to work on time, going to the gym, or doing the dishes. Purpose, by contrast, is a goal toward which we are always working. It is the forward-pointing arrow that motivates our behavior and serves as the organizing principle of our lives.</item>
        <item>Math is like an atomic-powered prosthesis that you attach to your common sense, vastly multiplying its reach and strength. Despite the power of mathematics, and despite its sometimes forbidding notation and abstraction, the actual mental work involved is little different from the way we think about down-to-earth problems.</item>
        <item>Welcome to Arco AM/PM Mini-Market. We would like to advise our customers that any individual who offers to pump gas, wash windows, or solicit products is not employed by or associated with this facility. We discourage any contact with these individuals, and ask that you report any problems to uniformed personnel inside. Thank you for shopping at Arco AM/PM, and have a pleasant day.</item>
        <item>You have technicians here making noise. No one is a musician, they are not artists because nobody can play the guitar.</item>
        <item>There\'s no reason a fake can\'t do what the real thing would. And it\'s possible for a fake to be more real than the real thing.</item>
        <item>Gentlemen, this will be a one-lap race. You will drive to Willy\'s Butte, go around Willy\'s Butte, and come back. There will be no bumpin\', no cheatin\', no spittin\', no bitin\', no road ragin\', no maimin\', no oil slickin\', no pushin\', no shovin\', no backstabbin\', no road hoggin\', and no lollygaggin\'.</item>
        <item>I cannot guess how many days have passed since then, but I have endured misery which nothing but the eternal sentiment of a just retribution burning within my heart could have enabled me to support. Immense and rugged mountains of ice often barred up my passage, and I often heard the thunder of the ground sea, which threatened my destruction. But again the frost came and made the paths of the sea secure.</item>
        <item>Overthinking, overanalyzing, separates the body from the mind. Withering my intuition, missing opportunities and I must feed my will to feel my moment drawing way outside the lines.</item>
        <item>Where did I go wrong\? I lost a friend somewhere along in the bitterness and I would have stayed up with you all night had I known how to save a life.</item>
        <item>Three Rings for the Elven-kings under the sky, seven for the Dwarf-lords in their halls of stone, nine for Mortal Men doomed to die, one for the Dark Lord on his dark throne in the Land of Mordor, where the Shadows lie. One Ring to rule them all, One Ring to find them, One Ring to bring them all and in the darkness bind them.</item>
        <item>Prying eyes had become a nuisance along the Old Road, and so I undertook to receive my most curious deliveries by way of marine shipments. A sheltered jetty was accessible by a narrow stone stair off the back of the manor, and a discreet system of pulleys could hoist even the heaviest prizes up the rock face from a securely tied dinghy below.</item>
        <item>It can\'t be, somebody tell me this is all a dream. Left your rings, like the life we had didn\'t mean a thing... can\'t you see you\'ve broken me\? Oh Valerie, this isn\'t how our story had to be. Oh Valerie, thought you\'d always be a part of me. I don\'t know if you know, I still think about you, oh... if you\'re ever coming home - I miss you so.</item>
        <item>I never thought I\'d be able to do any of this stuff. But I can. Anyone can wear the mask. You could wear the mask. If you didn\'t know that before, I hope you do now.</item>
        <item>Even good people are great at making bad decisions.</item>
        <item>It\'s not a question but a lesson learned in time. It\'s something unpredictable, but in the end it\'s right. I hope you had the time of your life.</item>
        <item>Sometimes when he brushed, he felt like he was scrubbing at the very crust of his soul.</item>
        <item>In the beginning, the Universe was created. This had made a lot of people very angry and been widely regarded as a bad move.</item>
        <item>There\'s a lot more to racing than just winning. I mean, taking the race by a full lap... Where\'s the entertainment in that\? No, no, no... I wanted to give folks a little sizzle.</item>
        <item>The most spectacular, amazing, unequivocally, unbelievable ending in the history of the world! And we don\'t even know who won!</item>
        <item>All right, I wanna know who\'s responsible for wreckin\' my town Sheriff. I want his hood on a platter! I\'m gonna put him in jail till he rots! No, check that. I\'m gonna put him in jail till the jail rots on top of him, and then I\'m gonna move him to a new jail and let that jail rot. I\'m... Throw him out of here, Sheriff. I want him out of my courtroom. I want him out of our town! Case dismissed.</item>
        <item>What is better\? To be born good or to overcome your evil nature through great effort\?</item>
        <item>There is little evidence regarding Stalin\'s feelings toward his father, who died young. To all appearances, however, he felt genuine affection for his mother. His letter to her in her later years contain lines such as the following: \"Hello Mama dear! How are you getting on, how are you feeling\? I haven\'t had any letters from you in a long time - you must be upset with me, but what can I do\? I\'m really very busy.\"</item>
        <item>We can\'t retract the decisions we\'ve made. We can only affect the decisions we\'re going to make from here.</item>
        <item>Who cares if we don\'t see the sun shine ever again\? I want you more than any blue sky. The weather can go crazy.</item>
        <item>In one small part of space, the war continues. In war, there can be only one victor. Space is an uninhabited wilderness and bloody wounds disappear with time. Maybe the multitude of stars in the sky remember those wounds. Maybe it is fated that even those stars will vanish one day. Man\'s presence in the midst of these stars is all that remains of a forgotten battle.</item>
        <item>One Eva Smith has gone - but there are millions and millions and millions of Eva Smiths and John Smiths still left with us, with their lives, their hopes and fears, their suffering and chance of happiness, all intertwined with our lives, and what we think and say and do. We don\'t live alone. We are members of one body. We are responsible for each other. And I tell you that the time will soon come when, if men will not learn that lesson, then they will be taught it in fire and blood and anguish.</item>
        <item>I hopped up and I said, \"I don\'t know; do you want to get something delivered\?\" She\'s like, \"Why would I want to eat liver\? I don\'t even like liver!\" I\'m like, \"No, I said delivered.\" She\'s like, \"I heard you say liver!\" I\'m like, \"I should know what I said.\" She\'s like, \"Whatever! I just don\'t want any liver!\"</item>
        <item>Written in these walls are the stories that I can\'t explain. I leave my heart open but it stays right here empty for days. She told me in the morning she don\'t feel the same about us in her bones. It seems to me that when I die these words will be written on my stone. And I\'ll be gone, gone tonight. The ground beneath my feet is open wide. The way that I\'ve been holding on too tight. With nothing in between.</item>
        <item>Well, if it isn\'t the man of the hour... You\'re late. I\'ve been waiting for you FOREVER, mister! I was beginning to think you\'d stood me up. I thought to myself, \"Wendy, is Mario ever going to show up\?\" And then I dozed off. Anyway, Mr. Bowser sent me to stop you from getting your grubby little mitts on this Big Paint Star. And now that I\'ve gotten some peaceful rest, it\'s time to help you rest in peace!</item>
        <item>Poured forth gracefully, this etheric tincture lifts winter\'s coat-of-arms with coaxing aromas and electricity. Used with vigilance, a pitcher of summer stirs a memory into swooning, and bravely, the flowers of the past will stretch their limbs into the sky while snow falls quietly all around.</item>
        <item>Blue Monday, how I hate Blue Monday. Got to work like a slave all day. Here come Tuesday, oh, hard Tuesday. I\'m so tired, got no time to play. Here come Wednesday, I\'m beat to my socks. My gal calls, got to tell her that I\'m out. \'Cause Thursday is a hard workin\' day and Friday I get my pay.</item>
        <item>Klausner sat down beside the telephone and waited. He tried to remember what the shriek of the tree had sounded like, but he couldn\'t. He could remember only that it had been enormous and frightful and that it had made him feel sick with horror. He tried to imagine what sort of noise a human would make if he had to stand anchored to the ground while someone deliberately swung a small sharp thing at his leg so that the blade cut in deep and wedged itself in the cut. Same sort of noise perhaps\?</item>
        <item>Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness, that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented and fabulous\? Actually, who are you not to be\? You are a child of God. Your playing small doesn\'t serve the world. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It\'s not just in some of us; it\'s in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others.</item>
        <item>Now it\'s not August, it\'s not February, it\'s not July, it\'s not even September! I think you know what it is. And when it comes around I wake up and kiss the ground, I was lost and now I\'m found! It\'s the first of October today!</item>
        <item>I breathed in my new surroundings. The air smelled different here, I don\'t know whether it was the desert air or the dry trees or just that I was far away from the stink of the city, but I liked it.</item>
        <item>When you wake up in the morning, tell yourself: the people I deal with today will be meddling, ungrateful, arrogant, dishonest, jealous and surly. They are like this because they can\'t tell good from evil. But I have seen the beauty of good, and the ugliness of evil, and have recognized that the wrongdoer has a nature related to my own - not of the same blood and birth, but the same mind, and possessing a share of the divine. And so none of them can hurt me.</item>
        <item>You had to kill the conversation, you always had the upper hand. Got caught in love and stepped in sinking sand. You had to go and ruin all our plans, packed your bags and you\'re leaving home. Got a one-way ticket and you\'re all set to go, but we have one more day together, so love me like there\'s no tomorrow.</item>
        <item>The person who stops studying merely because he has finished school is forever hopelessly doomed to mediocrity, no matter what may be his calling. The way of success is the way of continuous pursuit of knowledge.</item>
        <item>There is no faith and no courage and no sacrifice in doing what is expedient. There is no careful observation that actions and presuppositions matter, or that the world is made of what matters. To have meaning in your life is better than to have what you want, because you may neither know what you want, nor what you truly need. Meaning is something that comes upon you, of its own accord. You can set up the preconditions, you can follow meaning, when it manifests itself, but you cannot simply produce it, as an act of will. Meaning signifies that you are in the right place, at the right time, properly balanced between order and chaos, where everything lines up as best it can at that moment.</item>
        <item>I\'m in the race of life and time passed by. I sit back and I watch it, hands in my pockets. Waves come crashing over me, but I just watch \'em. I just watch \'em. I\'m underwater, but I feel like I\'m on top of it. I\'m at the bottom, but I don\'t know what the problem is. I\'m in a box, but I\'m the one who locked me in. I\'m suffocating and I\'m running out of oxygen.</item>
        <item>Three cars are tied for the season points lead, heading into the final race of the season. And the winner of this race, Darrell, will win the season title and... the Piston Cup! Does The King, Strip Weathers, have one more victory in him before retirement\? He\'s been Dinoco\'s golden boy for years! Can he win them one last Piston Cup\? And as always, in the second place spot, we find Chick Hicks. He\'s been chasing that tailfin his entire career. Chick thought this was his year, Bob, his chance to finally emerge from The King\'s shadow. But the last thing he expected was... Lightning McQueen! You know, I don\'t think anybody expected this. The rookie sensation came into the season unknown. But everyone knows him now. Will he be the first rookie to win a Piston Cup and land Dinoco\? The legend, the runner up, and the rookie! Three cars, one champion!</item>
        <item>Yeah! I\'ve got a cup brewing, yeah! Sure need some coffee, yeah! I haven\'t slept in twenty-eight days, yeah! Wait, I already finished, I need another one!</item>
        <item>I don\'t believe that anybody feels the way I do about you now.</item>
        <item>We got questions we should not ask, but how would you feel if I told you I loved you\? It\'s just something that I want to do.</item>
        <item>Nobody listens anymore. I can\'t talk to the walls because they\'re yelling at me, I can\'t talk to my wife; she listens to the walls. I just want someone to hear what I have to say. And maybe if I talk long enough it\'ll make sense. And I want you to teach me to understand what I read.</item>
        <item>Interplanetary adversaries battling for supremacy - sounds like a good way to build up my infamy. Soon as Automator sent for me, we headed over to receive our registration forms from the galactic embassy.</item>
        <item>But the house gets so quiet sitting here wishing for just an hour or two alone with you. Well, it\'s always too personal, always too close to comment. They all mention how tired you look and you realize you haven\'t said a word in hours. Well, who\'s hiding it\?</item>
        <item>I am not a recruiter. I am a software engineer. And as such, I know what it\'s like to be asked to whip up brilliant algorithms on the spot and then write flawless code on a whiteboard. I know because I\'ve been asked to do the same thing - in interviews at Google, Microsoft, Apple, and Amazon, among other companies.</item>
        <item>You know that I am called the Count because I really love to count. Sometimes I sit and count all day, but sometimes I get carried away. I count the spiders on the wall. I count the cobwebs in the hall. I count the candles on the shelf. When I\'m alone, I count myself!</item>
        <item>Live, then, and be happy, beloved children of my heart, and never forget that, until the day God deigns to reveal the future to man, the sum of all human wisdom will be contained in these two words: Wait and hope.</item>
        <item>Those who do not exist cannot suffer and are of no account to any viable ethics. If the true path to goodness is the elimination of suffering, then only those who must exist can be allowed to exist. It is the nature of life to favor existence over nonexistence, and to prefer the fertile soil to the poisoned wind. Because those who open their mouths to that wind pass from the world and leave no descendant, whether of flesh or of thought.</item>
        <item>Do you want to make the most valuable purchase you can\? Buy a juicer. Do you own a car\? Sell the car and buy a juicer. The juicer will take you much farther. Or just buy the juicer now!</item>
        <item>That makes perfect sense, turn right to go left. Yes, thank you! Or should I say, \"No thank you\", because in opposite world, maybe that really means, \"Thank you\"!</item>
        <item>And you\'d say, \"Time to rest your weary head, take your wings and go to bed; I know you want to know it all, my darling.\" And I\'d say, \"Set me down and rock me, rock me to sleep.\"</item>
        <item>We\'re all bored, we\'re all so tired of everything. We wait for trains that just aren\'t comin\'. We show off our different scarlet letters... trust me, mine is better. We\'re so young, but we\'re on the road to ruin. We play dumb, but we know exactly what we\'re doing.</item>
        <item>My face, body, lifestyle. I chose every aspect of myself with my own will. I don\'t want to be ordered around by anyone anymore, and I have no need for a past. I\'ve got dreams to fulfill, money to earn, love to find, and success to achieve. They may be foolishly simplistic desires for some, but to me, working towards them bit by bit is how I build my confidence.</item>
        <item>Last night I dreamt I went to Manderely again. It seemed to me I stood by the iron gate leading to the drive, and for a while I could not enter, for the way was barred to me. There was a padlock and a chain upon the gate. I called in my dream to the lodge-keeper, and had no answer, and peering closer through the rusted spokes of the gate I saw that the lodge was uninhabited.</item>
        <item>Well that is where we are. You say we are on the brink of destruction and you are right. But it is only on the brink that people find the will to change. Only at the precipice do we evolve. This is our moment. Don\'t take it from us, we are close to an answer.</item>
        <item>It\'s all wrong. By rights we shouldn\'t even be here. But we are. It\'s like in the great stories, Mr. Frodo. The ones that really mattered. Full of darkness and danger they were, and sometimes you didn\'t want to know the end. Because how could the end be happy\? How could the world go back to the way it was when so much bad happened\? But in the end, it\'s only a passing thing, this shadow. Even darkness must pass. A new day will come.</item>
        <item>What I love about Charlie: Charlie is undaunted. He never lets other people\'s opinions, or any setbacks keep him from what he wants to do. Charlie eats like he\'s trying to get it over with, and like there won\'t be enough food for everyone. A sandwich is to be strangled while devoured. But he\'s incredibly neat, and I rely on him to keep things in order. He\'s energy-conscious. He doesn\'t look in the mirror too often.</item>
        <item>A scientific approach to the examination of phenomena is a defence against the pure emotion of fear. Keep tight hold and continue while there\'s time. Now - counter to the previous syllogism: tricky one, follow me carefully, it may prove a comfort. If we postulate, and we just have, that within un-, sub- or supernatural forces the probability is that the law of probability will not operate as a factor, then we must accept that the probability of the first part will not operate as a factor, in which case the law of probability will operate as a factor within un-, sub- or supernatural forces. And since it obviously hasn\'t been doing so, we can take it that we are not held within un-, sub- or supernatural forces after all; in all probability, that is. Which is a great relief to me personally.</item>
        <item>When is the last time you cared about something except yourself, hot rod\? You name me one time and I will take it all back. I didn\'t think so. These are good folk around here, who care about one another. I don\'t want \'em depending on someone they can\'t count on.</item>
        <item>Yesterday is history, tomorrow is a mystery, but today is a gift. That is why it is called the present.</item>
        <item>When another blames you or hates you, or people voice similar criticisms, go to their souls, penetrate inside and see what sort of people they are. You will realize that there is no need to be racked with anxiety that they should hold any particular opinion about you.</item>
        <item>What, then, is that incalculable feeling that deprives the mind of the sleep necessary to life\? A world that can be explained even with bad reasons is a familiar world. But, on the other hand, in a universe suddenly divested of illusions and lights, man feels an alien, a stranger. His exile is without remedy since he is deprived of the memory of a lost home or the hope of a promised land. This divorce between man and his life, the actor and his setting, is properly the feeling of absurdity.</item>
        <item>Give me reasons we should be complete. You should be with him, I can\'t compete. You looked at me like I was someone else, oh well, can\'t you see\? I don\'t wanna slow dance in the dark.</item>
        <item>Stay, you\'re not gonna leave me. This place is right where you need to be. And why your words gotta mean so much to them\? They mean nothing to me.</item>
        <item>Tell you what it is, Mr. Reid. Now we\'re four misfits who don\'t belong together, we\'re playing for the other misfits. They\'re the outcasts, right at the back of the room. We\'re pretty sure they don\'t belong either. We belong to them.</item>
        <item>And I think how hope may be the thing that pulls you forward, may be the thing that keeps you going, but that it\'s dangerous, too, that it\'s painful and risky, that it\'s making a dare to the world and when has the world ever let us win a dare\?</item>
        <item>Dragons live forever, but not so little boys. Painted wings and giants\' rings make way for other toys. One gray night it happened, Jackie Paper came no more. And Puff, that mighty dragon, he ceased his fearless roar. His head was bent in sorrow; green scales fell like rain. Puff no longer went to play along the cherry lane. Without his lifelong friend, Puff could not be brave. So Puff, that mighty dragon, sadly slipped into his cave.</item>
        <item>Lenin believed that the time to revolt and seize power had come. Again he encountered opposition within the party to his call for armed insurrection, most prominently Kamenev and Zinoviev. Most of the other party leaders, including Stalin, supported him.</item>
        <item>\"Aha! I\'m free!\" he screeched, then let loose an expletive at the men in his tinny, grating voice. The kobold pulled a small, round black pellet out of a pocket on the inside of his cape. He yelled \"smoke bomb!\" and then threw it at the floor with all the might his feeble body could muster. In an instant, the air in the hallway filled with a black sooty fog. The men were momentarily incapacitated as their raucous coughing masked the pitter-patter of escaping kobold feet.</item>
        <item>You and I, we\'ve been through a lot together. I look back and I just, uh, I appreciate all the times that... that we had together, you know\? I remember just going down in my room and, you know, dealing... tryin\' to deal with some things. And you\'ve always been there for that. Always. Just me and you.</item>
        <item>I don\'t wanna see you cry. You don\'t have to feel this emptiness. She said, \"I\'ll love you till the day that I die\". Well maybe she\'s right. \'Cause I don\'t wanna feel like I\'m not me. And to be honest I don\'t even know why I let myself get down in the first place.</item>
        <item>I just thought I\'d say thank you for doin\' a great job. So I thought I\'d let you stay with me. I mean, not with me! But there. Not with me there! But there in your own Cozy Cone. And I\'d be in my cone.</item>
        <item>While software development is immune from almost all physical laws, entropy hits us hard. Entropy is a term from physics that refers to the amount of \"disorder\" in a system. Unfortunately, the laws of thermodynamics guarantee that the entropy in the universe tends toward a maximum. When disorder increases in software, programmers call it \"software rot.\"</item>
        <item>A king may move a man, a father may claim a son, but that man can also move himself, and only then does that man truly begin his own game. Remember that howsoever you are played or by whom, your soul is in your keeping alone, even though those who presume to play you be kings or men of power. When you stand before God, you cannot say, \"But I was told by others to do thus,\" or that virtue was not convenient at the time. This will not suffice. Remember that.</item>
        <item>Now, why would Danny and Diane both be suffering from the same delusion in two cities over 1,000 miles apart\? Let\'s face it, folks. There are no alligators in the sewers. No, it\'s... it\'s around the campfire. It\'s bedtime stories. See, these stories are modern oral folklore. They are the unselfconscious reflection of the fears of urban society.</item>
        <item>Okay, let\'s just turn around then. Let\'s just go back, and we can write a nice little boring thesis regurgitating all the usual crap about urban legend. We\'ve got a real shot here, Bernadette. An entire community starts attributing the daily horrors of their lives to a mythical figure.</item>
        <item>Give me honorable enemies rather than ambitious ones, and I\'ll sleep more easily by night.</item>
        <item>Anything is edible if you deep fry it long enough.</item>
        <item>Have you heard the story of the guy who decided not to die\? He figured living was just easier than falling really high. His son heard about it later, thought, \"Maybe that is why I\'m enamored with the thought of seeing angels in the sky that are singing.\" And they\'re singing, saying, \"Everything\'s all right.\" I haven\'t heard that on Earth, so maybe I will find a place to sleep; just a comfortable place to lay my head.</item>
        <item>Focus. Control. Resolve. A true ace lacks none of these attributes. Nothing can deter you from the task at hand except your own fears. This is your sky.</item>
        <item>String theory, which posits that all the forces of nature stem from stringy thingies wriggling in nine or more dimensions, implies that our cosmos is just a hillock in a sprawling \"landscape\" of universes, some with radically different laws and dimensions than ours. Chaotic inflation, a supercharged version of the big bang theory, suggests that our universe is a minuscule bubble in a boundless, frothy sea.</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>